<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-06-25T20:29:45+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">The InnBox</title><subtitle>The InnBox is a weekly newsletter featuring unique, affordable places and spaces for busy folks who need a break.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How I make time to ‘see it all’ when I travel</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/how-to-see-it-all-while-traveling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I make time to 'see it all' when I travel" /><published>2018-06-23T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-06-23T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-to-see-it-all-while-traveling</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/how-to-see-it-all-while-traveling/">&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f6&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt; By
  &lt;span itemprop=&quot;author&quot; itemscope=&quot;&quot; itemtype=&quot;http://schema.org/Person&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot;&gt;&lt;span itemprop=&quot;name&quot;&gt;Sabrina Majeed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/seeitall/00.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
One of the most stressful aspects of planning a vacation is figuring out your itinerary. If you're like me then you may feel pressured to pack as much as possible into your trip in order to justify the financial investment— but bouncing around from one tourist site to another is no fun either and takes time away from one of the best parts of traveling: stumbling upon your own serendipitous discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This stress is especially maximized if your trip is time-boxed due to your work schedule. Over the years I've come to fall back on a few patterns which have helped me balance the desire to &quot;see it all&quot; with my desire to relax while I'm on vacation. I hope these tips are helpful to anyone else who feels overwhelmed when planning itineraries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;1. Identify legitimate &quot;FOMO&quot; from forced &quot;FOMO&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
90% of travel writers are going to tell you to skip any popular tourist attractions on the basis of it being too crowded, or &quot;ruined&quot;. I actually have an issue with this hipster approach to travel. Some places are popular &lt;i&gt;for a reason&lt;/i&gt; and you shouldn't deprive yourself of an experience just because other people want to experience it too. Approaching popular attractions with the positive mindset that I'm going to experience this place with other humans from all around the world usually makes me a little more zen about dealing with crowds. Now, while crowds don't bother me as much, lines and exorbitant entrance fees do. I still need a way to suss out what's worth the time and the cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl pb2 w-100&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/01.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;Hanging with the crowds at Pai Canyon. Still 100% worth coming here to view the sunset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
My rubric for sussing out what's worth it usually comes down to: &lt;b&gt;is this a place I can experience beyond just looking at it?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Do I have some understanding of the history and context of the place I'm visiting, or is it interactive in some way that makes physically going there different from looking at a picture or admiring it from afar?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Statue of Liberty is a good example. Personally I've always been more satisfied with taking the free Staten Island ferry across the river to get a good view of the statue without having to actually &lt;i&gt;go there&lt;/i&gt;. However, if my ancestors came to America through Ellis Island then I might have the historical and cultural context which would make physically going there more meaningful for me. So what's &quot;worth visiting&quot; is really a personal question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/02.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/03.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;Crowds on the beach at James Bond Island (photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/wangjs/2070015107/in/photolist-49VnnD-iGb2X5-qSf1U7-bzhZFv-df6isD-iG8ona-dt1ktv-iGckEu-ERpNyx-df6iuS-df65wp-df5iwA-bYAZo7-df57xH-df65F2-df57pq-df6inV-df6PkC-df5XBw-bYB56Q-df5XvK-df4TmW-df5qpW-df6dF3-49Vnsk-df5xw3-df6P3t-df6c51-97S7kY-fTSuu-df5Xpz-df6NMD-97NWo8-97P5fB-df6NXM-df65Kg-df5HfL-df6Dfx-df5abj-97S9Ms-97P1ki-W76uSG-df6NJT-df5JpP-df6pC1-df5aiF-4LXfnP-dxHTu3-df5qtC-df6bXn&quot;&gt;Jiashang&lt;/a&gt;) vs James Bond Island II.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Another example is James Bond Island near Phuket, which is popular because of the film &lt;i&gt;The Man with the Golden Gun&lt;/i&gt;. I'll admit, I experienced FOMO over this one after seeing stunning photos of it on Instagram. Then I realized that this place is &lt;i&gt;packed&lt;/i&gt; all day long and you can't really go up to the island, just look at it from the nearby beach. To me, this experience was the equivalent of looking at a photo. Instead, we chose to go on an evening tour which purposely by-passes James Bond Island. We didn't choose the tour for this reason but as a bonus it did take us to &quot;James Bond Island 2&quot; which may be less gravity-defying but also less crowded and allowed us to kayak right up to it. As a part of that tour we also got to see (and wave our hands through) bio-luminescent sea plankton, an experience you can't get from a photograph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;2. Travel ethically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Putting an emphasis on traveling ethically is another way to cut out a lot of &quot;popular&quot; attractions without any qualms about missing out. As a result of this mindset I didn't swim with the whale sharks in Cebu, one of the most popular things to do on the island, but as a result I had the time to visit an additional island in The Philippines. We also ended up not visiting a waterfall in Koh Samui because of it's affiliation with an exploitive elephant riding tour, which in turn left us with a lot more time to chill on the beach. Similarly, I personally didn't feel comfortable visiting any plantations in Savannah which made the pace of my short two day trip there a lot more relaxing in more ways than one. Choosing to abstain from an attraction because it is endangering animals or profitting off of people's pain is a much better reason than just because &quot;other people like this thing&quot;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;3. Treat down time like it's an attraction worth seeing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/04.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;Panglao Beach in The Philippines. We had nothing planned after arriving on the island of Bohol so we wandered over to the nearby beach to check it out and witnessed one of the most stunning sunsets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
For me, &quot;down-time&quot; doesn't mean doing nothing. It's just a block of time with nothing specific scheduled in it. People do this often at work— blocking out a chunk of time so colleagues wouldn't schedule meetings over it. I usually like to dedicate at least one day in every city I visit to this. It's become the equivalent of a sight I need to see when I travel. I'd like to experience what it would be like to live in the place I've traveled to, at least for one day.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&quot;Travel days&quot;, a.k.a. the days you arrive and depart a location are ideal for this. You're already probably wiped from your journey so you want to relax anyway. If you're arriving it's the perfect time to get acquainted with the new place without the stress of needing to get somewhere on time, and likewise it's a nice buffer on your way out to prevent yourself from overextending and then rushing to catch your flight/boat/train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;4. Arrive early, leave late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
With this in mind, I usually try to arrive early in the morning (even if that means taking a red-eye) and departing late in the evening in order to maximize the time that I have in that place. Since I stay in so many hotels this is also a way for me to maximize that expense, by having more time to utilize the facilities. When we have a late flight we're usually able to store our luggage at the hotel and then go do stuff for the rest of the day. Although in situations where we've stayed at an Airbnb and might need to carry our stuff around with us I always advocate for traveling for backpacks over suitcases when possible. I've also written before about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.buzzfeed.com/sabrinam13/19-things-that-make-traveling-alone-a-lot-less-stressful?utm_term=.pxDVlQlxN#.iqOBV0V3X&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;why backpacks are better for solo travelers.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/05.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;A night hike in Seoul, done a few hours before an 11PM departing flight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Another added bonus of the arrive early / leave late philosophy is that it scores you two extra meals wherever you're traveling to, which is very important if like me you travel to eat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;5. Think of countries regionally rather than as one singular entity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Something I struggled with when I first started traveling was this idea that I would only go to a certain country or city once in my lifetime. I felt like with limited funds and a whole world out there to see, I couldn't go back to the same place twice which made me feel like I really had to hit up all those famous landmarks. Something that helped me get over this was to think of my destinations more in terms of regions or neighborhoods than specific attractions or sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;If I focused too much on specific sites I would end up with a very scattered itinerary and a lot of time wasted traveling from place to place. When I focus on a region this is inclusive of both the tourist sites within that region but also the time to discover daily life in that location. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/06.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;An adorable dessert shop in Phuket Old Town we stumbled upon during &quot;down time&quot; shortly after arriving in town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Thailand is a great example. It's a really popular itinerary to hop from Bangkok to Chiang Mai in the north to one of the southern islands in order to get a little taste of everything Thailand has to offer. I think this can work &lt;i&gt;if&lt;/i&gt; you have a significant amount of time but for those taking vacation days off from work I actually think it's better to pick one region and experience everything there because whether you go north, south, or central, there will be no shortage of beautiful sights and tasty food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Thinking of things regionally has helped me curb this notion of not wanting to go back to somewhere I've already been. It's less &quot;I've already been to Thailand&quot; and more &quot;I've been to Northern Thailand, next time I want to go to the South&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;6. Plan a circular itinerary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you are going to visit multiple sites in a day, multiple neighborhoods in a weekend, multiple cities in a trip, it's usually better to plan a circular route than to travel back and forth from a central location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Even though conventional knowledge is that round trip flights are cheaper than one way, it's usually not that &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; cheaper and you can save a few hours with a more streamlined path. This also applies to where you're staying. In big metropolitan areas like Seoul I'll even plan to move hotels or airbnbs so that I can more conveniently explore different neighborhoods instead of having to go back and forth. The added bonus is that I get to stay in more cute places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/07.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;I arrived in Flam after taking a train from Oslo and transferring to a smaller train. Rather than repeating my steps to get back on the train track to Bergen I decided to take a ferry directly from the port in Flam instead, which also offered me an up close view of the fjords.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;When I was in Norway I visited Oslo, Bergen, and Tromsø. It would've been a little cheaper to fly back to Oslo from Bergen and then get on another flight to Tromsø, but instead I paid a little bit more for a direct flight and got my first experience flying on a propeller plane as a result. Which kind of leads me to my next point...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;6. View your mode of transportation as an excursion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/08.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;Taking a rocky boat ride to Ometepe island in Nicaragua; riding a cable car to Lantau Island in Hong Kong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;As they say: it's about the journey not the destination. When you're visiting another country, if you plan to visit more than one city you are inevitably going to spend a lot of time in transit. If you can make that mode of transportation something novel, something that's exciting and fully a part of the experience, then you won't feel like you're wasting time in transit. For me, personally, boat rides are always exciting. It's just not something I do every day so I don't mind taking ferries to get around. Even when they're slightly unpleasant and I feel seasick, I feel like it's a part of the experience. For folks who don't fly often, getting on an airplane may provide a similar feeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/seeitall/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc mid-gray mb3 mb4-ns i f7&quot;&gt;Gamcheon Cultural Village in Busan, South Korea. Tourist-y? Yes. Worth it? Yes. Plus conveniently located on a circuit with fellow attractions Taejongdae Park and BIFF Square.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;I hope this helps reduce some of the stress and anxiety associated with planning itineraries, but if all else fails just remember this: you're going somewhere different from your day to day so it's going to be exciting no matter what. Even if you don't see any major tourist attractions. Even if it that's all you see. At the end of the day it's still a vacation and the only way you can mess that up is if you forget to delete Slack from your phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of my travel guides:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/bariloche/bariloche_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Your travel guide to Bariloche, Argentina: where to stay and what to do.&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/granada-nicaragua-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/granada/NICA_HEADER.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/granada-nicaragua-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Your travel guide to Granada, Nicaragua: where to stay and what to do.&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">By Sabrina Majeed</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where to stay in Portland, Maine (and Kennebunkport)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-portland-maine/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where to stay in Portland, Maine (and Kennebunkport)" /><published>2018-06-10T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-06-10T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-portland-maine</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-portland-maine/">&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;../images/portlandme/header.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Why go to Portland?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The two things I get the most excited about when I travel are 1.) Food and 2.) Nature— Portland, Maine has both of those in spades. The city has a reputation for being a foodie paradise, and is rumored to have more restaurants per capita than other city in the U.S. after San Francisco (including &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wweek.com/portland/blog-27050-whats-with-all-the-thai-restaurants-in-portland.html&quot;&gt;a surprising amount of Thai restaurants&lt;/a&gt;). For nature, simply get in your car and drive in either direction on the coastal Route 1: going south will take you the most photographed lighthouse in America and seaside lobster rolls at Cape Elizabeth, as well as the dog-friendly beaches of Kennebunkport. Head north and do a little shopping at L.L. Bean HQ before continuing on your way to Bar Harbor and Acadia National Park. August also marks blueberry season— and you'll find the sweet wild Maine blueberries jammed or embedded into baked goods all along the coast.

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
In addition to places to stay near Downtown Portland, we've included recommendations in Kennebunkport because their lodging game is &lt;i&gt;on point&lt;/i&gt;. Kennebunkport is a 20 minute drive away from Portland and ideal for those who prefer more of a small seaside town feel as opposed to Portland's urban New England vibes. Rates are based on a one-night search for August 2018. The InnBox may collect a share of sales from booking links on this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thepresshotel.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Press Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $290/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/press_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/press_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/press_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/press_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Portland's current boutique hotel darling (think the east coast equivalent of Portland, Oregon's Ace Hotel). The hotel occupies the former Portland Press Herald Building and channels its publishing past into the decor— with gorgeous desks and leather writing chairs (perfect for work-from-hotel types), herringbone textures, and letterpress references abound which should please aspiring writers and typography nerds alike. The hotel is a part of Marriott's Autograph collection and if you book directly through their site you can take advantage of their 'flexible booking' feature which shows you the lowest rate for each month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The Press Hotel has elevators and in-room accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/25328&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Antique Chic Decor in South Portland&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $91/Night — 1 Bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/airbnb_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/airbnb_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/airbnb_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/airbnb_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Sophie's South Portland apartment is a case study in doing Airbnb right. An affordable, unique, dog-friendly space in a convenient location with a friendly and communicative host who even drops off bagels for guests. This was where we stayed during our trip to Portland and I highly recommend it. Sophie's place comes in three different configurations— large groups can book the whole place while couples can book the individual floors. We opted to stay on the second floor which was more spacious and next to the gorgeous, shared kitchen space (we actually never encountered any other guests while using the kitchen so it felt very private to us). What I loved about the space was that even though the kitchen was technically shared our space had its own private living and dining area outside of the bedroom. Street parking was free and readily available right behind the apartment, and it was only a 5-10 minute drive across the bridge to anywhere we wanted to go in Downtown Portland. Your stay also comes with a free yoga class at the studio on the first floor but we were too busy to take advantage of it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is located on the second and third floor of a building and only accessibly by a stairway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mercuryinn.com/rooms/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Mercury Inn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $165/Night — Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/mercury_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/mercury_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/mercury_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/mercury_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Mercury Inn is a modern take on the classic bed and breakfast with a focus on sustainability. It's operated by a pair of charming husbands who channeled their combined interests in Greco-Roman mythology, food, and hospitality into this project. It's also pretty cool that the philosophy for the Mercury Inn was informed by one of the owner's experiences working as an intern in homeless shelter communities, &quot;learning what people require fundamentally to feel safe and comfortable in a space that is not their own&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;All rooms are located on the second and third floor of the building, with no elevator access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/pomegranate-inn.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Pomegranate Inn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $279/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/pome_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/pome_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/pome_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/pome_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I'll admit— I'm not the biggest fan of the traditional bed-and-breakfast aesthetic. They can sometimes feel a bit stuffy and outdated. However, Pomegranate Inn manages to take the classic Victorian vibe and make give it a fresh twist thanks to bold wallpaper, painted walls, and playful pattern mixing. The Inn is located in downtown Portland's West End neighborhood, which has been called &quot;one of the best preserved Victorian neighborhoods in the country&quot; by the Minnesota Star Tribune. It is also one of the most gay-friendly neighborhoods in the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There doesn't appear to be elevator access at Pomegranate Inn, but we recommend contacting the hotel directly for more accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/the-cottages-at-cabot-cove.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Cottages at Cabot Cove&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $249/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/cabot_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/cabot_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/cabot_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/cabot_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The perfect place for living out your fantasy of shacking up in a charming seaside cottage à la Diane Lane in &lt;i&gt;Nights in Rodanthe&lt;/i&gt;. Okay, her inn was a lot bigger, but you get the idea. These petite cottages are embued with tons of charm, dreamy robin's egg blue exteriors, and the small size will feel right at home to urban dwellers. Cabot Cove, itself a body of water, inspired the name of the fictional &quot;Cabot Cove&quot; seaside town setting in the famous series Murder, She Wrote. But don't worry, unlike its fictional counterpart the real Cabot Cove is &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; safe and idyllic. Book three months out for the best rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
All of the cottages are located on the ground floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/captain-jefferds-inn.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Captain Jefferds Inn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $259&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/jefferds_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/jefferds_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/jefferds_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/jefferds_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This is our top pick for dog owners! While Maine is generally very dog-friendly, there are many hotels who simply tolerate your pup's presence in exchange for a hefty fee— but it seems like the staff at Captain Jeffers truly love dogs and get that our pups are part of our family. The Inn has a carriage house with five dog friendly units, and an additional fee of $35 per dog per day which is actually very reasonable as many other hotels are in the $50-75 range. The fee covers cleaning but also some bonuses for your pet: a personalized dog treat, doggy bowls, towels/sheets, and as many pick up bags as you need. The hotel also offers in-room dog-sitting at $15/hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
There are ground floor units at Captain Jefferds Inn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/kennebunkport-inn-kennebunkport.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Kennebunkport Inn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $279/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/kenne_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/kenne_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/kenne_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/portlandme/kenne_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This picturesque port town hotel will make you feel like you're crashing at your friend's rich New England parent's house. The hotel has an amazing outdoor patio space for entertaining, and a very tasteful application of a nautical color scheme. There are older, more traditional bed-and-breakfast style rooms available as well as rooms with a more modern interpretation of the theme.
Your stay also comes with complimentary use of the beach cruiser bicycles on site, which you can use to navigate around Dock Square, the central area in Kennebunkport where the hotel is located.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Kennebunkport Inn has in-room accessibility and roll-in showers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: SALA Phuket Resort &amp;amp; Spa in Phuket, Thailand</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sala-phuket-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: SALA Phuket Resort &amp; Spa in Phuket, Thailand" /><published>2018-04-30T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sala-phuket-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sala-phuket-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; May 8 — 10, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $249/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;dib&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Sabrina&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/sala/01.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you've been following The Innbox for awhile now, you've probably picked up on the fact that I'm not a big fan of resorts. My main reasons for avoiding them being that they are expensive, often devoid of any personality, and too insulated from the actual place you're there to visit. I know, I know, &lt;i&gt;#notallresorts&lt;/i&gt;— that's exactly what this review is about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Since my birthday was coming up, I really wanted to treat myself. What would make a self-proclaimed hotel nerd happier than spending the entire day in a beautiful, well designed space? Though I've stayed in many hotels over the years, I'm always balancing time relaxing at the place I'm staying at with adventuring out into the city I'm visiting. This time, I didn't want to feel pressured to go outside. I wanted to just be able to fully relax and enjoy myself. Which is when it started to occur to me... &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; might be why some people do the resort thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
It kind of makes sense, right? If you're going to spend the money to stay at a resort, you might as well... &lt;i&gt;stay&lt;/i&gt; at the resort. We still booked a few days in Phuket at a cheaper hostel for the days when we would actually go out and explore the island.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I decided on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=89341&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;SALA Phuket&lt;/a&gt; because it was an outlier in my research. Most of the resorts in Phuket that actually had unique, interesting looking suites were generally in the over $450/night range. While the more affordable resorts all had that standard sleek, minimalist look which I know I could experience at the average hotel for much less. I liked the SALA's use of patterns and their beautiful balance of indoor and outdoor spaces. I also liked that SALA is a home-grown Thai hospitality company, as opposed to the plethora of international chains that have made their way to Phuket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We arrived at the Sala Phuket at exactly 4 PM— their designated check-in time. After being greeted with a refreshing glass of lemongrass iced tea and a short wait, we were escorted to our suite by one of the hotel staff. They gave us a quick tour of the premises and then left us to enjoy ourselves in our new space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/02.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/03.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
In case guests arrive before 4 PM, the hotel also has a designated guest lounge and library for people to hang out in while they wait for their room to be ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Suite&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Sala Phuket offers a vast range of different room options, from the most affordable balcony rooms (starting at a little over $112/night) to expansive two-bedroom pool villas (up to $450). We opted for the Sala Pool Suite, the resort's most popular option at just under $250/night which nabs you a glamorous little enclave with its own private pool.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Upon entering the suite the first thing we saw was its centerpiece— a bright blue pool that's the perfect size for two to four people to comfortably enjoy. Directly across from the entrance is a narrow, glass windowed building which serves as the suite's bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/04.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/06.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/07.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/05.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The bedroom has an extremely spacious layout: there's a large king bed right in the middle of the room, with plenty of space for a desk on one side of it and a sofa and coffee-table on the other. There is a narrow walkway behind the bed reserved for the mini-bar as well as closet space. I was relieved to find that one of the closets had a full-length mirror in it; an amenity that should be guarantee but isn't always.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/08.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Like many hotels in Asia, electricity in the suite is controlled by your key. While inside we always managed to stay comfortably cool thanks to the 5-speed fans, which can be controlled for either side of the room. The room's small living area also includes a comfortable sofa which I could easily see being used as an additional bed for a small child. In the middle of the day when it was too hot to be outdoors we retreated inside the breezy bedroom and spent the next few hours lounging around watching cable TV movies on the flatscreen before it was cool enough for another dip in the pool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Bathroom&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The outdoor bathroom is one of the suite's highlights— particularly the glamorous soak tub that overlooks the pool. The  tub even comes stocked with Himalayan bath salts and a tray that's perfect for balancing a glass of wine or a book on while you enjoy your soak. The only downside to the bath situation is that because it's so big, it took a considerable amount of time to fill the tub with water.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
For quicker rinses there's also an outdoor shower on a wooden platform to the right of the bath tub. There's an optional privacy curtain you can use around it if needed, although when not in use it adds to the suite's palatial ambiance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/15.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Kitty corner from the shower is the outdoor toilet, which feels quite private thanks to its clever placement. It's also conveniently located by one of the side doors in the bedroom suite for quick access. The only downside to the outdoor toilet situation is, unsurprisingly, the potential for unwanted 'guests'. In the middle of the night I woke up really needing to go and came outside to find a huge cicada just chilling in front of the toilet. I tried to hold it for another ten minutes, hoping the bug would go away on its own. I tried to flap a towel at it and it wouldn't move. Eventually I had to resort to swiftly reaching around and grabbing the bum-gun (that's the water hose next to most toilets in Asian countries) and forcefully spray the cicada off the platform and back into the nearby bushes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I do want to make it clear though that despite the unwanted intruder, the bathroom is &lt;i&gt;impeccably&lt;/i&gt; clean. Cleaner than many indoor bathrooms in hotels I've stayed at. I think the resort does an amazing job at maintaining a space that's ripe for insect life— we are staying on an island after all, so it's to be expected. There were occasionally baby geckos hanging around the walls of the toilet area but they are always harmless and if anything help to deter other pests from the area. For anyone who really can't deal, some of the less expensive rooms and suites do have indoor bathrooms that look just as nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/17.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/18.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/19.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
To the left of the mirror is a spacious lounge area, outfitted with the same plush pillows as the couch indoors. After building up an appetite from swimming we'd enjoy our room service out here before heading right back to the pool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The food at SALA certainly ranks in my top hotel food experiences, and was on par with what I would expect for a resort. Their breakfast, which was inclusive with our rate, consists of both a vast breakfast buffet &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; your choice of a made-to-order entree from their menu. I ordered the salmon bagel which seemed to be one of their most popular choices at breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/21.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/22.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/23.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The buffet included a cereal/yogurt/granola bar at one end of the room, a hot food bar at the other, a vegetarian/mezze and cold cut station in the middle, a fruit stand, and a toast station with a vast array of spreads to choose from. That's not including the drinks where in addition to your choice between their signature teas (roselle and lemongrass) they also offered vegetable tonics in shot form and — the crème de la crème — a complimentary bloody mary bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/24.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We took advantage of room service a couple of times during our stay— and I have to admit I actually preferred the room service meals I ordered to the meal we ate when we actually ventured down to the restaurant for dinner. For room service I ordered their lamb meatballs one day and their open faced steak sandwich the next, both of which were delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/20.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The menu options are expanded if you physically go to the restaurant for dinner. I would characterize the majority of the menu as a modernized spin on classic Thai dishes. We ordered their fancy version of Miang Kham and a curry dish and while both were good— I could pay a fraction of the price for the same dish at the local street stalls in our neighborhood in Bangkok. So for me the highlights of their menu were the more distinctly western dishes that I can't easily get elsewhere in Thailand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;It's funny, since I normally stay in hotels with cozy little rooms, I find myself hanging out in the common areas more often. This was not the case at the SALA Phuket. With our own private pool and outdoor lounging area &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; room service available, we had little reason to leave the privacy of our suite outside of going to breakfast. That said, there are some really nice facilities here that I would've taken more advantage of if we had a longer stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/25.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There's a small but clean on-site gym on the hotel grounds with a few machines and hand-weight racks. When I saw it I definitely thought to myself &quot;I'm totally going to work out here&quot; but then I went back to my suite and drank a glass of wine instead.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/26.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/27.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;In the same area as the gym there's also a hair salon, spa, and a sauna.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/28.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/29.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The resort's restaurant has both an indoor and outdoor area, with plenty of lounge seating and a roof deck. There's also two communal pools. The restaurant and pool are located right by the property's private beach. Compared to other beaches across Thailand and other countries in Southeast Asia, it's not particularly noteworthy but it is clean and peaceful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/30.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/31.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;We didn't have too much interaction with hotel staff outside from check-in/out and food service but everyone we interacted with was really pleasant. I was also really impressed with their turndown service— aside from turning down the sheets they also come and set up mosquito repellant lights by your bed and also in the outdoor bathroom area, as well as leave you a bottle of one of their homemade teas to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/32.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/33.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;In addition, because we stayed during my birthday, the hotel sent a complimentary chocolate cake to our suite! It was super fudge-y and surprisingly big (I thought they'd send, like, a slice but it was the whole damn cake). I really appreciated the thoughtful touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The SALA Phuket is conveniently located very close to the airport, in an area with a few other resorts like the Renaissance Phuket and JW Marriott Phuket. There's not much to do within walking distance, and no real reason to venture out to the immediate area around the resort. I didn't mind this since I wanted to justify the cost of the resort by spending a lot of time &lt;i&gt;in&lt;/i&gt; it, and there was little temptation to leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
You would definitely need to hire a car or cab to come and take you to many of the popular sites on the island.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/34.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I'm genuinely surprised that a resort of this size seems so inaccessible for wheelchair users. At the very least our suite was: the entrance requires going up a short flight of steps, there's another short step elevating the outdoor bathroom area from the pool, and then a narrow walkway between the pool's edge and the entrance to the bedroom. They may have other suites that are more accessible but I haven't seen it advertised anywhere. Also, I can't recall any paved ramps for accessing the private beach. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sala/35.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I would recommend SALA Phuket as a &quot;starter&quot; resort for folks like me who aren't quite sold yet on the resort experience and want to try it out for a reasonable price. While $250/night is definitely no chump change, when considering resorts in Phuket, SALA is definitely one of the more accessible venues— and it's a good deal when taking into consideration the space, private pool, and inclusive breakfast. If you're still not convinced you can take a look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/200-dollars-airbnb-new-york-city/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;how far $200 would get you in New York City&lt;/a&gt; for a comparison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
To save even more money you could go for one of their balcony suites, sans pool, which start at a little over $100/night in low season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While I can't see myself doing the resort thing for every beach trip, I'm definitely considering staying at other SALA locations throughout Thailand. Their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=1624710&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Ko Samui&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=209973&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Khao Yai&lt;/a&gt; locations are particularly tempting. I love that the design is slightly different in each location but still has that mix of romance and modernity that is distinct to the SALA brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;
Please use our link below to book at SALA Phuket Resort &amp;amp; Spa (or any other hotel!). The InnBox may collect a small share of sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=89341&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ SALA Phuket&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/muji-hotel-shenzhen-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/muji/00_Cover.jpg'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/muji-hotel-shenzhen-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The first ever MUJI Hotel in Shenzhen, Guangdong, China&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/mbs/17.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Marina Bay Sands in Singapore&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: May 8 — 10, 2018 Rate: $249/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: Hotel 1 in Busan, South Korea</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hotel-1-busan-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: Hotel 1 in Busan, South Korea" /><published>2018-04-30T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hotel-1-busan-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hotel-1-busan-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; April 24 — 26, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $77/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;dib&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Sabrina&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/hotel1/00.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Sunlight sparkles across the water on Gwangan Beach and reflects off the bright, white marble walls of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=2962286&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Hotel 1&lt;/a&gt; in Busan. The resulting effect makes it feel like you're floating amongst the clouds— it's a modern, minimalist take on a hotel in Heaven. There's even free snacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While it's the trendy marble aesthetic that draws you in, it's the clever and fun details like cozy plaid robes, stuffed animal pillows, and smart layouts that seal the deal— and keep the minimalist vibe from feeling full mausoleum. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This hotel is probably one of my favorite &quot;finds&quot;, and I truly mean &quot;find&quot; as I didn't come across it until my third or fourth intense research session looking for places to stay in Busan. Nothing was really speaking to me until I came across a photo of a girl in a white marble room, with the brilliant blue sea behind her. A white marble hotel? I whispered a small prayer to the hotel pricing gods and clicked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The hotel is fairly straight-forward to reach via public transit from Busan station: just hop on the 41 bus and it will practically take you to the hotel's front steps. After a 40 minute ride you'll get off at a bus stop just a couple of small blocks away from the hotel, which sits right on the coast of Gwangan Beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/01.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/02.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/03.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Upon entering the hotel, you'll be asked to take off your shoes. This is a practice we abide by at home but which I'd never encountered in a hotel before. The no-shoes policy supported the hotel's stark, clean, and almost museum-like vibe. Plus sliding around on the marble tiled floors in socks felt pretty good. Upon check-in we were given our room key and directed to the storage lockers for shoes to the right of the lobby. The room key also allows you to easily lock and unlock your designated shoe cubby. Pretty advanced, TBH. With our shoes stored away we padded over to the elevator to head up to our room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Hotel 1 is unique because it offers rooms at three separate tiers for different types of budgets and travelers. There are &quot;capsule&quot; style rooms that come with either single beds or bunks, then there are the mid-tier &quot;slim&quot; rooms that are ideal for couples who can get cozy, and lastly the &quot;mansion&quot; tier rooms which are more spacious and offer a sense of luxury and expansive views. In addition to the size tiers there's also small price difference between rooms with a beach versus a city view. It is 100% worth paying for a beach view room. Later I will show you exactly which rooms you'll want to request for the best view.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/04.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We decided to opt for the slim room instead of splurging on a mansion. Partially to save a little bit of money and also out of curiosity for how they would pack everything in to such a narrow and small space. Plus as former New Yorkers, small space living was nothing we weren't used to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&quot;Slim&quot; was no exaggeration. The room was as wide as the bed, and the shower, toilet, and sink all take up about half of the bed's width, with the other half serving as your hallway. Because the bed is placed on an elevated platform the room takes advantage of storage underneath it, and uses that platform as a &quot;chair&quot; for a small desk that is positioned behind the shower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/05.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/06.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We had just enough room for our two large bags, which we stored at the end of the bed platform, and placed smaller bags on the desk. We could've placed our luggage on the available space by the window but we liked having that space free for us to relax by. Speaking of that window...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/07.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/08.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The view really sealed the deal for me. Whether it was sunrise, cloudy (when these photos were taken), sunny, or nighttime it was like staring out into a real life postcard. We were lucky to have the most perfectly positioned room at our tier, with a window that sticks out a little bit and is angled towards the main crescent of the beach, and the skyscrapers across the water. I've highlighted the rooms with the best views below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you look at the facade of the hotel you'll see that the middle section extrudes. If you book a &quot;mansion&quot; class room then you want to book the rooms that occupy that extruded space and will give you a full panoramic view, or a corner room on the right side of the hotel (if you are standing across the street facing the hotel). If you are booking a slim or capsule room than you want to book the room on the right side of the extrusion. Any other room on the ocean view side will still give you a nice view of the water and Gwangan Bridge (which has a light show at night) but the angled windows will offer a more panoramic view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The room also comes supplied with a MUJI blow dryer and water heater, and an electronic back massager, stored under your bed. The flatscreen TV is also equipped with a Chromecast so you can mirror videos from your phone. Then there's the plaid flannel &quot;robes&quot;. It was a nice departure from the usual fluffy white hotel robe, which you'd probably expect considering the aesthetics of the place, but the red plaid injected a burst of color and personality. They were also comfy as hell and I truly think the hotel should make them available for purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Bathroom&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The bathroom is less a self-contained room itself than a series of small boxes. One contains the shower, which although small (there's about 4 square feet of standing room in the slim room shower) still managed to feel luxurious. There's a lovely green and white marble tile used on the shower walls and sink, which at first I was like &quot;hmm that's kind of weird&quot; but then started to slowly fall in love with. Again, it's these small injections of color in this otherwise stark white marble palace that have such a big impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fn center mb3 mb4-ns tc&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The other cool thing about the shower is that the rainbath faucet is directly built in to the ceiling, which really sells that sense of immersion than rainbaths try to offer. The shower UI (Can we call it that? Can I make that a thing?) is also pleasantly straight forward, and in addition to the rainbath, and handheld shower head mode, there's also a normal faucet mode ideally for rinsing sandy beach feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/15.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The toilet is located in a separate self contained room next to the shower. There's not too much to say about that. There's a mirror in the room for some reason, and a cute white radio that doesn't get the best signal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/17.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/18.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The sink, which is sandwiched between the door and the toilet room, appears small but packs a surprising amount of surface and storage space. My only complaint is that it does a get a little dark in the sink area because the bathroom and shower stalls are blocking the light from the windows. However, as if the hotel is aware of this, there is a small stand mirror on the desk by the bed which gets unobstructed light on the ocean side of the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/19.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Hotel 1 has some fun common areas to explore. The first floor houses the pantry area (more on that later) with some stadium seating facing the water. The seating and pillows are accentuated by cute, fluffy stuffed animals to lean on. This dining area is branded as the &quot;Byul Bed Cafe&quot;.  
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/20.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This same motif is present on the second floor of the hotel, which includes more traditional dining seating and seating options for groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/21.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The top floor houses an exposed roof deck with a generous amount of patio seating, but perhaps because of the rainy and not entirely warm April weather, it was pretty dead up there during our stay. The deck is supposedly open between 6pm and midnight but we were able to access it during the day— and when we did try to go at night it was a total ghost town. I imagine it's probably more lively during the summer, otherwise the hotel could do a better job of making it an inviting space and encouraging guests to take advantage of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/22.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;We didn't have too much interaction with the staff, but everyone was polite and friendly. The staff may not be the most proficient in English, which is understandable as it seems like the hotel doesn't receive too many western guests, but they will try their best to answer any questions you have. If you're patient and not a jerk, it will be fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The food situation at Hotel 1 was both kind of cool, and kind of perplexing. What is cool is that there's a whole big pantry area with snacks that are &lt;i&gt;unlimited&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;free&lt;/i&gt; with your stay for the taking, including ice cream and juice. The only items that you have to pay for are instant noodles and beer. I think this is especially great for travelers on a budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/23.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The less cool part was that the hotel offers a breakfast buffet in the mornings for $9 per person but the offerings are... pretty weak. You still need to go to that same pantry area to get your food, but the only difference is there's a few muffins and other types of baked goods set out. The options were about as varied as the grab-and-go options at your local Starbucks. Maybe it was slim pickings because we arrived on the later half of the breakfast service but... I can't imagine what I saw being worth the $9. On the other hand, if you need to eat early there aren't too many places open before 11AM in the immediate area, although there is a mini-mart next door, so pick your poison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The hotel is in a very central area on Gwangan beach, one of the two major beaches in Busan. While Haeundae is the more popular beach, I actually preferred the vibe of Gwangan. It was definitely more picturesque— as you get the view looking out towards the buildings near Haeundae rather being amongst them, and it was a little quieter and less crowded. Having been to both I also noticed that many of the bars and restaurants in Haeundae also have a branch in Gwangan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/24.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Gwangan was also a better base for us to visit the main sights we came to see in Busan, like Taejongdae Park, Jagalchi Fish Market, and Gamcheon Cultural Village, as its closer to them than Haeundae. Public transit, whether by bus or metro line, was also super accessible from Hotel 1. It was probably a five minute walk &lt;i&gt;at most&lt;/i&gt; to the nearest stop for either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Hotel 1 does have an elevator and claims to have rooms with in-room accessibility. I will say from my experience that the &quot;slim&quot; rooms do not seem wheelchair friendly, so I would avoid that tier and also inquire directly with the hotel to make sure the room you're booking is accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hotel1/25.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I highly recommend for any visitors to Busan to stay at Hotel 1.
I appreciate that they have room options for every budget. If you're traveling solo, go for the capsule rooms. If you're a couple, get cozy in a slim room, if you're a group of friends then go for the mansions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Hotel 1 has such a fresh, youthful vibe that stills feels classy and upscale. Come for the white marble aesthetic, stay and fall in love with all the clever little details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;
Please use our link below to book at Gwanganli Hotel 1 (or any other hotel!). The InnBox may collect a small share of sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=2962286&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ Hotel 1&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/muji-hotel-shenzhen-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/muji/00_Cover.jpg'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/muji-hotel-shenzhen-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The first ever MUJI Hotel in Shenzhen, Guangdong, China&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/mbs/17.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Marina Bay Sands in Singapore&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Mintlodica</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: April 24 — 26, 2018 Rate: $77/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: The first ever MUJI Hotel in Shenzhen, Guangdong, China</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/muji-hotel-shenzhen-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: The first ever MUJI Hotel in Shenzhen, Guangdong, China" /><published>2018-04-30T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/muji-hotel-shenzhen-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/muji-hotel-shenzhen-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; April 5 — 6, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $150/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;dib&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/mintlodica/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Mintlodica&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/muji/00_Cover.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotel.muji.com/shenzhen/en/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;MUJI Hotel&lt;/a&gt; provides a ‘just enough’ stay in Shenzhen, the most cyberpunk city of China. MUJI’s minimalism is a true contrast to the city’s modern copy and paste development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Finding the hotel was not a straightforward task. Beware, at the time of writing, Google Maps has the incorrect location. Additionally, the hotel happens to be inside a mall so you won’t be able to see it from the street. If coming by car, there is a loading curb right in front of the entrance. However, it was easier for drivers to pick up and drop off out on the main street of the mall. Like a lot of new malls in China, only a third of the stores in the mall were open. If you’re coming in from the front doors, go up the escalators to the second floor and then take the hallway to the left and exit. The hotel is right outside the doors, across from a Sony store. You’ll be greeted with relief and the iconic signage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/01_Hotel_A.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/01_Hotel_B.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Check in itself was easy. Make sure to bring the credit card you booked with and your passport. The front desk staff speaks both Chinese (Mandarin and Cantonese) and English. They honored my request for a top floor room. The hotel is minimally decorated throughout with only a few indoor plants and floral arrangements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/01_Hotel_C.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/01_Hotel_D_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/01_Hotel_D_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The BGM that plays in all MUJI stores follows you wherever you go. You truly do get the feeling you are staying inside the store. The room numbers shine brightly against the wooden hallways. To unlock your room, tap the key card against the sensor lock.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I booked the most affordable room since I was staying by myself. There are 5 different room types: A, B, C, D, and E, each increasing in size and amenities. Despite the five levels, the most expensive room tops out at $400 and still follows the 'just enough' ethos. In my Type A room, there was a full length mirror to my right and a closet with a robe, 2 pairs of slippers, a safe, and clothes drying rack to the left of the entrance. Turning the corner from the small hallway, I see the bed and armchair areas and become smitten.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_A.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_B_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_B_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The bed is a platform frame MUJI bed with their wonderfully firm MUJI mattress and attached is nightstand on each side. The perfectly fluffed blanket made it extra inviting to go to bed. Across from the bed, there was also a TV and a desk with a concealed lamp inside the upper shelf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_C.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Feast your eyes upon the most MUJI Hotel amenities shelf! Inside the cabinet underneath is an empty mini fridge. On top, for your use is a MUJI water kettle, bone china coffee and tea cups, instant drip coffees (one caffeinated, one not), and rooibos tea. Although I own most of these products in my home, it was such a joy to see them all together and use them all at once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_D.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_E_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_E_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
By the window is an armchair, small coffee table, and ottoman. This was my favorite part of the room. I was still jet lagged during my stay, so I woke up early to make a MUJI drip coffee and drank it in the morning light. I usually find hotel armchairs unappealing, but the MUJI armchair and ottoman felt soft yet supportive. Like so, I have now added their modular sofas to my furniture wishlist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The only piece of art in the room is the minimal wood art above the armchair. Instead of hanging large art pieces, the hotel chooses to prominently feature the materials making up the walls of the room themselves. The materials for the rooms were sourced from traditional Chinese homes. There is finished wood, a mat texture, and grey concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
It would’ve been nice if there was a view beyond the room, but alas you are in a mall in a newly developed area, so there is only the concrete rooftop or the street to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_F_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_F_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_G.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Finally, there is the iconic Naota Fukasawa CD player with BGM loaded up. My room had BGM CD 7, but you can borrow any of their CDs from the front desk. While you listen to MUJI BGM, you can page through the MUJI brand book. There is a copy of it in every room and you can borrow one in English if you want to read it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_H_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/02_Bed_H_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Visiting the hotel is a great way to 'try before you buy' any MUJI products you are curious about. In the hotel guidebook, there is a list of items to you borrow from the front desk including their aroma humidifier. Another list tells you can take as keepsakes from your time at the hotel. These items are: the 2 house slippers, 2 toothbrushes, the bathroom vanity kit, black gel pen, coffees, and the waters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt; Bathrooms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The bathroom in my room did not have any windows and was underwhelming. In comparison to the rest of the room, it lacks the same amount of finesse. I was a disappointed to see my bathroom only had a shower stall. I had been on my feet for a good part of four days and was looking forward to a good soak. Upon second look of the website, it’s clear only the higher tier rooms D and E had fuller bathrooms with tubs. It’s listed as a feature of those rooms, but I had assumed all mid-tier hotel rooms had come with a bathtub these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/03_Bathroom_A.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I will say though the Japanese Toto Washlet was nice. The toilet had its own door which would be a great bonus when having to share a room. Inside the vanity kit you can take home is a travel sized toothpaste, make-up pads, q-tips, and 2 shower caps. You won't be able to take little bottles of soap home since the bathrooms are outfitted with big MUJI soap dispensers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The third floor of the hotel hosts shared amenities.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/04_Commons_A.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The lobby features a library with design books you can read. There are also 3 meeting rooms you can book at cost on this floor.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/04_Commons_B_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/04_Commons_B_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There is a gym with some work out machines, towels, and bottled waters. This is minimal as far as hotel gyms go. No pool, sauna, classes, or staff actively attending the share amenities area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Service was all right. The staff was polite during our interactions, but did not go above or beyond unless responding to a request. They did keep my luggage safe the day I checked out and went off to explore Shenzhen, but that is a perk of staying with any hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/05_Diner_A.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/05_Diner_B.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/05_Diner_C.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The hotel only has one eatery, the MUJI Diner. It's decorated much like the standalone MUJI Cafes in Asias with beautiful kitchenware objects. The reception area of the diner also has a small library and bar. One side of the diner shares a wall with the store, so there are books on either side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/05_Diner_D.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The hours of the diner are 6:30 to 23:00. Breakfast is included with your booking, but you may also have lunch, dinner, and drinks there later in the day. I only had breakfast at the diner. The diner was empty at 8:00 when I showed up and got more packed closer to 9:00. It opens at 6:30 for breakfast. The way it works is that you pick a set breakfast: Chinese, Japanese, or Western. You are limited to 1 set breakfast per morning. There is also a buffet for condiments, rice, curry, miso soup, bread, small pastries, fruits, and drinks. This was unlimited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The included breakfast is nice and does work in their ethos of providing guests with a grounding stay in the city for their visit. The food was cooked all right, but also was nothing special. It is on the level of what a home cook could make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Store&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The hotel is attached to a 2 story MUJI store, of course. The store takes up half of the property spanning across the 2nd and 3rd floors. If you didn’t bring a MUJI outfit, you can buy one here for your obligatory photo in front of the sign! There is a Found MUJI section, Idée section, books, PLANTS, and plenty of clothing. Found MUJI is a curated section of MUJI like products not created by company and Idée is their more colorful sister brand inspired by nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/06_Store_A.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/06_Store_B.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2-ns mb1&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/06_Store_C.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/06_Store_D_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/06_Store_D_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Depending on your trip’s itinerary, I would look up prices across different countries for MUJI. I made the mistake of not doing so and paid more than what I would have in Hong Kong for the same merchandise. All the merchandise found in this store are the same things stocked in MUJI Asia branches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Take inventory of what you cannot buy at home first! I picked up a pair of shoes, as many planters as I could carry, and pajamas. There are not any exclusive MUJI Hotel store items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The hotel is located in Futian District. Outside of the mall, the area is mostly residential and commercial buildings. You would need to take the metro or a cab to for Shenzhen activities. For example, the famous Huaqiangbei electronics street is 2.5 miles away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/07_Design_A_a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/07_Design_A_b.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;If you are reading this post, I suspect you may be interested in seeing the new Design Society building! It is 4.7 miles away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The MUJI hotel in Shenzhen is accessible. A driver should be able to drop off guests at the front door and there is an elevator which guests can use to access all floors. Show your driver the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.muji.com.cn/cn/store/feature/mujihotel/shenzhen/#access&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;address on the website&lt;/a&gt; to make sure they can find the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/muji/08_Sign_A.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photo Credit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jasonli&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Jason Li&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
MUJI fans will definitely enjoy their stay here, despite my nitpicks about the bathrooms and the breakfast. It’s the closest a fan can get to living in a store. The prefab homes and huts are quite the pretty penny, and only available in Japan after all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
MUJI curious can stay at the hotel to try out a good portion of their products before committing to the just enough no brand lifestyle. One night would be enough to get a sense!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I would not recommend staying here if you’re not at least curious about MUJI. For a few more dollars, you can find alternative accommodations in Shenzhen that have the usual hotel amenities MUJI has edited away. I was personally over the moon and didn’t want to check out of the hotel after my stay. However, you’ll have to consider that I have friends who use the scale of “from 0 to Mintlodica, how much are you a MUJI nerd?” and on this scale, I max out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I hope you enjoyed this guest post! Thanks Sabrina for having me on The InnBox. Thank you reader, and be well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;
If you found this review helpful, please let the MUJI Hotel know when you book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://hotel.muji.com/shenzhen/en/&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ MUJI Hotel&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;About Mintlodica&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Mintlodica is Susan’s creative studio. Check out her studio’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mintlodica&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/mintlodica/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;. If you are looking for art for your walls, check out her &lt;a href=&quot;https://susan.level.press/&quot;&gt;art prints shop&lt;/a&gt;! She also offers &lt;a href=&quot;http://mintlodica.storenvy.com/&quot;&gt;shiba inu pixel art apparel&lt;/a&gt; and has a &lt;a href=&quot;http://mintlodica.tictail.com/&quot;&gt;limited edition enamel pin&lt;/a&gt; up for grabs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/birdhouse/1.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Birdhouse El Nido in Palawan, Philippines&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/mbs/17.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Marina Bay Sands in Singapore&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Mintlodica</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: April 5 — 6, 2018 Rate: $150/Night Who Stayed: Mintlodica</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Your travel guide to Providence, Rhode Island: where to stay and what to do.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/providence-rhode-island-travel-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your travel guide to Providence, Rhode Island: where to stay and what to do." /><published>2018-04-15T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-04-15T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/providence-rhode-island-travel-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/providence-rhode-island-travel-guide/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/providence/splash.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Providence. The biggest city in America's smallest state. It's a known creative hub; home to one of the country's best art and design schools and a history in textile manufacturing. It's the perfect weekend getaway on the east coast, particularly in the summer season when the surrounding waters warm up and locals and visitors alike embrace the salty seas. Foodies will also appreciate the unending supply of American restaurants, from fine dining spots downtown to the burgeoning brunch scene in the city's more youthful neighborhoods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for June 2018. &lt;br /&gt;The InnBox may collect a share of sales from booking links on this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/the-dean.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Dean Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $149/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dean_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dean_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dean_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dean_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The Dean is often described as New England's answer to the Ace Hotel and it's not surprising to see why: The Dean is also home to a hip coffeeshop, bar, and restaurant, making it more than just a hotel but a place for people in Providence to hang out. The rooms are minimally decorated but with classic east coast twists like off-white walls, golden fixtures, and dark industrial furniture; all of which are an ode to the city's manufacturing background. The building's former life as a strip club and brothel also adds hidden meaning to the hotel's cheeky tagline &quot;Sleep with The Dean&quot;. The Dean offers affordable bunk rooms for groups of friends as well as rooms for solo-travelers. We stayed here in a double room for a long weekend in 2015 and loved it's central, downtown location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;The Dean Hotel offers facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/dye-house-lofts.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Dye House Lofts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $134/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dye_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dye_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dye_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dye_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Located in a renovated 1880's mill building, Dye House Lofts is home to an adorable couple and their ceramic studio, as well as two tastefully decorated lofts that are available for guests. The warehouse space gets amazing light, features beautiful art and ceramics, and some amazing tile work, like that red shower which is giving me 80's gym vibes, in the best possible way. The property is located in Olneyville, a quiet arts neighborhood that's less central but still only a seven minute drive away from downtown. Dye House Lofts has a three-night minimum stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;Guests under 21 years of age are not permitted. Please reach out directly to the hotel for more information on accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/1576859&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Providence Pied'De'Terre&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $100/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/pied_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/pied_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/pied_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/pied_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;I can't get over the dreamy, cobalt blue kitchen cupboards, slanted ceilings, and candy-colored exterior that make this Airbnb seem straight out of a storybook. The host, Chip, operate four separate Airbnbs out of this building but this top floor unit with its half-moon windows and pyramid alcoves is our favorite. The Airbnb is located in a safe, diverse, and thus far un-gentrified neighborhood near both Federal Hill and Downtown— where Chip has lived for over 25 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;This Airbnb is a top-floor unit accessible only by stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17525017&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Modern Armory Victorian&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $105/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/armory_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/armory_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/armory_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/armory_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This bright, modern Airbnb is operated by a jewelry designer who has lived in Providence for the past twelve years. We love how the space is accented with interesting, artful pieces like chunky, knitted throws on the bed or vintage tufted mustard colored chairs in the living room. The bathroom also features a steam-room shower. Even though the Airbnb is big enough for four, at its price point it's also a great deal for a couple or pair of friends. The unit is located in the city's Armory neighborhood, walking distance to several hip cafes and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;This Airbnb is located on the ground floor, however entrance to the building requires going up a small stoop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/19983622&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Home at Harkness&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $147/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/federal_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/federal_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/federal_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/federal_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This Airbnb is our pick for families and large groups. The Airbnb can comfortably accommodate 5 (but can squeeze in up to 7) which makes it a steal at its price point. This is also a great example of how furniture and decor can add so much personality into a space with relatively straight-forward architecture. White boxes and a standardized kitchen are brought to life with colorful textiles, clashing patterns, tiny trinkets and large sculptures. The home was originally built in 1855 but renovated last year in 2017 and is operated by a mother and daughter duo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt4 mb4&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Top 6 Things To Do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;pt4-ns cf&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin-right: auto; margin-left: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/risd.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://risdmuseum.org/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Get inspired at the&lt;br /&gt;RISD Museum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll admit, I'm not a huge museum person but I do love small-sized institutions that are approachable and not overwhelming. The art museum affiliated with the Rhode Island School of Design is just that. It's small but covers a wide breadth from classical to contemporary art, and the buildings that form the museum are just as gorgeous as the works housed within. It's a solid way to spend an afternoon and afterwards take a stroll around the nearby campus and take in all the colorful, adorable houses. Admission to the museum is free on Sundays.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb0 mb0 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/risdmuseum&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;@risdmuseum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 pt3 cf&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin-right: auto; margin-left: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/newport.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fr w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Get nautical in Newport&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About an hour's drive out of Providence is the port-town of Newport. The town can be best described as a J-crew catalog come to life but that doesn't mean it's without charm. Kick back with a beer and some stuffed quahogs on the pier or check out the International Yacht Restoration School (IYRS) where you can view a yacht currently in the process of restoration and peep all the interesting vintage artifacts they found onboard scattered throughout the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;anchor2&quot; class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 pt3 cf&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin-right: auto; margin-left: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/sweetberry.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fr w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Pick fruits at Sweet Berry Farm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all love farmer's markets but those of us who live in urban enclaves rarely get to pick out the goods ourselves. Sweet Berry Farm, located halfway between Providence and Newport, is known for their 'picking season' which runs from June to November. You get charged by the basket and are allowed to roam the fields and harvest your own fruits. Very IRL Stardew Valley! We went during strawberry and raspberry season and had so much fun trying to pick the 'best' fruits. But beware— hands and shirts will get stained so maybe keep your summer whites in the suitcase for this one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 pt3 cf&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin-right: auto; margin-left: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/hangingrock.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fr w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Take a hike at Hanging Rock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a short drive from Sweet Berry Farm is Norman Bird Sanctuary, which is also home to seven miles of hiking trails. Since you'll be driving a lot to get around in Providence, it's definitely worth a pit stop to stretch your legs. The sanctuary's most famous trail is Hanging Rock, which is a ridge trail that leads up to a seventy feet tall overlook, where you'll be rewarded with sweeping views of the Rhode Island coastline. Admission is $7.00. For folks who are really into the outdoors, you can even stay in an adorable &lt;a href=&quot;http://normanbirdsanctuary.org/farmhouse/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Farmhouse&lt;/a&gt; on the sanctuary grounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 pt3 cf&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin-right: auto; margin-left: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/dorrance.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fr w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/the-dorrance/4e78d70d22714e6e5f2fa733&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Drinks at The Dorrance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Dorrance is the exact opposite of the cozy, teeny tiny little cocktail bars I usually find more romantic. Yet with its tall ceilings, stained glassed windows, and dramatic curtains it still manages to make me feel a little wistful. This downtown cocktail bar and restaurant is located in an old Federal Reserve building and gets pretty lively on the weekend nights. Order a craft cocktail and head upstairs to the balcony level for people watching and privacy— or, if it's not already occupied, you can try nabbing the couch in the building's old vault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 pt3 cf&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin-right: auto; margin-left: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/providence/julians.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fr w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/julians/4a8844dff964a520a40520e3&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Eat Eggs at Julian's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While there are many new brunch restaurants that have cropped up in recent years in Providence's hip Federal Hill neighborhood, Julian's has been a neighborhood establishment for over twenty years. Their signature also happens to be my favorite brunch dish: Eggs Benedict. Take your pick of seven different varieties and one of their creative hash sides. If Benedicts aren't your thing the restaurant also offer you eggs wrapped, poached in shakshuka, scrambled into a pizza, or fried into an omelet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our travel guides:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/san-luis-obispo-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/slo/SLO_Header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/san-luis-obispo-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Why not SLO down in San Luis Obispo for your next weekend trip?&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/bariloche/bariloche_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Your travel guide to Bariloche, Argentina: where to stay and what to do.&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: Calma Ubud in Ubud, Bali</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/calma-ubud-bali-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: Calma Ubud in Ubud, Bali" /><published>2018-04-08T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-04-08T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/calma-ubud-bali-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/calma-ubud-bali-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; March 8 — 10, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $87/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Best Friend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/calma/splash.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
A ten minute motorbike ride outside of central Ubud is the residential village Kutuh Kaja, where at night the skies are dotted with more stars than many of us city dwellers are used to seeing, and by day large swaths of rice fields dominate the scenery. Here is where you'll find the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?cid=1801609&amp;amp;pcs=1&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=1258271&quot; targt=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Calma Ubud&lt;/a&gt;, the most accurate picture of a boutique hotel if there ever was one, and one of the best values in Ubud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Calma Ubud consists of ten individual rooms set in what feels like a very private complex of villas. Operating at such a small scale the hotel is able to provide a high quality experience for guests at a lower cost than many of the larger resorts dotting the Ubud area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Checking in at the Ubud was a fairly straight forward process, although finding the hotel for the first time is a little tricker— keep those eagle eyes out because it's very easy to drive by as the hotel blends so seamlessly into the surrounding area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Calma's lobby is open aired and elegantly decorated, a little taste of what's to come when you enter the compound. We signed up for a spa package during check-in and then were guided through a few wooden doors to our suite, where we were greeted with complimentary mojitos as a welcome drink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We had booked a &quot;Superior Room&quot; and honestly I was a little surprised at the size of the bedroom, which was smaller than I had expected. The Calma Ubud has ten rooms but six different room types, and it gets kind of confusing to keep track of the hierarchy here. I think I had mistaken the &quot;Superior Room&quot; for the &quot;Superior Double or Twin&quot; which appears a little more spacious in photos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Nonetheless, it wasn't a huge disappointment and because of the large bathroom and easy access to the hotel's common areas, we never felt cramped or like there wasn't enough room for the two of us. Since Ubud is also packed with sights to see and we had a relatively short time there (two days) we weren't spending that much time in our room anyway. Our room also included a little patio in front with two chairs, straw blind for privacy, and buddha statue out front.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The room itself was very minimal in decoration. I loved the carved white wooden headboard, jade colored side tables, and vibrant woven rug, but I'm not going to lie I wasn't super into the minimalist wooden wall art on display in the room. Since the room is already so sparse I would've loved to see some color on the walls in addition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt; Bathrooms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;As usual, the bathroom is always a highlight for me and the Calma Ubud is no exception. The open shower area has a skylight that fills the room with the most wonderful warm ambiance in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fn center mb3 mb4-ns tc&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/7.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
There was plenty of counter space around the sink for all of our things and the landscape mirror was perfect for two girls to get ready at the same time. The bathroom also has a drying rack in addition to a ladder-style towel rack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/9.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/8.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The center-piece of the Calma is the infinity pool overlooking rice fields in the back. Due to the hotel's small size the pool was never over-crowded during our stay. It's the perfect place to spend the afternoon and chill out with a happy hour drink after seeing sights all day. On the other side of the pool is also a quieter wooden deck area with a few lounge chairs overlooking the fields if you're looking for some privacy.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/18.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The pool is connected to the hotel's restaurant, which is tastefully decorated with a variety of seating options: bar, coffee tables with sofas, hammocks, a large communal table, and more traditional cafe-style tables for two.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;I feel like I had very mixed experiences with the service at Calma Ubud. There were certain staff members who went above and beyond during our stay, like the front desk attendant who went around asking the other staff members for small bills so that I could break a large bill to pay my motorcycle driver. Or the friendly young man who would drive the hotel's van to drop us off in central Ubud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;On the flip side, breakfast our first day was somewhat stressful. Knowing that our tour guide was coming to pick us up at a certain time, I wanted to make sure I was able to get breakfast, which is included free with your stay. I think the restaurant must've been understaffed that day because it took over twenty minutes before someone was able to take my order. We ended up having to ask them to package breakfast to go in order to leave the hotel on time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;In addition when we booked our spa services it wasn't clear to us that we had essentially booked a 'couples' treatment when what we wanted were two individual treatments. This meant we shared a lot of the same time and resources but without any discount on the price of the services. Despite this, I would still recommend getting a massage or bath at the spa if that's something that interests you— ultimately the price is so much more affordable than getting similar treatments in the U.S. that it's hard to complain too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Despite my complaints about the slow service in the kitchen, I have to say the food itself was amazing. The strawberry crepes we had for breakfast the first day were some of the best I've ever had. I think it's super impressive albeit ambitious that their free breakfast is made to order from a decently varied menu, considering most hotels with free breakfast will either set out a buffet or limit their menu to two or three options at most. The free breakfast also includes your choice of juice or a smoothie in addition to tea and/or coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/15.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you're looking for a quiet and tranquil area to stay in Ubud you can't get much better than the Calma. However, the hotel isn't walking distance to any restaurants or sights. You'll need to take the hotel shuttle to downtown Ubud which is free if you go according to their shuttle schedule or around $6 each way (for the whole party) outside. Our schedule pretty much never worked out with the shuttle so we ended up paying for the shuttle a few times, with the return trip always being a little cheaper because you can just find a driver in Ubud to take you back for less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I'm still kind of torn on whether or not I would've liked to stay in Central Ubud. On the one hand, it's nice to be close to all the restaurants, shops, and nightlife. On the other hand, it's also nice to be in a more relaxing environment with the space to stretch out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While there are ground-floor rooms available at the Calma, there are steps all over the hotel grounds that it's hard for me to recommend this place for wheelchair users. With the exception of the upper-floor suites these tend to be short flights, but they are there separating the rooms from the pathway to the restaurant, from the restaurant to the pool, from the pool to the spa area and the lounge/deck area on the other side of the pool. There are also shallow steps around the various thresholds and doorways leading to the suites from the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/calma/17.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you really want to go &quot;all out&quot; during your stay to Ubud there are definitely bigger, more reputable resorts that are worth checking out. However, if you are keen to stick to a budget but still want to stay somewhere inspiring and relaxing then I think the Calma Ubud is one of the best options in the area. It's price point is simply lower than average for the quality they deliver and as long as you keep that in mind and overlook a few flaws, you'll be happy with your stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;If you found this review helpful, please use our link below to book at Calma Ubud (or any other hotel!). The InnBox may collect a small share of sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?cid=1801609&amp;amp;pcs=1&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=1258271&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ Calma Ubud&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/birdhouse/1.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Birdhouse El Nido in Palawan, Philippines&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-slow-canggu-bali-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/slow/01.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-slow-canggu-bali-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Slow in Canggu, Bali&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: March 8 — 10, 2018 Rate: $87/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Best Friend</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Here’s what $200 on Airbnb can get you in New York City</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/200-dollars-airbnb-new-york-city/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Here's what $200 on Airbnb can get you in New York City" /><published>2018-04-01T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-04-01T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/200-dollars-airbnb-new-york-city</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/200-dollars-airbnb-new-york-city/">&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;../images/nycair/Splash.png&quot; /&gt;
I'm currently in the midst of planning a trip back to New York City so we can visit friends and renew our long-term Thai visas. After staying in so many stunning yet affordable places across Southeast Asia, needless to say the reality of the New York lodging market had me &lt;i&gt;shook&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While I ultimately ended up booking four nights at the airy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/the-boro-hotel-lic.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Boro Hotel&lt;/a&gt; in Long Island City, I probably had about forty Airbnb tabs and Booking.com tabs open simultaneously. If I hadn't stumbled on a discounted rate for Boro, we probably would've ended up staying in an Airbnb because it would've been more affordable for a four-night stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While browsing Airbnb I found myself fascinated by the variety of homes available in New York. Location is responsible for a big variety in both design and price of available units. Inspired by BuzzFeed posts like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.buzzfeed.com/juliegerstein/heres-what-1000-a-month-in-rent-will-get-you-in-all-50?utm_term=.wagZgQKPR#.yizKOJ1w4&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;these&lt;/a&gt; which focus on the difference in rent prices across different states, I thought it'd be fun to compare how far $200 a night can get you in New York— that's approximately the average rate for an entire home according to &lt;a href=&quot;http://insideairbnb.com/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Inside Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;The Rules&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;1.)&lt;/b&gt; I will only be comparing &quot;entire units&quot;, not private rooms or shared rooms.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;2.)&lt;/b&gt; I'll be comparing Airbnbs in all five boroughs (Manhattan, Brooklyn, Queens, Bronx, and Staten Island) as well as New Jersey.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;3.)&lt;/b&gt; I won't be factoring in cleaning fees since that will vary the nightly rate based length of stay.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;4.)&lt;/b&gt; I'll be looking for the &lt;i&gt;best&lt;/i&gt; places I can find under $200, rather than showing you the most &lt;i&gt;typical&lt;/i&gt; place. We're talking best case scenario here!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;5.)&lt;/b&gt; In order to determine the 'best' I'm factoring in: design, size, location, and amenities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Airbnbs in NYC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/5838858&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;SoHo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $202/Night — 1 Bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Soho_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Soho_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
'Lush' is the first word that comes to mind to describe this romantic Airbnb located at the crux of SoHo &amp;amp; Chinatown. This airbnb has two beds (one is curtained off from the living area) and can accommodate up to 4 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Big for a downtown apartment, centrally located near trendy shops and restaurants, elevator, laundry, king-sized Casper bed, great taste in wallpaper.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; The second 'bedroom' has less privacy.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There is a step-free path that leads to the Airbnb's elevator. The elevator door is at least 32 inches wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/4204496&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Harlem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $125/Night — Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Harlem_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Harlem_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This airy Airbnb, which can accomodate up to 2 guests, is located on the third floor of an 1800's brownstone and manages to make a small space feel open and bright. The host is also the owner of an Indian restaurant located downstairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Renovated bathroom and kitchenette, solar shades, historical design accents, Casper mattress, located just a block from the nearest subway stop.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; No elevator or sofa (there is a cute French chaise but it doesn't look like the type you can sink into).
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Access to this studio requires going up two flights of stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17747778&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Financial District&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $210/Night — Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Fidi_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Fidi_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This unit is located in a luxury building downtown and utilizes modular furniture to make use of the small space. It can accommodate up to 4 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Full-service apartment building, quiet, views of the water, laundry, elevators, lots of storage space for guests, close to multiple subway stops and tourist sights.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Virtually no privacy if occupied by more than two people. Floors look a bit dated.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This Airbnb has step-free access and a wide entrance doorway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/1487222&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Crown Heights, Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $120/Night — 2 Bedrooms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Prospect_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Prospect_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This bright white apartment is an absolute steal for the price and how many people it can comfortably accommodate. It's also located on the border between Prospect and Crown Heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Privacy, big kitchen, balcony, backyard garden, tin tile ceilings, heating and air conditioning for each room, and plant dad vibes.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Roughly a ten minute walk to the nearest subway stop according to reviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Access to this Airbnb currently requires stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/15988664&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;East Village&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $140/Night — Alcove Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/EV_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/EV_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This apartment has all the classic East Village vibes — including an alcove studio that's &lt;i&gt;almost&lt;/i&gt; like a bedroom, but not quite. The unit can accomodate up to 2 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Located near many popular restaurants and parks, dope living room wallpaper.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Small, and a bit of a walk to the nearest subway stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Please enquire directly with the host regarding accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/73586&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Long Island City, Queens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $150/Night — 1 Bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/LIC_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/LIC_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb is located in a modern building chock full of amnenities and is conveniently located close to both the major airports and Manhattan. It can accommodate up to 4 guests, but there will be fees for over 2 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Amazing views, elevators, hot tub, gym, minimal design, located two blocks from the nearest subway stop.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Minimum stay varies, farther away from tourist sights and popular restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb is located in an elevator-serviced building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17617875&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Staten Island&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $125/Night — 3 Bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/SI_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/SI_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I honestly had to do a double-take when I realized this Airbnb was located in Staten Island. It's one of the better designed spots on this list— artful without feeling forced. It can comfortably accommodate up to 5 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Spacious, sky lights, walking distance to the ferry into Manhattan, and there's an Eames chair.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; No air conditioning in the unit, not in the direct vicinity of many retaurants, master bedroom is separated from the main space by a curtain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb has a flat path to the front door, wide hallway clearance, step-free access to bedroom and bathroom and an accessible-height bed. Werk!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/20247895&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Midtown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night — Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Midtown_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Midtown_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This clean and simple Midtown unit looks and feels like a tastefully decorated hotel room. It can accomodate up to 6 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Clean and minimal design, modern bathroom, A+ curtain game.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; 4th floor walk-up, tight fit if fully occupied, and a bit of a walk to the nearest subway station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Access to this Airbnb requires going up four flights of stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/4109420&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Astoria, Queens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $111/Night — 2 Bedrooms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Astoria_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Astoria_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This spacious Astoria Airbnb is perfect for those who want a home-away-from-home vibe and it can accommodate up to 3 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Separate dining room, big kitchen, proximity to LGA, quiet, close to tons of good restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; About 10 minutes walk to the nearest subway stop and 20 minutes into Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb is located on the second floor of a three-floor building. We recommend enquiring directly with the host for more accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/6660046&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Williamsburg, Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $150/Night — Alcove Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Williamsburg_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Williamsburg_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This unique Airbnb in Williamsburg feels both opulent and refined at the same time. It's got a nautical vibe and labeling it a 1 bedroom, while technically true, is a bit of a stretch. The unit can accommodate up to 2 guests. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Submarine vibes, dope bathroom, great for having friends over, close to tons of trendy restaurants and shops.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Ground floor unit (good for accessibility, less great for noise). While the design is awesome it makes you feel more like you're in Europe than Brooklyn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb is located on the ground floor. We recommend enquiring directly with the host for more accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/449680&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Woodstock, Bronx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $105/Night — 2 Bedrooms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Bronx_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/Bronx_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb is located in a historical neighborhood in the Bronx and has tons of color and charm! It's ideal for a nuclear familiar and can comfortably accomodate 4 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; High ceilings, consistent design, air conditioning, crystal chandeliers, and located just a few blocks away from two different subway lines.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Located farther away from tourist sights and trendy restaurants. It's about a 30 minute subway ride to downtown Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb is located on the ground floor. We recommend enquiring directly with the host for more accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/15372508&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Upper East Side&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night — 1 Bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/UES_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/UES_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
There's something charming and romantic about this simple and understated Upper East Side apartment, which tactfully uses mirrors to make the small space feel bigger. The 5th floor walk-up can accomodate up to 2 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Vintage vibes, Juliet balcony, great views, located two blocks away from the nearest subway stop, quiet, and desk space.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; 5th floor walk-up, small, dark and tiny looking kitchenette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Access to this Airbnb requires ascending five flights of stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17746626&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Jersey City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $149/Night — 4 Bedrooms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/JC_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/JC_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Live like a king— or a whole royal family— in this resplendent Italian-influenced New Jersey apartment which can accommodate up to 6 guests. The apartment is about a 5 minute walk away from the PATH train into Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Full-service apartment building, elevators, great views of Manhattan, huge kitchen, sauna, modern bathrooms, free pizza and wine dinner for first-time guests staying at least three nights.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; 30 minutes commute into Manhattan, having to deal with New Yorkers making fun of you for staying in Jersey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
There is a step-free path leading to the Airbnb's elevator. The elevator door is at least 32 inches wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/11775347&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hell's Kitchen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $199/Night — Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/HK_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/HK_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This pop art inspired abode is perfect for Broadway fans or first time visitors. It's close enough to Times Square for convenient access but far enough away to give you some space from the crowds. The studio can accommodate up to 2 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Clean, well designed studio (they even painted their radiator red, I mean...), backyard garden, proximity to dope Thai food, luggage drop-off allowed, close to several tourists sights.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Close to several tourist sights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb is located on the second floor of a three story building. We recommend enquiring directly with the host for more accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/821135&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Downtown Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $125/Night — 1 Bedroom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/DB_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/DB_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This warehouse loft gets gorgeous light and is tastefully decorated with mid-century details. It can accomodate up to 5 people but it'd be most comfortable for 2 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; 1000 sq feet, close to several subway lines, just a few stops away from Manhattan, high ceilings, shared roof deck, dope fireplace.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Noisy location, part-time elevator service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb has an elevator but it only runs from 11am—11pm during the week and 12pm-10pm on the weekends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/236949&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Greenwich Village&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $150/Night — Alcove Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/WV_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/WV_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This charming Airbnb is located on the cusp of Greenwich and West Village, with a quintessentially quirky layout. The alcove area for the bed is also quite spacious— the only thing stopping it from being a true bedroom is a door. The unit can accomodate up to 2 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Skylights, high ceilings, tasteful decor, bright bathroom, just a few blocks from the nearest subway stop, proximity to trendy restaurants and shopping.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; 4th floor walk-up, questionable forest wallpaper in the bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Access to this Airbnb requires climbing four flights of stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/4340161&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Lower East Side&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $119/Night — Studio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/LES_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/nycair/LES_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This sun-drenched Airbnb gave me déjà vu because it has the same layout as an Airbnb I stayed at in Buenos Aires. The spacious downtown apartment can accommodate up to 2 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Pro's:&lt;/b&gt; Juliette balcony, great natural lighting, A+ color coordination, proximity to trendy restaurants and shops, elevator, and easy access to public transit.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Con's:&lt;/b&gt; Some reviewers mention the bed being too soft, or A/C not functioning as well as it should.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Airbnb has elevator access, but we'd recommend directly contacting the host for more accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Want to see how New York Airbnbs compare with other cities?&lt;br /&gt;Check out our other Airbnb lists:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb3 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-san-francisco/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/sf/sf_bnb_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-san-francisco/&quot;&gt;The 13 Best Airbnbs in San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/asheville/asheville_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/&quot;&gt;The 13 Best Airbnbs in Asheville, North Carolina&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">I'm currently in the midst of planning a trip back to New York City so we can visit friends and renew our long-term Thai visas. After staying in so many stunning yet affordable places across Southeast Asia, needless to say the reality of the New York lodging market had me shook.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: The Slow in Canggu, Bali</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/the-slow-canggu-bali-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: The Slow in Canggu, Bali" /><published>2018-03-25T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-03-25T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-slow-canggu-bali-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/the-slow-canggu-bali-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; March 10 — 12, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $182.67/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Best Friend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/slow/01.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Just five minutes from the beach in the little surfer town of Canggu is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?cid=1801609&amp;amp;pcs=1&amp;amp;hid=1515695&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Slow&lt;/a&gt; —  an art gallery as much as it is a boutique hotel and the brainchild of Australian fashion designer George Gorrow (of Ksubi) and his wife Cisco Tschurtschenthaler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The hotel, described by its owners as an exercise in &quot;tropical brutalism&quot;, was designed in collaboration with local architect Rieky Sunur of &lt;a href=&quot;http://gfabarchitects.com/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;GFAB architects.&lt;/a&gt; Every detail at The Slow has been designed with intentionality, to coax bustling tourists into relaxation, and encourage guests to take full advantage of the beautiful space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The check-in process at The Slow was surprisingly informal and began as soon as our car pulled up into their driveway. One thing I love about staying at smaller hotels is that with only a few people checking in each day, they seem to know exactly who you are when you arrive. Rather than awkwardly waiting at a desk for them to pull up our information, the staff were ready and immediately took us and our bags to our room, which they proceeded to give us a quick tour of, noting little details like how to control the volume on the in-room speakers and all the storage space in the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/02.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The room itself was one of the most comfortable and spacious that I've ever stayed in. The polished concrete floors and vertically slatted windows made the room feel surprisingly cool despite the hot Bali weather outside. The room's aesthetic seemed to have a decidedly Californian influence— minimalist, modern, and airy but paired with more traditional wooden furniture and textiles. When we first entered the room the stereo was even set to Cali-based &lt;a href=&quot;http://reverberationradio.com/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Reverberation Radio&lt;/a&gt;, which we kept on for most of our stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/03.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/01.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/04.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I loved the low platform bed and found myself curing up with the cozy woven blanket on top of the bed several times during the course of our stay. Another small, appreciated detail was the outlet set-up: an equal amount of outlets on each side of the bed with USB outlets included (perfect for those who forgot to pack an adapter). One other thing I have to compliment The Slow on is their in-room art curation. Normally I find myself unmoved by hotel art. It's usually very predictable, more often than not some kind of floral still life. Even at the nicest hotels! It was refreshing to see something different on the walls at The Slow, which tends to feature more modern art and photography from the Gorrows' personal collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/05.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Slow only has two types of rooms: pool suites and non-pool suits (called grand suites). I initially wanted to book a pool suite but they were unsurprisingly all sold out for my travel dates. Even without a pool the grand suite still felt luxurious— and it's hard to complain when you're just a five minute walk down the street to the nearest beach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/06.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/07.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt; Bathrooms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Bathrooms at The Slow have a narrow layout but still managed to feel spacious like the rooms themselves. I loved the open shower, separated from the rest of the bathroom by a single pane of glass and from prying eyes outside by a full-length frosted window. The shower also comes with a handy bench, the perfect prop for shaving legs or hosting your toiletries, and plenty of hooks for hanging towels or clothes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fn center mb3 mb4-ns tc&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/08.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The bathroom also kind of serves as a walk-in closet with ample storage space, including tons of drawers or a platform perfect for throwing your suitcase on top of (if you're lazy like me and don't want to fully unpack). There's also a large full-length mirror at the opposite end of the bathroom from the shower which was *very* appreciated, because if there's one thing I always lament when it's missing in a hotel room, it's a full-length mirror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;While the rooms at The Slow are so spacious that it's tempting to hole up in there during your downtime, the hotel also has some beautifully designed common areas that are worth checking out. The upper level, where our room was located, has an outdoor deck. My only complaint was that it was way too hot during the day to really hang out there (and despite it being a fully booked hotel, no one was). Adding in some kind of shade or deck cover would definitely make this area more inviting for guests!
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Downstairs at the bar and restaurant, things are a little more active. We spent a lot of our downtime just chilling at the bar with a glass of rosé, chatting idly with the staff and occasionally with other guests when seated on the two sofas in the lobby. The ground floor of the hotel also acts as an art gallery with a rotating collection of artwork on display there. While we were there they were displaying work by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.brooklynwhelan.com/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Brooklyn Whelan&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.josemiguelmendez.com/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Jose Mendez.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The service was one of the highlights of staying at the Slow for me. The staff were all so personable, it's kind of amazing how well they get to know you even over the course of a two night stay. The bartender was constantly giving us recommendations on where to go and when the staff would ask about our day plans they always had some good advice or interesting facts to impart about the places we were going. They were also helpful with getting us a car to take us to Tanah Lot, going as far as to call around to make sure that we got a good rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Breakfast at The Slow may have been my favorite of the whole trip to Bali. While it wasn't included in our stay, it felt reasonably affordable for the quality. If I'm being honest, a lot of my meals at trendier restaurants in Bali tended to look a lot better than they tasted, but the food at The Slow's restaurant actually tasted incredible. I ordered this jackfruit-bread with roasted bananas for breakfast and while I've had jackfruit many times before, I've never had anything quite like this. The bread was perfectly moist, with just the right amount of sweetness and jackfruit chunks baked in. They've also got a nice selection of juices and cocktails which are bottled on site. In retrospect I kind of wish we ate more of our meals at the restaurant!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/17.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Slow is located in a neighborhood on Bali's southwest coast called Canggu (pronounced &lt;i&gt;Chang&lt;/i&gt;-gu), which has a reputation for being a laid-back surfer town. It was probably my favorite area that we visited in Bali— a nice reprieve from the more tourist-crowded Ubud and Kuta. That's not to say there aren't tourists in Canggu, but it seems that most people staying in Canggu are there to simply experience hanging out in the area rather than to visit any specific attraction. There were more intriguing restaurants than we had time to visit and a surprising amount of cute clothing boutiques popping up on the main drag. The Slow itself was also located just a few minutes away from &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/the-lawn/56640fb1498e318179a472e4&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Lawn&lt;/a&gt;, a dreamy outdoor bar on the beach and also next door to a gorgeous yoga studio, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thepracticebali.com/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Practice&lt;/a&gt;. The only thing which gives me a little pause about Canggu is how the town will continue to balance its growing western influence. Depending on where you go in Canggu, one might wonder if they're actually in Australia rather than Indonesia. Granted, this is an issue affecting many places in Bali, not just Canggu, but the western influence is more vivid here than even in Ubud. While it's not so bad now, I wonder how this balance will change as Canggu's popularity continues to grow.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While The Slow doesn't outright claim to be accessible, there are ground floor units available (the more expensive pool suites). The upper units are unfortunately only accessible by stairs. If planning to stay in Canggu, wheelchair users should be aware that the sidewalks in the area around The Slow can often be blocked with construction debris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/slow/15.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I would totally recommend The Slow to any art and design lovers planning a trip to Bali. The small size of the hotel will grant you plenty of attention from the staff, and the overall quality of the hotel is a great deal at its price point compared to most American hotels. This is not a drop-your-stuff-off and come back to sleep type of hotel, this is a place you'll actually want to spend your time at, to literally &quot;slow down&quot;, if you will. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;If you found this review helpful, please use our link below to book at The Slow Canggu (or any other hotel!). The InnBox may collect a small share of sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?cid=1801609&amp;amp;pcs=1&amp;amp;hid=1515695&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ The Slow&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/birdhouse/1.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Birdhouse El Nido in Palawan, Philippines&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/mbs/17.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/marina-bay-sands-singapore-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Marina Bay Sands in Singapore&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: March 10 — 12, 2018 Rate: $182.67/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Best Friend</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Your travel guide to Hội An, Vietnam: where to stay and what to do.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hoi-an-travel-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your travel guide to Hội An, Vietnam: where to stay and what to do." /><published>2018-03-18T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-03-18T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hoi-an-travel-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hoi-an-travel-guide/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/hoian/splash.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Hội An is a charming little seaside town and preserved historic district located about an hour south of the port city of Da Nang. Its streets are lined with bright orange buildings and traffic flows across green colored canals that divide up the town. It's a popular destination for couples due to its relaxed and romantic atmosphere but it's also a great option for families with kid-friendly activities like cooking classes and sunny beaches. It's a foodie heaven thanks to daily night markets and regional twists on popular Vietnamese dishes. Hội An is the perfect place to pause for a few days and watch the world go by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for May 2018. &lt;br /&gt;The InnBox may collect a share of sales from booking links on this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For time travelers — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?cid=1801609&amp;amp;pcs=1&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=70194&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Nhi Nhi Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $27/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/nhinhi_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/nhinhi_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/nhinhi_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/nhinhi_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Nhi Nhi hotel is proof that more traditional aesthetics can still be a breath of fresh air. It's a counterpoint to the many sparsely decorated hotel rooms Hội An. The Nhi Nhi's gorgeous sun-lit interior courtyard will transport you back in time— and don't many of us travel to be transported? All the little details in the rooms, from the pattern of the bathroom tile to the wood-carved furniture, may fill you with a wistful sense of nostalgia, if you're of East or Southeast Asian descent like me. The staff was exceptionally friendly and kind, and their breakfast buffet was one of the best we had in Hội An. The hotel is located on the west side of town, in a quiet area but about a five minute walk away from Old Town. Nhi Nhi is a little more affordable than most hotels in Hội An, and perfect for anyone trying to balance a budget— but I do think it's worth it to splurge a little to make sure your room has an interior facing balcony!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;The Nhi Nhi hotel has ground floor rooms available with accessible bathrooms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For green thumbs — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?cid=1801609&amp;amp;pcs=1&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=1179186&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Atlas Hội An Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $48/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/atlas_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/atlas_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/atlas_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/atlas_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Atlas is a 48-room hotel most known for its stunning exteriors which utilize over 100 cantilevered concrete planters to give the illusion of being surrounded by a lush jungle, whether you're inside your room or chilling in one of the hotel's many courtyards. The hotel was actually shortlisted for the World Architecture Festival awards in 2017 and was designed by the Vietnamese architect Vo Trong Nghia and his firm, who are known for their deft use of greenery in urban spaces (see the stunning &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dezeen.com/2017/04/13/vo-trong-nghia-binh-house-planted-terraces-interspersed-living-spaces-architecture-residential-vietnam/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Binh House&lt;/a&gt; in Saigon). The hotel is also just a few blocks away from the famous Japanese Bridge that marks the entrance into Old Town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;Atlas Hội An has an elevator for accessing upper floors and allergy-free rooms available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples and quiet time — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/vn/azumi.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Azumi Villa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $50/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/azumi_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/azumi_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/azumi_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/azumi_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The Azumi is a minimalist, 14 room boutique hotel on the eastern side of Hội An. Their furnishings are higher quality than many similarly priced hotels in the area, and I can say as a soft-bed lover that their bed was the most comfortable hotel bed I've slept in during the past year— I melted right in. Their beds are also curiously positioned in the center of the room, surrounded by lounging chairs in the front and a desk in the back. Their bathrooms also feature steam room showers (your girl's fave). Azumi is located about a ten minute's walk away from all the action in Old Town, which is ideal for guests who prefer a quieter atmosphere. If you're worried about the distance though, Azumi has some cute bikes that are free for guest use and will get you to Old Town in a snap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;Upper floors are accessible by stairs only, however Azumi has ground floor villas in which the entire unit is wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Foodies— &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?cid=1801609&amp;amp;pcs=1&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=979272&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Maison Vy Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $79/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/maison_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/maison_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/maison_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/maison_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The eponymous Trinh Diem Vy is a culinary institution in Hội An.  She's an accomplished cookbook author and the proprietor of several of Hội An's most famous restaurants: Morning Glory, Mermaid, Vy's Market Restaurant, and Vy's Kitchen &amp;amp; Deli. Maison Vy marks her first foray as a hotelier. The hotel is tastefully decorated in a swath of off-white and turquoise and floor-to-ceiling windows. It's located a little farther out from Hội An's old town (about a ten minute walk, similar to Azumi) so again a great choice for any light sleepers. Breakfast is included with most rates, and given her extensive culinary success, you know it's going to be amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot; class=&quot;f6 i pb4 light-silver&quot;&gt;Upper floors are accessible by stairs only, however Maison Vy does have ground floor facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt4 mb4&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;What to do in Hội An&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Take a stroll through Old Town&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/oldtown.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Hội An Old Town is a UNESCO World Heritage Site and the main attraction which draws visitors to the sleepy seaside town. Within it's streets you'll find signature yellow buildings and clay roof titles under which lie hidden coffeeshops, clothing stores, and restaurants. There are a few historic sites and temples in Old Town that you'll need to buy tickets to see up close, although we ended up just walking around and instead visiting some of the temples located just outside of Old Town for free. The best time to visit Old Town is at night when all of the lanterns are lit up (although black outs do happen occasionally). I highly recommend taking a boat ride down the canal at night for a little bit of romance— you'll be surrounded by paper lanterns and even get to deposit one of your own into the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Eat Bánh Mì @ &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/madam-kh%C3%A1nh--the-b%C3%A1nh-m%C3%AC-queen/51b67b8b498e9270692a1655&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Madam Khánh's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/bahnmi.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;My favorite bánh mì I've had out of all my trips in Vietnam was at a little shop here called &quot;Madam Knanh - The Bánh Mì Queen&quot;. Some say it's the best banh mi in all of Vietnam— I don't think I'm enough of an expert to support or deny that claim but it sealed the deal for me. You can order from a very limited menu of bánh mì (always a good sign) and a much more vast menu of drinks. One bánh mì will set you back 20,000 dong which is less than $1.  The eponymous Madam Knanh (which is technically not her real name, it's her husband's last name which she never formally took) didn't seem to be making sandwiches anymore, at least when I visited, but she was patrolling the restaurant with a huge wad of cash in her hands, monitoring her employee's performance and collecting them bills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor2&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Visit Mỹ Sơn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/myson.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Mỹ Sơn is technically not in Hội An but rather about an hour's drive into the countryside. Still, it's one of the top things to do in the area and worth the day trip. Mỹ Sơn is a holy site composed of the ruins of Hindu temples, with a storied history. It was only 'discovered' in our recent history by French colonialists in the 1800s, who then took parts of the ruins back with them to France, where they now sit in the Louvre, which refuses to return the artifacts to Vietnam. Then during the war in Vietnam, U.S. forces bombed the area, inadvertently destroying the majority of the temples. Visiting the site is not only a visual experience, but a contemplative one. The entrance fee to Mỹ Sơn is roughly $6 per person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Take a Cooking Class&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/cookingclass_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/cookingclass_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;You'll see signs advertising cooking classes all over Hội An. We chose to do ours through &lt;a href=&quot;https://tastevietnam.asia/cooking-classes&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Vy's Market Restaurant&lt;/a&gt; (the same Miss Vy of Maison Vy mentioned above). It was a little pricier due to Miss Vy's reputation but very informative. The class included a tour of the local market in Hội An, and a tasting of some examples of local street food, which included some delicacies I personally hadn't tried before, like duck egg embryo and silk worm salad (okay I chickened out of trying the latter). We signed up for the &quot;Holiday Masterclass&quot; which is the school's most popular option but in retrospect perhaps not challenging enough for a couple who cooks frequently at home. There were many young kids in our class which leads me to believe that the &quot;Holiday Masterclass&quot; is a great option for families. My favorite part of the class was learning how to make bánh xèo, a savory pancake made out of rice flour and turmeric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Get Custom Tailored Clothes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/tailor_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/tailor_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Hitting up the tailor shops is a *thing* in Hội An, where silk shops line the streets, and it's a great idea if you struggle to find clothes that fit you off the rack. Being a petite lady it's pretty much impossible for me to find a jumpsuit that fits so I decided to try to get one made here. Many of the tailor shops are located within a few block's radius of one another and I started my inquiries at one of the highest rated shops in town, A Dong Silk. Their prices were steeper than I had expected at $120 (they did offer to discount if I ordered additional garments). I knew that the other popular shop in town, Kimmy Tailor, would be just as expensive so I skipped that one and wandered over to a Be Be shop (most of the brands have multiple locations within the same block) who was willing to price the jumpsuit at $90, but I wasn't able to find a fabric I liked there. My third time was a charm as I then went to the highly rated but less popular &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g298082-d2717876-Reviews-Peace_Tailor_in_Hoi_An-Hoi_An_Quang_Nam_Province.html&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Peace Tailor&lt;/a&gt; who offered to do the jumpsuit for $50. Over the course of one and a half days I came in for two fittings as they altered the garment to my perfection. Looking back at the respective shop's TripAdvisor photos, it didn't surprise me that Peace Tailor has more photos of younger customers with progressive styles and pieces than Kimmy &amp;amp; A Dong. So if you're looking for something a little edgier I'd definitely trust them to do justice to your vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Try out the street food @ Hội An's night market&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/nm_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/nm_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/nm_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The night market in Hội An is open every night starting at 6pm and a great place to try the local street food. Our favorite was a Vietnamese-style crepe pizza that cost less than $1 (we'd order one and then find ourselves craving another not too long after). My other favorite snack we got was a coconut crepe/cake drizzled with chocolate. There were also sit down restaurants on the side of the street where we had other Hội An and Vietnamese staples like Cao Lầu and Com Ga. I didn't do too much actual shopping at the night market but wandering around at a night surrounded by all the colorful lanterns was magical. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Hit up the Beach&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hoian/beach.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Okay so I didn't actually go to the beach during my time in Hội An but that's because we already had beach trips to the Philippines and southern Thailand planned. If you're not planning on going to a more well known beach destination, then definitely take advantage of being in Hội An and treat yourself to a beach day! If you're including Hội An in a larger trip with beach destinations than it may be worth putting the time there towards one of the other activities listed here or just having a chill day in Old Town or nearby Da Nang and Hue. An Bang is the most popular beach in Hội An— it used to be Cửa Đại but the latter was damaged by erosion (although parts of it have since recovered and are accessible to visitors). If you're feeling a little more adventurous hitch a couple of hours' boat ride to the nearby Cham Island for a more picturesque beach trip.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>