<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-07T22:28:53+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">The InnBox</title><subtitle>The InnBox is a weekly newsletter featuring unique, affordable places and spaces for busy folks who need a break.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: Le Pirate Boatel in Labuan Bajo, Indonesia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/le-pirate-boatel-labuan-bajo-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: Le Pirate Boatel in Labuan Bajo, Indonesia" /><published>2018-10-07T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/le-pirate-boatel-labuan-bajo-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/le-pirate-boatel-labuan-bajo-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt;September 15 — 18, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $43/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;dib&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Sabrina&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/boatel/00.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Labuan Bajo is the launching pad for exploring the many islands off the coast of the larger Indonesian island Flores. The most internationally well known of these smaller islands is Komodo Island, home to the largest living lizard species. These small islands break up harsh waves from the ocean outside, resulting in peaceful, shallow seas in between them. So it should come as no surprise that one of the most popular ways to stay in the region is on liveboards, a.k.a. boats that also function as a residence. One such concept is &lt;a href=&quot;https://lepirate.com/boatel/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Le Pirate Boatel&lt;/a&gt;, anchored in a peaceful bay about fifteen minutes away from Labuan Bajo’s main harbor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This actually wasn’t the first time I’ve stayed on a “boatel”. A few years ago I stayed at &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/dk/cphliving.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;CPH Living&lt;/a&gt;”, anchored in one of Copenhagen’s canals. While that particular spot in Copenhagen was more of a hotel pretending to be a boat, Le Pirate is more like a boat pretending to be a hotel, if that makes sense. It’s a more rustic experience that also serves as a cozy home base for exploring the neighboring islands. Let’s begin…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Le Pirate’s boatel is anchored in a bay off the shore of Labuan Bajo. This means the boatel doesn’t come to you, you need to get to it. But how? Well, there’s a smaller shuttle boat that runs back and forth between Labuan Bajo harbor and the boatel every two hours.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/02.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Labuan Bajo Harbor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Upon landing at Komodo International Airport, a five minute cab ride will get you to the harbor in Labuan Bajo. Le Pirate actually has an on-land hotel around here and I highly recommend you get dropped off at the hotel instead of at the harbor. For the record, we did not do this and it resulted in us just hanging around in confusion at the harbor for awhile, in the heat, while I was feeling sick because of the strenuous hike we did the day before in Nusa Penida. If you get dropped off at Le Pirate Labuan Bajo, you can chill there for awhile and when the shuttle actually arrives someone from the hotel will escort you directly to the proper shuttle boat. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Fifteen minutes later you’ll be pulling up to this view… &lt;p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/03.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Le Pirate’s rooms are generally small and minimal, and it’s not just because they're on a boat. We also stayed at Le Pirate’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hid=487581&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;beach club in Nusa Ceningan&lt;/a&gt; (review forthcoming) and I actually preferred our room on the boat, which felt brighter and more spacious. The crowning glory of the room is that instead of a wall, or even a window, one side of the room is completely open and facing the sea. It’s like looking out at a perfectly framed landscape picture every time you enter your room. Of course, there is an opaque screen you can pull down and zip up for maximum shade or privacy, as well as transparent curtains which can be used as a mosquito net. The room also has no air conditioning but there is a small fan mounted in the corner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/04.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/05.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/06.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Every room comes with it’s own little private deck which includes a netted hammock, as well as a hanging hammock and some cushions to chill on. There’s also a step ladder leading directly into the water so when you wake up (and it will be hot when you do) you’re literally steps away from a refreshing plunge. I actually really appreciated having the personal hammocks and deck because often times at hotels and resorts there may be one or two of these features in a common area and you’ll have to wait for an opening to enjoy it (or wait for that one person who’s taking 50,000 photos for their Instagram). At Le Pirate Boatel, everyone gets a hammock!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/07.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/10.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We also got lucky with our room facing the sea most of the time we were there. They do rotate the boat daily, both for balance and I imagine also to make it more fair for guests staying on both sides of the boat. The other side of the boat faces the shore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/11.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Bathroom&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The boatel has a shared bathroom situation, and if you stay there it’s best to keep your expectations quite low. Let me just say this: it’s functional and reasonably clean— and there’s enough of them. There are two bathrooms designated for men and women each, but since they're single occupancy I can't imagine it really matters which bathroom you use. I never had any issues finding a free bathroom when I needed one. As for cleanliness, I say reasonable because, well, it’s on a boat. It’s in nature. I spotted some tiny, harmless little ants around the sink and sometimes on the walls in the bathrooms but it didn’t impact my ability to use the facilities. I’ll admit, I’ve also grown quite used to the presence of tiny ants in bathrooms from traveling throughout Southeast Asia. The more rustic your accomodations, the more likely they are to be there. Another thing I’ve gotten used to is the concept of the bathroom basically being a shower stall with a toilet in it. I’ve stayed at Airbnbs in Korea and Hong Kong with a similar set-up and while it takes some getting used to, it does make sense when you have limited space. Luckily, as I mentioned before, the space was as clean as it could be and even while sharing it with strangers, I never once walked in on anything gross in the bathrooms or had to clean up after anyone. Everyone onboard seemed to respect the common space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/12.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/13.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you do end up staying here, some more bathroom details to keep in mind: there is no hot water, but I would be very surprised if anyone felt like they needed it. It was transitioning to dry season while we were there and it was &lt;i&gt;hot&lt;/i&gt;. Also, since they have to get fresh water delivered to the boat for showering and brushing teeth, the faucet is designed to curb water waste. That means it’s not a knob you turn but a button you press that will let out a stream of water for somewhere between thirty seconds to a minute and then you’ll need to press it again for more water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The common areas of the boat are located on the upper deck, where you’ll find lounge chairs as well as long dining tables, the bar, food counter, and staff office. To be honest with such compelling private areas we mostly only came up here to eat or get something to drink. If you were traveling as a group with multiple rooms this would definitely be a good place to come hang out though, and you get a wider view from the upper deck than you would from your room— especially if it’s not facing the sea on any given day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/14.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/15.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/16.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/17.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I’ll be honest, the food on the boat was… &lt;i&gt;okay&lt;/i&gt;. It wasn’t bad but it was pretty clearly catered towards western tastes and thus sometimes a bit blander than what I'm used to. Our best meals in Labuan Bajo were all taken off the boat, like the one day we took the shuttle back to the harbor for lunch, and the day we went on a multi-island tour. Breakfast is included with your stay and that consists of a fruit, granola, and yogurt bar (which was actually quite good) as well as the option to order eggs cooked anyway you like. The eggs are served with bread and a slice of tomato. While it doesn’t offer much in the way of variety for those staying onboard for more than a couple of nights, it certainly wasn’t bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/18.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/19.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
For lunch you can order a la carte from a consistent menu of snacks that includes burgers and wings. We were actually never on the boat during lunchtime so I can’t comment on those. For dinner there’s a fixed rotating menu with a few options each night, and you’ll want to get your dinner order in before 5pm each day so they can prep it in time to be served at 7pm. Dinner is not included with your stay and it is a bit more expensive than what you would find on land because of the extra costs of getting the ingredients to the boat. In addition to your entree there’s also some sides set out (like a super good root vegetable hash). To reiterate, the food isn't bad but it’s ultimately a choice between convenience (staying on the boat) for food that’s fine but a bit more expensive versus going on land for something more mind-blowing that may be cheaper. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Due to the nature of the boatel we had quite a bit of interaction with the staff on board, between meal services and coordinating excursions off the boat. Everyone was incredibly friendly and awesome. One of the crew members even knew some basic Thai greetings! I was also not feeling well when we first arrived on the boat and slept most of the day, but the following day some of the staff on the boat as well as the hotel back on shore asked if I was feeling better, which I really appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/20.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The bay that the Boatel is anchored in is incredible peaceful, with a view that perfectly centers a sunset between two islands. It’s about a twenty minute boat-ride away from the crowded harbor, with only a few boats other boats in the vicinity. Not too far from the boatel on land is AYANA Komodo Resort, a sprawling complex that on Saturday nights sets of fireworks from a small boat that is often docked not too far away from the boatel. During the day the Boatel can also arrange for short activities in the nearby area like snorkeling and kayaking. There’s also an island right next to the boatel where sometimes you can spot monkeys hanging out around the beach.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/22.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/23.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/01.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
One other nice thing about the Boatel’s location is that if you decide to do a day trip to the surrounding islands like Padar, Komodo, and Rinca, it’s very likely that the tour boat will pick you up directly from the Boatel on the way to the other islands, as opposed to staying on land where you would have to travel to the harbor to get on the boat. At least, that’s what happened with us! I’ll be posting a review of the day-trip we took in a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I would not recommend Le Pirate Boatel for guests with mobility impairments. The boat transfers to get to and from the harbor to the boatel involve ascending and descending steps with no ramps and the upper deck of the Boatel is only accessible via stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/24.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Tons of these little fish hang around the boat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/boatel/21.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I would definitely recommend Le Pirate Boatel to adventurous travelers that enjoy nature (including all the unglamorous parts). Like I said in the beginning, the Boatel is more of a boat acting like a hotel than the other way around so I would ask yourself: would you enthusiastically choose to stay on an actual boat over a hotel for a few days? If the answer is yes, then I think you will enjoy the boatel. If your expectations are properly set and you’re not expecting a cruise ship or luxury hotel experience, you’ll have an amazing time onboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Le Pirate also offers a cruise-like experience in Labuan Bajo on a smaller boat which actually moves around between several of the main islands. I think I would be more likely to do the cruise experience if traveling with a group large enough to occupy the entire boat. However, I’m glad that we did the anchored boatel instead. It was nice to feel like you had a place to “come home” to at the end of a long day, and the rooms on the Boatel seem a little bit bigger and more private than those on the cruisers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;If you found this review helpful, please let Le Pirate know when you book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;new&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://lepirate.com/boatel/&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ Le Pirate Boatel&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/hokkaido/hokkaidolodging_thumb.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality/&quot;&gt;What Hokkaido taught me about hospitality&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/birdhouse/1.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/birdhouse-el-nido-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Birdhouse El Nido in Palawan, Philippines&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates:September 15 — 18, 2018 Rate: $43/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">17 cool places to stay in Upstate New York</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-places-to-stay-upstate-new-york/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="17 cool places to stay in Upstate New York" /><published>2018-09-23T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-09-23T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best-places-to-stay-upstate-new-york</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-places-to-stay-upstate-new-york/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3&quot; src=&quot;../images/upstate/arnold_1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thearnoldhouse.com&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;thearnoldhouse.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;As we make our way towards the end of September, I'm starting to develop some serious seasonal FOMO towards my east coast friends as they experience all the trademarks of transitioning into autumn. The flame-colored leaves, toasty spiced drinks, and that slight chill in the air that brings out everyone's most fashionable attire. Do you know how long it's been since I've worn layers? Here in Thailand we get two seasons: wet and dry, and they're pretty much the same minus the higher probability of getting caught in a merciless rainstorm (I've seriously been considering buying a pair of Crocs as a result).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;If I were still living in New York, I'd probably be planning an escape upstate right about now. With no work holidays between Labor Day and Thanksgiving (depending on how your employer feels about Indigenous Peoples' Day and Veterans Day), I usually need a little weekend trip somewhere in between to tide me over until the holiday season is in full swing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Plus, if you asked me, I'd tell you that I think upstate New York is where some of the most &lt;i&gt;exciting&lt;/i&gt; things are happening in the American lodging and hospitality game right now. What was once a landscape dominated by grandeur ski and lakeside resorts for wealthy families has now been balanced by stripped down farmhouses, resuscitated motels, and cozy cabins catered to couples and groups of friends. So even if you're not based near New York, maybe the next time you hit up the big apple, you can make a detour to go apple picking instead (Ha! See what I did there?).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Below are my top choices for places to stay all across upstate New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a weekend stay in October or November 2018. &lt;br /&gt;The InnBox may collect a share of sales from booking links on this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;1. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bullandgarland.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Bull &amp;amp; Garland&lt;/a&gt;, Hobart&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $135/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/bull_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/bull_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/bull_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/15002932&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Bull &amp;amp; Garland is an English pub and inn located in the Catskills town of Hobart, which is often described as &quot;bucolic&quot;, &quot;storybook-like&quot;, and is notable for its many bookstores. The building which Bull &amp;amp; Garland occupies was formerly a coaching inn built in 1830s (a coaching inn catered to those traveling by stage coach and often included a stable for the horses). One of the owners of the Bull &amp;amp; Garland previously managed pubs in London before settling down in the Catskills. The inn's accompanying pub is open from Thursday to Sunday for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Three of the four suites at The Bull &amp;amp; Garden are located on the second floor, while &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/28455545&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Victoria&lt;/a&gt; is located on the ground floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;2. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/brentwood.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Brentwood Hotel&lt;/a&gt;, Saratoga Springs&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $197/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/brentwood_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/brentwood_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/brentwood_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/brentwood.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Booking.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Brentwood Hotel is located right off the historic Saratoga race course, America's oldest racetrack. The building itself was originally a motel which has been refurbished by Brooklyn-based Studio Tack, which you may know as the people behind those cute Public—Supply notebooks. They're also the team behind Scribner's Lodge, also on this list. The hotel has a lot of subtle equestrian touches; it's like the horse girl all grown up. Your stay includes complementary coffee in the hotel lobby as well as free use of Linus bikes for exploring the town and nearby mineral springs. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;All rooms are located on the ground floor, accessible via a gravel lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;3. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/16497757&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Olive Outpost&lt;/a&gt;, Olivebridge&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $250/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/olive_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/olive_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/olive_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/16497757&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This place is so stinkin' cute and perfect for groups. It's the upstate home of one of the founders of Heyday, a facial spa chain based in New York City. The lumber and gravel used in the house were sourced from local pine trees and quarries, and the home is situated in the middle of a meadow which fills up with fireflies at night. With its many big, bright windows and surrounding trees, this is an especially perfect place to witness the leaves change in the fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The home is located on an elevated platform, without paved road access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;4. &lt;a href=&quot;http://getawaycabin.com/kohl3&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Getaway&lt;/a&gt;, Somewhere 2.5 Hours from NYC&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $199/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/getaway_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/getaway_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/getaway_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;http://getawaycabin.com/kohl3&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Getaway.house&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Getaway operates three outposts outside the major metropolitan cities of New York, Boston, and Washington D.C. Each outpost is outfitted with a selection of minimal, sleekly designed, pet-friendly camper cabins that are perfect for 2-4 people. Each cabin comes equipped with a mini-kitchen and drinkable water, as well as a toilet and hot shower with biodegradable toiletries. The exact location of each outpost is kept a secret until a week before your booking, in order to dissuade guests from over planning their trip. Getaway also offers an &lt;a href=&quot;https://getaway.house/artist&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;artist residency&lt;/a&gt; for creatives who need a little unblocking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;For $25 off your first stay, use our &lt;a href=&quot;http://getawaycabin.com/kohl3&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;referral link: getawaycabin.com/kohl3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Getaway cabins are elevated and accessible via a short flight of stairs, and surrounded by unpaved grounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;5. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxfiremountainhouse.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Foxfire Mountain House&lt;/a&gt;, Mt. Tremper&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/foxfire_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/foxfire_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/foxfire_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxfiremountainhouse.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Foxfiremountainhouse.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Foxfire Mountain House is the dreamy little love nest of a nomadic chef and a television producer. They renovated the 100 year old building in the Catskills, which now houses eleven bookable suites for guests, as well as a pet-friendly three-bedroom cottage. Dinner is available in the Bar Room on weekends and a complimentary Nordic-inspired breakfast is included with your stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Please contact the inn directly for more accessibility information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;6. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/stickett-inn.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Stickett Inn&lt;/a&gt;, Barryville&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $160/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/stickett_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/stickett_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/stickett_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/stickett-inn.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Booking.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Stickett Inn has been described by its owners as a &lt;a href=&quot;http://gayletter.com/weekend-stickett-inn/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;&quot;sexy Boyscout camp for gays&quot;&lt;/a&gt;, located in a charming little town on the New York-Pennsylvania border. The inn itself has four suites, minimally decorated with shibori-dyed sheets and rustic steel bathtubs. There's also a two bedroom cottage behind The Inn, playfully referred to as &quot;The Rear&quot;. Hopefully you're catching on to the cheeky naming convention and I don't need to spell it out! ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Please enquire directly with the property for accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;7. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sprucetoninn.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Spruceton Inn&lt;/a&gt;, West Kill&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $169/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/spruceton_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/spruceton_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/spruceton_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sprucetoninn.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Sprucetoninn.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Formerley a vacation resort known as &quot;Schwarzenegger's Sunshine Valley House&quot; (yes, that Schwarzenegger), now Spruceton Inn, a renovated and minimalist motel smack dab in the middle of the Catskills. The inn houses nine rooms (some with kitchenettes), five fire pits, a bar/canteen, and an events barn whose construction was originally started in the 1800s. Owned by a designer and an illustrator, it should come as no surprise that the Spruceton also offers a week-long &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sprucetoninn.com/artist-residency/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Artist Residency&lt;/a&gt; during the winter months for those who seek a quiet, inspiring place to create.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Units are located on the ground floor, however accessible via an unpaved road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;8. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/wm-farmer-and-sons.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Wm Farmer &amp;amp; Sons&lt;/a&gt;, Hudson&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $229/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/wm_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/wm_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/wm_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/wm-farmer-and-sons.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Booking.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you ever drive through Hudson, it's hard not to notice the brilliant white corner building that Wm Farmer and Sons occupies. The Farmer family bought the 19th century building and former grocery in 2013 and spent two years renovating it into the guesthouse it is today. Wm Farmer and Sons now consists of 13 bookable spaces across three buildings, all decked out in a dark and cozy color scheme with rich wooden accents, clawfoot tubs, and gas stove fireplaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Wm Farmer &amp;amp; Sons has two ground floor units in their &quot;Annex Suite&quot; next door the main building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;9. &lt;a href=&quot;https://hoteltivoli.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel Tivoli&lt;/a&gt;, Tivoli&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $229/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/tivoli_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/tivoli_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/tivoli_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://hoteltivoli.org&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Hoteltivoli.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Hotel Tivoli is owned and operated by two painters, Brice and Helen Marden, who are apparently a big deal in the art world (but hey, it's okay, I don't know who they are either). The pair bought up the Tivoli when its former incarnation, the Madalin Hotel, shut down— and their local neighborhood hangout along with it. The Mardens gave the hotel a colorful makeover, including a unique purple tint to the wooden floors, and also re-did the restaurant which now features a mediterranean-inspired menu and cocktails designed by the team behind NYC bar Employees Only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;All units are located on the second and third floors in a building with stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;10. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=2668037&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Scribner's Catskill Lodge&lt;/a&gt;, Hunter&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/scribner_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/scribner_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/scribner_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scribnerslodge.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Scribnerslodge.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Scribner's Lodge is the third life of a site that was originally home to a grand 1880's hotel, and a 1960's motor lodge long after that. In its most recent revival designed by Studio Tack (who are also on this list for Brentwood), the lodge gets a woodsy Scandinavian-influenced makeover with blonde lumber, whitewashed walls, and textile accents. There are 38 guestrooms and suites, a heated outdoor pool, nightly bonfires, and on-site restaurant featuring a Swiss-inspired menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Two standard rooms are suitable for wheelchair-users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;11. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nineriverroad.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;9 River Road&lt;/a&gt;, Calicoon&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $209/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/9river_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/9river_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/9river_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nineriverroad.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Nineriverroad.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
9 River Road was originally built in 1884 as a family home and furniture store, and then later served as a boarding house in the 1930's. It's now in the hands of its third owner, the Fosters, an upstate-based hospitality company also behind The Arnold House (next on this list), North Branch Inn, and The Debruce. 9 River Road features 8 bright guest rooms and some cozy common areas like the kitchen (where you'll check in) and porch. Your stay at 9 River Road also includes free use of their bikes so you can fully explore the border town of Calicoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There are two ground floor rooms and a paved entrance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;12. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thearnoldhouse.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Arnold House&lt;/a&gt;, Livingston Manor&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $249/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/arnold_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/arnold_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/arnold_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thearnoldhouse.com&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Thearnoldhouse.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Arnold House was the first boutique hotel opened by Foster Supply Hospitality group (the team behind 9 River Road, listed above). The Foster family itself goes back five generations in Livingston Manor, a hamlet to the west of The Catskills. The Arnold House consists of 13 rooms spread across three buildings, as well as a bookable Lake House located up the road from the main building. The rooms manage to keep their vintage charm with antique furniture and their original wooden floors. If you plan your stay in the spring you may be lucky enough to partake in the Arnold House's ramp picking weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The rooms in the main building are all located on the second floor. However, there is a ground-floor unit in the Garden House. Please reach out directly to the hotel for more accessibility information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;13. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lazymeadow.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Kate's Lazy Meadow&lt;/a&gt;, Mt. Tremper&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $99/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/lazy_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/lazy_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/lazy_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lazymeadow.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Lazymeadow.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Kate's Lazy Meadow is a renovated motel with a famous founder. The kitschy, psychedelic interior design all makes sense when you realize that this is the baby and brainchild of Kate Pierson of the B-52s. The motel rooms channel &quot;Love Shack&quot; vibes with their colorful vintage kitchens and space-age decor (very Jetsons-do-Woodstock, which is only a 15 minute drive away from the meadow). In addition to the motel rooms, Kate's complex also includes a separate cabin and lodge for groups to rent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;All units in the main motel building are on the ground floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;14. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rivertownlodge.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Rivertown Lodge&lt;/a&gt;, Hudson&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $265/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/rivertown_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/rivertown_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/rivertown_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://rivertownlodge.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Rivertownlodge.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If there's a hotel on this list you may have heard of, it's probably Rivertown Lodge, which has received a lot of press and accolades for its transformation of a former movie theater and motel into a 27-room oasis and &quot;public living room&quot; that's a showcase of Hudson's local artisans. The hotel was designed by Brooklyn studio Workstead, who have worked on The Wythe Hotel as well as The Dewberry in Charleston (featured in our &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/last-minute-valentines-day-escapes/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Valentine's Day post&lt;/a&gt;). Some of the rooms have unusual layouts— a problem the owners solved by building beds directly into them. Though these tend to be smaller rooms, they have since become fan favorites and are the first snapped up by guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Units are located on the second floor and accessible via stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;15. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/roundhouse-beacon2.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Roundhouse&lt;/a&gt;, Beacon&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $229/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/roundhouse_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/roundhouse_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/roundhouse_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/roundhouse-beacon2.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Booking.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I originally featured The Roundhouse in our &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/last-minute-valentines-day-escapes/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Valentine's Day post&lt;/a&gt;, so this place truly has year-round charm. If you're a minimalist who wants an unobstructed view of the changing leaves then The Roundhouse is perfect you. It may even be worth splurging for a room with a circular tub overlooking the window. Beacon is only two hours north of the city and while you're there you can hit up the famous Dia:Beacon museum— the MTA even sells &lt;a href=&quot;http://web.mta.info/mnr/html/getaways/outbound_diabeacon.htm
&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;a package&lt;/a&gt; that includes both your round-trip transportation on the MetroNorth as well the museum admission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Roundhouse has facilities for guests with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;16. &lt;a href=&quot;https://atinyhouseresort.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;A Tiny House Resort&lt;/a&gt;, South Cairo&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $175-295/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/tinyhouse_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/tinyhouse_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/tinyhouse_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://atinyhouseresort.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Atinyhouseresort.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
A Tiny House Resort is another collective of custom-designed modern campers (similar to &lt;a href=&quot;getawaycabin.com/kohl3&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Getaway&lt;/a&gt;, listed earlier). These are located in South Cairo, a town in the northern Catskills, and sit overlooking the picturesque Catskill Creek. The campers were designed with the &quot;tiny house&quot; lifestyle in mind, and while most are rustic yet minimal, there's even a &quot;lux&quot; option for those who don't want to leave behind their creature comforts. Most of the campers are priced the same regardless of their occupancy, meaning you can either get cozy with a group of friends to save money, or pay a premium for your own space. They do have one smaller camper, &quot;The Green Bean&quot;, for two that is priced cheaper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Cabins are elevated and accessible via a few short steps, and surrounded by unpaved grounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;17. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thisoldhudson.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;This Old Hudson&lt;/a&gt;, Hudson&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $295/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/thisold_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/thisold_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/upstate/thisold_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thisoldhudson.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Thisoldhudson.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I saved my personal favorite for last. This Hudson property was originally built in 1915 and has been renovated into two separate bookable spaces for guests by a celebrated prop stylist. The home also serves as a studio space for his company, Zio &amp;amp; Sons. The homes all feature a clever mix of high quality materials and surprisingly affordable furniture finds. The 1,300 square feet upstairs studio space also includes a reading nook, dressing room, and porch. Guests also receive a cute custom-designed travel guide to the neighborhood upon arrival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
One of This Old Hudson's units is located on the ground floor, but we recommend reaching out directly to the host for more accessibility details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our where-to-stay roundups:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-boutique-hotels-paris/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/paris/paris_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-boutique-hotels-paris/&quot;&gt;The 7 best boutique hotels in Paris under $300&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/where-to-stay-palm-springs/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/palmsprings/ps_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/where-to-stay-palm-springs/&quot;&gt;8 Places to Stay in Palm Springs that aren't the Ace Hotel &amp;amp; Pool Club&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Photos via thearnoldhouse.com</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: The Marshall House in Savannah, Georgia</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/the-marshall-house-savannah-georgia-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: The Marshall House in Savannah, Georgia" /><published>2018-09-09T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-09-09T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-marshall-house-savannah-georgia-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/the-marshall-house-savannah-georgia-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; May 30 — June 1, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $161/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;dib&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Sabrina&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; Her Best Friend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/marshall/00.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
As much as I love a modern, new building with a fresh take on hospitality, I also &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; hotels with a rich history. I'm intrigued by buildings that have lived many lives and I like to think about all the people who may have passed through the same hallways, or looked out of the same window as me but at an entirely different view outside. So naturally I was very excited to stay &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/the-marshall-house.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Marshall House&lt;/a&gt;, which claims to have been Savannah’s first hotel. It also claims to be haunted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The house, which was originally built in 1851 was occupied by Union soldiers towards the end of the Civil War and served as a hospital for wounded soldiers, as well as during two subsequent yellow fever outbreaks. So needless to say a lot of shit went down in these halls. A lot of amputations. In the late 1990s when the hotel was being restored to its most recent incarnation, workers found human remains— mostly arms and legs— hidden under one of the floorboards. Yikes. The staff also reported bad vibes and odors coming from a few specific rooms at the hotel— 214, 314, and 414. In addition, guests over the years claimed to have seen ghosts of young children, civil war soldiers, and the hotel’s founding matron herself roaming the halls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
So, yeah, historic hotels certainly come with a lot of baggage— the supernatural aside, old buildings have foundational problems they have to overcome to meet the needs of the modern traveler. So let me tell you how The Marshall House stacks up in 2018…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Upon landing at the airy Savannah/Hilton Head International Airport, we grabbed an uber with the original plan of heading straight to our hotel downtown. However, a few minutes into chatting away with our driver— a born and bred Savannah local— we were convinced to make a pit stop for lunch at &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/mrs-wilkes-dining-room/4b3a53a7f964a520b26425e3&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Mrs. Wilkes Dining Room&lt;/a&gt; first. At Mrs. Wilkes twenty dollars treats you to an all-you-can-eat meal served family style, where you’ll sit at a big table with strangers (likely other tourists) as side after side and plate after plate of food is served until the entire surface area of the table is covered in dishes. It was a great experience to start off our time in Savannah and afterwards, feeling sufficiently carbo-loaded, we walked the remaining 8-or-so blocks to the hotel.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/01.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/03.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/02.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Upon arriving at the hotel we were greeted by the doorman and a welcome gust of air conditioning. The check-in process was fairly straightforward, with the unexpected surprise of a complimentary upgrade from the “petite queen” room I had booked (the hotel’s most affordable offering) to a “superior king” room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The room we were upgraded to was very simple and traditional— not the type of aesthetic I usually gravitate towards but suiting for a historical hotel and inoffensive. I did appreciate having the larger bed to spread out in (maybe my BFF who likes to cuddle would disagree) but as far as I can tell from photos online, the petite queen room’s layout may actually be better. In our king room there were some odd organizational choices such as an arm chair tucked away into a dark corner of the room, making it less an appealing spot to lounge and more like an elaborate shelf for my duffel bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/04.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/05.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/06.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/07.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Our view was also virtually non-existent and of the parking lot behind the building— which I didn’t mind as much as the fact that there was only one window in the corner of the room. If you’ve been following my reviews for awhile, you might know that I crave, &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; natural lighting to feel at peace in the world. In our room it was a bit scant, and a bit gloomy. While I doubt adding an extra window would be a trivial change to make, it does feel like the rooms could use a few furnishing updates to feel as lively as the common spaces downstairs.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Bathroom&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;As mediocre as the bedrooms are, the bathrooms were a pleasant surprise that truly transported me. With its checkerboard tile floors, white paneling, and vintage light fixtures, one could really believe for a moment that they’re in a turn-of-the-century southern hospital. Well, more like the romanticized ideal of such a thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/08.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/09.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The bathrooms were very clean despite their retro appearance, though the facilities themselves felt a bit older. Our shower faucet kept trickling despite our best attempts to turn it off completely, a problem that could only be solved by the housekeeping’s midas touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;While I’m lukewarm about the rooms, the common spaces are where The Marshall House truly shines. It’s not just in how they’re decorated— bright, airy, colorful— but how they are utilized. Every evening starting at 5:30pm there’s a complimentary wine happy hour in the hotel’s lounge, which is styled like a fancy southern living room. There’s even an attendant on hand to refill your glass with your choice of red, white, or rosé. What’s cool though is that in addition to the wine there’s also complimentary entertainment— some days it’s a musical session by a harpist, one who even takes contemporary requests— when we there she played us a little Death Cab for Cutie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/10.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/12.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/11.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The second night of our stay, in lieu of musical entertainment there was a history lesson led by a local historian. This happy hour was surprisingly much more crowded than the harpist’s, and had many older couples in attendance. Pretty much every available seat in the lounge was taken. The historian spoke at length about the history of the hotel— which I was pleasantly surprised to learn centered around a female real estate tycoon. The hotel was founded by Mary Marshall, a local business woman who inherited and grew her father’s fortune as his only heir and was responsible for many new developments in Savannah in the 1800s. She never had any biological children but at age 50 adopted a daughter— who excelled at playing the harp. Ah, it all makes sense. The historian also pointed out a lot of interesting architectural details, encouraging visitors to roam the hotel and see them for themselves— like oddly placed fireplaces and historical drawings of Savannah in its heyday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/13.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/14.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/15.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food + Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Marshall House has an atrium where they serve a breakfast buffet for around $10 per person, but with such a short time in Savannah we passed on eating food at the hotel in favor of the local restaurants nearby. The Marshall House’s extremely central location put it walking distance to several great places to grab a bite. Some of my favorites in the area were... &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/the-coffee-fox/50784378e4b0459b7580fba5&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Coffee Fox&lt;/a&gt;, just a few blocks west— an Austin-themed coffeeshop with chill staff and delicious kolaches, &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/olde-pink-house-restaurant/4b1075ebf964a520ec7023e3&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Olde Pink House&lt;/a&gt; for a fancy dinner, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/little-duck-diner/59d27c4c2105c3413dc411f6&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Little Duck Diner&lt;/a&gt; for a boozy brunch. Also in the area is &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/moon-river-brewing-company/4b2d22a5f964a52030cf24e3&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Moon River Brewing Company&lt;/a&gt;, where you can get a really generous tasting flight of 10 beers for $15 and &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/savannah-bee-company/4d63d214dd51ba7a7b30ba02&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Savannah Bee Company&lt;/a&gt; which does a really yummy mead tasting flight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/16.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/17.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Left: Olde Pink House; Right: Lavender bubble bath bellini at Little Duck Diner.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;All the staff that we interacted with at The Marshall House were extremely friendly and polite, from the doormen to the nightly entertainment and concierge. We bought a bottle wine from the front desk on our last night at the hotel with the intention of spending the night in and enjoying it, but ended up feeling too full to imbibe. Luckily the staff were very understanding and gave us a full refund since we didn’t open the bottle. It seems like the obvious thing to do but you’d be surprised how many businesses wouldn’t. Overall The Marshall House definitely lives up the reputation of southern hospitality.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Marshall House does have elevator access to all of its floors, and in addition has rooms specifically designated for accessibility with roll-in showers. Check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://wheelchairjimmy.com/savannahga/hotels/the-marshall-house/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;this review&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/marshall/18.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I think The Marshall House is an ideal place to stay for first timers to Savannah, like me on this trip. It’s price-point is mid-range: it’s neither the cheapest nor the most expensive hotel in the area, but it may have the best location. While there’s a cluster of newer looking hotels closer to the river, I really preferred The Marshall House’s spot, integrated on a street with coffee shops, bars, boutiques, and a historic theater. It goes without saying that history buffs or anyone who likes to nerd out about that sort of thing would really enjoy it here. I would probably recommend either going with the most affordable room or splurging for one of the balcony rooms, or the Mary Marshall suite, which would presumably get more light and have a better view. It was nice that we got a free upgrade but I don’t know if I would be willing to pay out of my own pocket for our mid-tier king room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
As for any paranormal activity— I can’t say I personally experienced or sensed any restless spirits. Sure, there were creaking floorboards at night but that seems par for the course for an old building. Perhaps I just don’t have the magic touch that would attract said spirits, but I can’t say it bothered me. I felt a lot more comfortable and at peace not thinking about it, and perhaps too distracted by all the fun I was having in Savannah to notice. I was also severely jetlagged having just traveled from Bangkok so as soon as I hit the sheets, I was out. Sorry, ghosts. Maybe next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If I were to go back to Savannah I’d probably want to stay in a less central location to get a better taste of local life in the city but again for first time visitors, considering all the restaurants, nightlife, and attractions it’s walking distance from, combined with the historical atmosphere, it’s certainly a unique place to stay for a reasonable value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;
Please use our link below to book at The Marshall House (or any other hotel!). The InnBox may collect a small share of sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/the-marshall-house.en.html?aid=1452227&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ The Marshall House&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-slow-canggu-bali-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/slow/01.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-slow-canggu-bali-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Slow in Canggu, Bali&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-aviary-hotel-siem-reap-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/aviary/00.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-aviary-hotel-siem-reap-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: The Aviary Hotel in Siem Reap, Cambodia&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: May 30 — June 1, 2018 Rate: $161/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Best Friend</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Xiao Chi: A comprehensive guide to street food in Taiwan</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/xiao-chi-taiwanese-street-food-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Xiao Chi: A comprehensive guide to street food in Taiwan" /><published>2018-09-02T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-09-02T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/xiao-chi-taiwanese-street-food-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/xiao-chi-taiwanese-street-food-guide/">&lt;div class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;By&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/tarngerine/&quot;&gt;Julius Tarng&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/ST.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There’s a saying in Taiwan, 「吃就對了」,  and it’s often the advice I get when I visit a new city and ask my host for recommendations. It roughly translates to “just eat — you can’t go wrong”. I love this advice because it matches with the way I explore both cities and markets — comb every block on foot and eat anything that looks good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Xiao Chi (小吃), meaning “little eats” a.k.a. street food, is available any time of the day in restaurants, shophouses with sidewalk tables, food carts or the night market. Wherever you stay, there’s likely several places to eat just around your block. Got jetlag? Most breakfast places open at the crack of dawn, and many night markets and midnight snack (宵夜) places are open late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Like many other countries, Taiwanese cuisine emphasizes umami, sweetness, and deep frying as many things as you can. However, I’d like to introduce your palette to the most important element of Taiwanese food: QQ. To be Q is to be bouncy, chewy, squishy. If you’ve had fresh tapioca pearls in your bubble/boba/pearl milk tea, you’ve experienced QQ. If you’ve ever had sticky rice, you’ve experienced QQ. If you’ve ever had gummy bears or pasta al dente, you’ve almost
experienced QQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 pl4 pt4 pr4 pb4 bg-washed-yellow&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;​​While most people head to Taipei when they visit the country, I also highly recommend pulling a day or two for a food tour of Tainan, the former capital and Taiwanese food paradise in the south. Several of the dishes below are best tried in Tainan, including ba wan, oyster omelette, and mi gao. Tainan is 2 hours from Taipei by high speed rail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 pt4 pt5-ns pb2 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Xiao Chi 101&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The first part of this guide introduces some of Taiwan’s most popular street foods. You might have had some of these already, but it’s worth seeking them out in their homeland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;黑糖珍珠奶茶 - Black sugar bubble tea&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;hei tang zhen zhu nai cha&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/PMT_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/PMT_1.JPG&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/D3zmVrzdTeQ2&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Chen San Ding Black Sugar Bubble Tea&lt;/a&gt;, Taipei.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Bubble/boba/pearl milk tea is probably the most famous Taiwanese export, but Taiwan really screwed up  its branding and never standardized the translation (for the record, PMT is technically correct but who has time to say PMT). Most chains use syrups for sweetening, but find a shop that uses black sugar with a fresh batch of pearls for optimal QQ. QQ potential: pearls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;鹽酥雞 - salt and pepper fried chicken&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;yan su ji&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/Popcorn_Chicken.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Boneless, bite-sized, and twice fried. Most stalls will offer it along size a bunch of other stuff you can deep fry with the chicken. I recommend sweet potato fries and chicken butt (a fatty piece that comes from the rear end, my childhood favorite). QQ potential: guess what? Chicken butt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;牛肉麵 - beef noodle soup&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;niu rou mian&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/BNS_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The apex of noodle soups (okay, phở and ramen are pretty dang good, too), with large chunks of tender beef and crisp. You can choose clear (清燉) or spicy (紅燒) broth, and wide or thin noodles, as well as the mix of meat to tendon (I prefer all meat). ALWAYS choose spicy (it’s not spicy) and wide noodles. QQ potential: noodles semi al dente, and tendon if you get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;蔥油餅 - scallion pancake&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;cong you bing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/SP_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/SP_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/ANMjdXYgqWH2&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Tian Jin Onion Pancake&lt;/a&gt;, Taipei.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Fried, flaky, and fragrant. You can have it on its own or stick stuff inside: eggs, basil, beef, ham — whatever your heart desires! The croissant of Taiwan uses oil instead of butter for max flakiness. QQ potential: the dough inside must be chewy and not dry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;掛包 - Taiwanese hamburger&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;gua bao&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/GB.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/Rb9ewN6R1jS2&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;藍家割包 Lan Jia Traditional Taiwanese Snack&lt;/a&gt;, Taipei.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Many ramen joints in America sell pork buns that are extremely similar to gua bao. Gua bao also uses pork belly, but adds crushed peanuts, cilantro, and a hit of sugar. QQ potential: the bun and pork belly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;胡椒餅 - black pepper bun&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;hu jiao bing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/BPB_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/BPB_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/EPwMeXK9vxH2&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;老甕碳烤胡椒餅&lt;/a&gt;, Taipei.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Like a regular meat bun, but you spilled too much black pepper in the mix and also accidentally stuck it to the inside of the tandoor you happened to own. Baked at extremely high temperatures, black pepper buns are crispy on the outside, and juicy on the inside. QQ potential: the meat mixture as a giant chewy ball of umami.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 pt3 pt4-ns pb2 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Xiao Chi 102&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Slightly less commonly known, but I end up eating each of these at least once every trip because they’re so good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;蛋餅 - egg pancake&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;dan bing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/EP.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
My breakfast of choice. A staple found at any of the many breakfast spots in Taiwan that also sell soy milk, Chinese donuts, rice balls, shao bing pastry, and more. Similar to scallion pancake, but with an egg and not deep fried. QQ potential: dough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;油飯 - oil rice&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;you fan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/OR_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/OR_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
My absolute favorite comfort food. A dish that combines the Q of glutinous sticky rice and the umami of shiitake mushrooms and dried shrimp, ideally topped with cilantro. QQ potential: everything in this bowl of rice is Q.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;米糕 - mi gao&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/MG.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/A9yWtRKJBLy&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;戽斗米糕&lt;/a&gt;, Tainan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Mi gao is similar to oil rice, and is also one of my favorite dishes. In addition to the mushrooms and dried shrimp, mi gao also often includes pork belly, fish floss and a side of sweet pickles. QQ potential: everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;飯糰 - rice ball&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;fan tuan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/FT.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Like Japanese onigiri, it’s a ball of rice with magic inside. Like oil rice and mi gao, it also uses glutinous sticky rice, and common ingredients include pork floss, egg, pickles, and even a Chinese donut. You can find both savory and sweet rice balls at most stalls. QQ potential: rice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;綠豆薏仁 - mung bean and adlay soup&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;lü dou yi ren&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/MBS.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I’m upset, because mung bean is the worst translation for this delicious bean. In Chinese it’s “green bean”, and it’s the cousin of red bean, but because green beans the vegetable exists in English, we have to translate it to mung bean. While red bean soup is usually served hot in cold weather, mung bean soup is served chilled in the summer. With a slight sweetness and the Q texture of adlay, this is one of my favorite desserts. QQ potential: adlay. You can get it without adlay, but it’s a lot mushier in texture with only mung beans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;豆花 - silken tofu&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;dou hua&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/ST.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Freshly made, this fluffy tofu, usually served with a simple syrup and soft peanuts, glides down your throat. Served hot or cold, and you can customize the heckin heck out of it. Red beans? Cool. Tapioca pearls? No problem. Mung bean and adlay soup? You’ll get some weird looks but okay. QQ potential: this is the exemption where the softer the tofu, the better. The Q will come from the ingredients you choose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;芋圓 - taro balls&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;yu yuan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/TB.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/BUVLYWaoN8U2&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;阿柑姨芋圓 Ah Gan Taro Balls&lt;/a&gt;, Jiufen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
QQ! One of the most QQ desserts you can get. The purple ones are taro, and often come with the yellow sweet potato balls. It can be served with crushed ice, silken tofu, or grass jelly and can be found at many crushed ice dessert shops. This one is on grass jelly with a slightly sweet creamer. QQ potential: so Q the one chain I found outside of Taiwan that serves taro balls is named QQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 pt3 pt4-ns pb2 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Dr. Xiao Chi, PhD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;If you’re ready to show off to your Taiwanese family and friends, tell them you tried and liked each of these dishes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;臭豆腐 - stinky tofu&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;chou dou fu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/ST_LWYang.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/lwy/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;LW Yang&lt;/a&gt; via Flickr/Creative Commons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Yea, it smells bad, and it smells worse when they’re in the middle of deep frying it, which is when you’re likely in line for it. I swear it tastes good! It’s deep fried, garlicky spicy fermented goodness. Often served with a tangy Taiwanese pickled cabbage (or Taiwanese kimchi, if you will). Unlike the other stinky food, durian, stinky tofu pungence does not stick around long after you eat it, as it’s dwarfed by the smell of garlic. QQ potential: really varies depending on the style. I’ve had a slightly soft, soupier version that was extremely QQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;肉圓 - ba wan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/BW.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/Yt38yANWLg42&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;杜蝦仁肉丸&lt;/a&gt;, Tainan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
How would we take a regular meat bun and make it as QQ as possible? Replace rice flour with glutinous rice flour! One of the dishes that sparks the most Taiwanese pride, and you get extremely weird looks if you pronounce it in Mandarin instead of Taiwanese. You can find ba wan that are giant, and ba wan that are bite sized. Pictured are bite sized shrimp ba wan I had in Tainan. QQ potential: it is the definition of QQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;蚵仔煎 - oyster omelette&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;oh ah jian&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/OO.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Oyster omelettes originate from the Teochew region in China, and you can find many variants of it, including in Thailand. What makes the Taiwanese version unique is, you guessed it: it’s QQ as heck! Similar to ba wan, using glutinous rice flour mixed with the egg and oysters produces an insanely goopy and crispy texture that’s hard to resist, especially with a good sweet and sour sauce on top. QQ potential: c’mon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;腕粿 - bowled rice cake&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;wah gweh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/BRC_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/BRC_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/Hr1Q3A7q3rz&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Fu Sheng Hao 富盛號碗粿&lt;/a&gt;, Tainan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I swear this dish is impossible to photograph to look tasty. It’s a savory rice cake where pork, shiitakes, and other goodies are steamed with glutinous rice flour into a small bowl. You’ll get a tiny fork and hopefully instructions to carve around the edge of the cake, and then split it into four. I did not see these instructions until after my second time having it, so these photos really look unappetizing. It’s often served with a sweet and sour fish cake soup 魚羹. QQ potential: it’s like a solid block of QQ.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;藥燉排骨 - medicinal rib stew&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;yao dun pai gu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/taiwanfood/MRS.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Try it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/4fEbPVJzCny&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;陳董藥燉排骨&lt;/a&gt;, Taipei.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Chinese medicine is the bane of every child whose parents made them drink it when they were sick. Somehow, they’ve turned it into a delcious stew with fall-off-the-bone pork ribs. QQ potential: tender meat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you’ve got anything from this list, I hope I’ve impressed upon you how important QQ is. I’d like to submit it to whatever governing culinary body can add QQ as the 6th taste after sweetness, sourness, bitterness, saltiness, and umami.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Xiao Chi Tips&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;f5&quot;&gt;If there’s a lot of people in line, you should probably queue up, too. Otherwise, use Google maps to check ratings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;f5&quot;&gt;Shops often close for break from 2-5PM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;f5&quot;&gt;General night market advice: zigzag through every row once before buying anything, making notes of anything you like. You don’t want to be in the position where you want to eat something but you’re too full.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;f5&quot;&gt;In Tainan, you’ll be hard pressed if you don’t speak or read Chinese. I highly recommend finding a food tour guide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt4 pt5-ns pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;About Julius&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Julius currently lives in Bangkok and loves to eat, draw, and play games (sometimes making his own). Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/tarngerine/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;@tarngerine&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram to see tasty food stories from all over Asia, figure drawing and character design, as well as the occasional 8-bit game made in Pico-8.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Love food? Then you'll love these travel guides:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/bedstuy/bedstuy_food_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn/&quot;&gt;10 places to feed your stomache and your soul in Bed-Stuy, Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-algarve-portugal-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/algarve/00.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/the-algarve-portugal-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Your travel guide to The Algarve, Portugal: where to stay and what to do.&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Julius Tarng</name></author><summary type="html">By Julius Tarng</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Traversing Hokkaido in 8 days: a road trip itinerary and travel guide</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hokkaido-road-trip-itinerary-and-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Traversing Hokkaido in 8 days: a road trip itinerary and travel guide" /><published>2018-08-18T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-08-18T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hokkaido-road-trip-itinerary-and-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hokkaido-road-trip-itinerary-and-guide/">&lt;div class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;By&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot;&gt;Sabrina Majeed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/AKA_1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;When one imagines traveling to Japan, the first image that comes to mind may be the bustling neon lights of Tokyo, or the tranquil temples in Kyoto. Perhaps even the southern beaches of Kyushu. Hokkaido, Japan’s northerly pastoral island, doesn’t typically rank highly on the list— but I have a feeling that’s about to change. While it still feels off the radar for American travelers, vacationers in Asian countries such as Taiwan, China, South Korea, and Thailand have been increasingly flocking to this bountiful island.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Hokkaido is a nature lover’s dream. Summertime is filled with more vibrant, saturated shades of green and blue than I had ever seen before, but there’s something to see in all seasons. Swap out summer’s melons and lavender blooms for skiing and ice-breaking tours in the wintertime, bursts of red and orange leaves in the fall, or springtime’s cherry blossoms and pink moss phlox. Aside from the outdoorsy type, there’s another kind of traveler that Hokkaido is perfect for: the kind that hates crowds. With the exception of Furano and nearby Biei, it sometimes feels like you have the whole island to yourself. It’s all open road, fertile farmlands, and small cities that feel far from congested by tourism (at least for now).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Speaking of open roads, a road-trip or self-drive, is one of the most popular ways to explore Hokkaido. Which kind of makes sense given that their tourism infrastructure is still somewhat nascent. Having your own set of wheels will also allow you to explore the island at your own pace, which is good, because it simply wouldn’t feel right to be in a rush in a place so relaxed and at ease. Most of the existing itineraries I found suggested circumnavigating the island in 10 days but we managed to do it in 8 days. This felt about right for us, although I can certainly see how I might have filled an extra day or two if I had them. I’ve outlined my itinerary in detail below but you can also skip to the end for alternative itinerary suggestions if you’re interested in expediting or extending the length of your own Hokkaido road-trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pt3 pb2 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Before You Go&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There are a few housekeeping items you’ll need to take care of before arriving in Hokkaido if you plan to drive yourself around the island. First things first, you’ll need to get an international driver’s license. It’s basically just a multi-language translation of your existing driver’s license that is acceptable in most countries. Just fill out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aaa.com/vacation/idpf.html&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt; and bring the required documents to your nearest AAA location and you can usually get your IDL within 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Next, the car rental. We went with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aaa.com/vacation/idpf.html&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;OTS&lt;/a&gt; because it was cheaper than the alternatives and the web-site was a lot easier to use to reserve a car in advance. You’ll also have the option to reserve an ETC card, which allows you to use all the expressways in Hokkaido. We decided not to get the ETC card because it was pretty expensive and with some slight speeding we still managed to make good time to get from place to place, plus there are some free sections of the expressway that we were able to use. Your car will probably also come equipped with a GPS but I highly recommend referring to Google Maps for your driving directions instead. The GPS time estimates were really exaggerated— up to twice as long as what Google Maps accurately estimated, especially if you don’t have an ETC card and are avoiding toll roads. &lt;span class=&quot;b&quot;&gt; For hotels and lodging, refer to my other post about &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;lodging in Hokkaido&lt;/a&gt; that corresponds with this itinerary.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 1: Arrive in Hakodate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/HKD_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Hakodate is a sleepy little bay-side town that I’m dubbing the San Francisco of Hokkaido (you heard it here first, folks). It’s hilly, foggy, and has its share of Victorian buildings— a result of Hakodate being Japan’s first port open to foreign trade after the Convention of Kanagawa in 1854.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
You can reach Hakodate from Honshu via the recently opened Shinkansen station, or hop on an hour long flight. We opted for a round-trip flight from Tokyo to Hakodate which ended up being about the same price as train tickets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Once you're there; drive to the top of &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/JT6BhxM1nZu&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Mt. Hakodate&lt;/a&gt; at night for a stunning view of the city and surrounding bay. Take a stroll around the star-shaped &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/WUriky9CsoC2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Goryokaku Fort&lt;/a&gt; and learn about its’s role and history in the Boshin War. Eat at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/CDUifJUYyTo&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Lucky Pierrot&lt;/a&gt;, a colorful clown-themed local chain that serves some dope burgers and spaghetti. Eat breakfast at the Morning Seafood Market, and indulge in all the ice-cream your heart desires— Hokkaido's known for their dairy! My first cone was at a simple stand in the hills of Hakodate, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.co.th/search?tbm=lcl&amp;amp;q=%E6%89%8B%E4%BD%9C%E3%82%8A%E3%82%BD%E3%83%95%E3%83%88%E5%A4%A7%E4%B8%89%E5%9D%82&amp;amp;rflfq=1&amp;amp;num=20&amp;amp;stick=H4sIAAAAAAAAAB1Ru00DQRSUE0R-iGAjl_D-814XtGAhIwJLRqYx6qIKZpE2OM3efPf5ab2oSk2YmnqNVSER6wivDJGcdrSlmAxBUQSiO8p9ZqRBfrnIpOikF1wsWtfhrZkd6dJZqY3eotaAB93GrUU7ex2tKNKnLEMFMFOKisoMo2zjdjXxWkfCDUzozBxBKRD0QfFbbIrKvfORn9TTkNBAlnVlOdFQxqIgdjZvlNs6oCXVVuPCU4oNsrWOsJh0WKiHyzqqWvhfNQnKAYBt5RjKSdKTRYNJ2IqYD5fhrsYtOcd_K0mD7Kk1qwa82Wh7O40yyAo-BXRvTSeuMcGyjNXQn9Pp9_T6dr1_3a7ny-37fv6-Xh7vn-eP--MPFGB0QsoBAAA&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwjs8euXv_ncAhVMXCsKHaKoCvUQjHIwGHoECAgQSA&amp;amp;rldimm=11069421213692667574&amp;amp;tbs=lrf:,lf:1#rlfi=hd:;si:10937000227201825274;mv:!1m3!1d47460.1348473532!2d140.73820099999998!3d41.80668899999999!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i183!2i383!4f13.1&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;手作りソフト 大三坂&lt;/a&gt;. On the other end of the ice-cream spectrum was the decadent strawberry ice-cream parfait at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/Rm7VsrDEF4x&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;glacier c’est chouette&lt;/a&gt; near Goryokaku Park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/HKD_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/HKD_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Hakodate is also one of Hokkaido’s three “ramen cities”. Each city has its own style of ramen that it’s famous for. Here, it’s Shio Ramen. However, keep in mind that restaurants close surprisingly early in Hakodate. We had a hard time finding anywhere open past 8 p.m. and ended up at a ramen joint next door to a few gentlemen’s clubs just to get our fix!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 2: Hakodate → Otaru → Sapporo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/SAP_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Hit up Hakodate’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/FnyUsD99tVM2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Morning Seafood Market&lt;/a&gt; on your way out of the city— it’ll help guarantee an early start. We tried some fresh uni from a crowded stand and then picked a restaurant next door to the indoor market for some chirashi for breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/HKD_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/OTA_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We decided to take a slight detour and hit up the town of Otaru on the way to Sapporo. Both cities are about a four hour drive from Hakodate, with Otaru being about an hour west of Sapporo. Otaru is most known for it’s small canal by the coast, which is particularly pretty when the water reflects back a sunny, cloudless day. We also stopped by &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/TcFLdnPfSDB2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Naruto Honten&lt;/a&gt; to fuel up on some fried chicken before getting back in the car and heading to Sapporo in time to make our hotel’s happy hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/OTA_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/HKD_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Sapporo is Hokkaido’s largest city and in retrospect, it would’ve been nice to add on an extra day to our trip here so that we could experience more of the city’s food scene, or try Sapporo’s famous Miso ramen. We saved our one night in the city to hit up the obligatory &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/YhE26yWo2HA2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Sapporo Beer Garden&lt;/a&gt;. In addition to tasting limited edition beers you can only find in the city, the beer hall is also known for its lamb barbecue dishes. They’ll even give you plastic bags to cover your clothes and bags so you don’t take the smell of grilled meat home with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 3: Sapporo → Nakafurano&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/FUR_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
It takes about three hours to drive from Sapporo to Nakafurano, but I highly recommend making a slight detour to &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/nRhGQDUHwcQ2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Makomanai Takino Cemetery&lt;/a&gt;. Here you’ll find a stunning, giant stone Buddha enshrined by a minimalist cement circle designed by Tadao Ando. We got to see more of Ando’s work on Naoshima and Teshima but this temple may be my favorite of all his spaces that I’ve experienced. From afar you can see the Buddha’s head just peeking out from a hill surrounded by seasonal lavender blooms. It was like no other temple I’ve seen before, and a nice sneak preview of the flower fields we’d soon see in Nakafurano.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/SAP_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/SAP_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Taking the detour to Makomanai will also help you arrive in Nakafurano later in the afternoon. Here’s why that’s a good idea— Furano is going to be the most crowded and tourist-packed place you’ll visit in Hokkaido. &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/46ntAfiP7GM2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Farm Tomita&lt;/a&gt;, which has free admission, is the spot to view epic flower fields and rows upon rows of local lavender in July. By getting there as close to its closing at 6:00pm you can get your golden hour pics and also arrive just as the last of the mega-tour-buses are pulling out of the parking lot. There’s one large lavender field right off the road that most people will be taking photos at. However, if you walk up the left side of that field there’s a little opening that will lead you to another, more secluded field for more optimum photo taking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/FUR_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/FUR_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Next door to Farm Tomita is &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/t3gxML4kqw22&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Tomita Melon House&lt;/a&gt;, a complex that exclusively sells the town’s famous sweet melons and derivative treats. Melon House closes at 5:30pm so I recommend hitting that up first (and taking advantage of their parking lot). Purchase a slice, half, or whole melon and pair it with some ice-cream, but save room for the famous Lavender ice-cream at Farm Tomita as well. By the time you’re done at Melon House, the crowds at Farm Tomita should be thinning out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/FUR_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns pb4 pb5-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/FUR_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pt4-ns pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 4: Nakafurano → Biei → Daisetsuzan National Park → Asahikawa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/DAI_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you get an early start to your day, swing by &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/d5emQ7mtVKx&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Choei Lavender Farm&lt;/a&gt; in the morning. This hillside farm has a ski-lift that is only operational during lavender season (June—August). A couple yen gets you a round-trip to the top where you can get a beautiful view of the surrounding farmlands and sneak in a couple more photos in a less-crowded area than Farm Tomita.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
A half-hour drive northeast will get you to &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/ufpU2fVtkdx&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Shirogane Blue Pond&lt;/a&gt;, also known as Blue Pond Biei. It’s a mysterious light turquoise pool of water that was actually man-made to protect the nearby town of Biei from lava flow due to the nearby volcanoes. However, it’s bright blue color was totally unintentional— a quirk due to minerals suspended in the water. The Blue Pond is another hot tourist spot so don’t be surprised to find it packed, but you really don’t need more than twenty minutes here to walk around the pond before getting back on the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/BIE_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
From the blue pond, continue driving northeast for forty-five minutes to &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/e4hYfA2CdHR2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Mt. Asahi-dake&lt;/a&gt;, the tallest mountain in Daisetsuzan National Park. Park the your car and take the somewhat pricey (~$30 roundtrip) but worth-it ropeway to the peak for a brisk hike around one of the most stunning and surreal landscapes you’ll ever see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/DAI_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/DAI_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/DAI_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/DAI_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Daisetsuzan was originally called Kamuimintara (カムイミンタラ) by the Ainu, the indigenous people of Japan. This roughly translates to “garden of the gods” or “garden where the gods play”, which seems fitting for a terrain that consists of vibrant alpine flora, snowy white glaciers and their glassy melting ponds, and billowing stacks of smoke sprouting off an active volcano. Mt. Olympus is real y’all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/DAI_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/ASA_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
After you’re done at Asahi-dake drive about an hour north to the city of Asahikawa for the night. Asahikawa is another one of Hokkaido’s ramen cities so treat yourself to a bowl of shoyu ramen. We went to &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/JKEFJSD95y52&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Aoba Ramen Shop&lt;/a&gt; which had the friendliest staff, and even ran into some other Thai tourists there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 5: Asahikawa → Kitami → Abashiri → Koshimizu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/KIT_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This is where your route may alter depending on the season. In the winter it may be more worthwhile to head northeast to Monbetsu for ice-breaking tours on the Sea of Okhotsk, or drive by Takinoue in the spring to see the pink moss phlox in bloom. Since it was summer we headed directly east through Daisetsuzan National Park. Admittedly, the scenery in the summer is a bit monotonous with unending rows of green trees, but in the autumn seasons when the leaves turn colors it’s supposed to be quite breathtaking. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
After driving for about three hours we stopped in Kitami to check out Kitakitsune Farm, a small sanctuary for northern foxes. Pulling up to the “farm” it admittedly looked run-down and a bit sketchy. Especially with all the souvenirs and trinkets on sale at the entrance. We paid about 500 yen to go to the large yard in the back where the foxes roam. There were no park attendants out that day so it was just us and the foxes, with no fences nor cages between us. Most of the foxes were sleeping (maybe we arrived at naptime) but the ones that were awake seemed very calm, albeit cautious. You aren’t supposed to pet them and they will kinda stop near you until realizing you don’t have food and then trot away. It was still pretty cool to see the foxes up close— they are ridiculously cute. It was a nice break to stretch our feet, although we were also lucky that we spotted some foxes in the wild crossing the road a few other times on our road trip, so Kitakitsune is definitely not a “must-see” if you want to catch a glimpse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/KIT_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/KIT_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We then headed to the eastern coast near Abashiri, where there are supposedly blooming patches of wildflowers. I can’t say we saw too many wildflowers but I did see a nice variety of wildlife here: a funky caterpillar, an eagle, some horses, and a ghostly white and red moth. There’s also a short little trail that leads to the beach, where you can look out at the fog folding over the Sea of Okhotsk and know that Russia is somewhere on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/ABA_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/ABA_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/ABA_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/ABA_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/ABA_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We ended up in the little town of Koshimizu for the night, to stay at this adorable Airbnb I wrote about extensively in &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;my post on lodging in Hokkaido!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 6: Koshimizu → Akan National Park → Kushiro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/AKA_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We got a late start on day six because we decided to stop by the potato festival in Koshimizu before leaving town. From there we backtracked about forty-five minutes to Bihoro and then drove south down the Bihoro Pass. At the end of the pass is an observatory, marking the entrance to Akan National Park with breathtaking views of Lake Kussharo. Even on a windy, cloudy day, the water still appeared so bright and blue, and the rolling hills so vividly green. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/KOS_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/AKA_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
After visiting the observatory we made a game-time decision to go see Kaminoko Blue Pond on the west side of the park. In retrospect, we could’ve headed directly to Kaminoko from Koshimizu and saved some time, but oh well! The Kaminoko pond is blue in a different way than Blue Pond Biei. The water is much clearer and a deep, cerulean color. We couldn’t really find an explanation on why it was blue, just that the water at the center of the pond is so cold that the fallen trees in there never rot. Access to this pond requires driving slowly through a dirt path so it’s a bit secluded and there were very few other people there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/AKA_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
After Kaminoko we drove back towards the center of the park and stopped by Mt. Io, an active volcano that constantly emits steam and liquid sulphur. The light brown peaks are stained with a bright, sulphuric yellow and a wash of pastel greys and pinks that make it look quite beautiful. That beauty is somewhat tempered by the air smelling faintly like a bag of farts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/AKA_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/AKA_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/AKA_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
From Mt. Io we drove further west to Lake Akan. Due to our late start we arrived at Lake Akan a little too late to really do anything unfortunately. We were able to run into the museum by the lake five minutes before it closed to use the restroom and check out their very small marimo collection. Marimo are these cute little moss balls that grow plentifully in Lake Akan, and have become somewhat of a mascot for the region. If we had gotten there earlier I would’ve have taken a boat trip to the observatory on an island in the middle of the lake where they have an even larger collection of marimo. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Instead we took a quick walk around a short trail by the lake and then got back in the car and headed south towards Kushiro for the night. We ate dinner at this kitschy Japanese western restaurant called &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/4zdyMqN5ZiH2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Green Parlor&lt;/a&gt; where I had a really delicious sweet spaghetti with meat sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 7: Kushiro → Noboribetsu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/MOM_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This was the most brutal of driving days. There’s not really much between the city of Kushiro in the east and Noboribetsu in the west so we were looking at a solid six hour drive. If we had more time it would’ve been nice to check out even more wildlife in Kushiro, which is known for its wetlands, but with such a lengthy drive ahead of us we wanted to get to the hot-spring town of Noboribetsu early enough to enjoy as much of the onsen as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
About four hours into our drive, a little bit before Chitose, we stopped for a snack at &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/k5fZ6L8UCrn&quot;&gt;Momo Cafe&lt;/a&gt;, tucked into the trees off a slow road. Supposedly if you’re lucky you might catch a glimpse of a chipmunk on the cafe grounds but instead we just saw many bright yellow dragonflies. We ordered a chocolate-banana tart and some drinks and were treated to a complimentary slice of a mini-berry tart. Both tarts were delicious and the perfect hit of sugar to keep us going for the rest of the drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/MOM_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/MOM_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
When we finally arrived at our onsen in Noboribetsu we emailed changed into our robes and headed down to the baths for a pre-dinner soak. If you don’t want to stay in a hotel with an onsen, there are many bath houses you can simply drop into for a small fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Day 8: Noboribetsu → Lake Tōya → Hakodate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/NOBO_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
After a generous breakfast at the onsen we headed out from Noboribetsu. With a whole day ahead of us and the only goal being to get back to Hakodate by night, we planned to spend some time in Jigokudani Hell Valley, an area with steaming sulphur pools and hot springs just outside of Noboribetsu. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/NOBO_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/NOBO_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
A short but sweaty hike up and over a mountain in Jigokudani will lead you to &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/i2ReEv57HH12&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Oyunuma Pond&lt;/a&gt;, a large sulfurous hot spring pond with surface temperatures of 50 degrees celsius. You may even spot a snake going up the mountain trail like I did and then run off screaming down the other side. Walking a little further around the pond will lead you down a path to a heated sulfur river that is used as a public foot bath. Fair warning though, the water is HOT— in the summer I could only stand to have my feet in there for no more than a minute or so before pulling out and letting them cool off on the surface. I can only imagine how great the toasty temperatures would feel in the late fall or winter seasons though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/NOBO_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/NOBO_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
There is also a bear park located near Jigokudani where you can supposedly feed the bears but I’ve read mixed reviews regarding the well-being of the animals and we decided that we would rather spend the time at Lake Toya on the way back to Hakodate. We grabbed some bento-style lunches from “Hot Chef”, a food stand inside the Hokkaido-based gas station chain Seicomart and decided to eat by the peaceful lake. Like many of the lakes in Hokkaido, Lake Toya is a caldera lake with a cute little island in the middle. The view is really quite peaceful and lush. If you stay late enough there are fireworks set off by the lake in the summertime, however we were exhausted and wanted to get back to Hakodate in time for a relaxing dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/TOY_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido-2/TOY_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
A few hours later we were back in Hakodate and at the conclusion of our trip. We wanted to get back to Hakodate the day before flying out so that we weren’t in a rush or at the mercy of traffic trying to catch a late flight on the same day as departing Noboribetsu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb5-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The next morning we dropped our car off at the OTS lot in the airport and a shuttle dropped us off at our terminal. A little over an hour later we were back in Tokyo, reeling from all the wonderful memories of summer in Hokkaido, and a burgeoning curiosity to experience this island in the cooler months of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;w-100 tc mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/qUeUtmogOqE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pt4-ns pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Alternative Itineraries&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;f5&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;3—4 Days&lt;/b&gt;: Fly Into Chitose Airport → Noboribetsu → Sapporo → Furano (+ Otaru or Niseko)
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;f5&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;5—6 Days&lt;/b&gt;: Noboribetsu → Sapporo → Furano  → Biei + Daisetsuzan National Park (+ Hakodate or Asahikawa)
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;f5&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;10+ Days&lt;/b&gt;: Our 8 Day Itinerary + Rishiri-Rebun National Park + Monbetsu (in the winter) + Kushiro Wetlands + Shiretoko National Park
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pt4-ns pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Additional Resources&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Innbox: Hokkaido Road Trip Lodging Guige&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lonelyplanet.com/japan/hokkaido/travel-tips-and-articles/hokkaido-road-trip-exploring-japans-wild-north/40625c8c-8a11-5710-a052-1479d2762b3d&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Lonely Planet: Hokkaido Road Trip Guide&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jayndee.com/self-drive-hokkaido-road-trip-itinerary/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Jayndee: Hokkaido Road Trip in 10 Days&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.milesofhappiness.com/blog/summer-road-trip-in-hokkaido#.W3o7IJMzZ-U&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Miles of Happiness: 4 Day Itinerary Guide&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.phenomenalglobe.com/hokkaido-road-trip-itinerary/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Phenomenal Globe: 10 Day Itinerary&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our travel guides:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/san-luis-obispo-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/slo/SLO_Header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/san-luis-obispo-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Why not SLO down in San Luis Obispo for your next weekend trip?&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/why-right-now-is-actually-a-good-and-helpful-time-to-visit-mexico-city/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/mexicocity/MexicoCity_Header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/why-right-now-is-actually-a-good-and-helpful-time-to-visit-mexico-city/&quot;&gt;Why right now is actually a good and most helpful time to visit Mexico City&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">By Sabrina Majeed</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What Hokkaido taught me about hospitality</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What Hokkaido taught me about hospitality" /><published>2018-08-12T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-08-12T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/what-hokkaido-taught-me-about-hospitality/">&lt;div class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;By&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot;&gt;Sabrina Majeed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/hokkaidolodging_thumb.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Let me cut to the chase and say that Japan is one of the more challenging places I've booked lodging in. Japan is known for being an expensive country and thus that desired combination of affordability and intentional, sophisticated design is elusive.
Where you'd expect clean lines, natural textures, and minimalism, you'll more often find the interior design of hotels and guesthouses to reflect the compact, pastel plastic aesthetic of the 90s. At least in Tokyo the density of Airbnbs has been able to fill the gap, but the farther out you travel in Japan, the slimmer the pickings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Enter Hokkaido, which is pretty far out. It's Japan's northernmost island and quite remote. Tourism hasn't quite hit it big yet the way it has other parts of the country. I'll write more about &lt;i&gt;why&lt;/i&gt; we decided to visit Hokkaido later but for now just know that outside of Sapporo, the island's biggest city, the boutique hotel game is non-existent. You'll be hard-pressed to find trendy, modern design staples like gold accents and mid-century modern furniture but in their absence you may find something better: authenticity, warmth, and charm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;During our week-long road trip across Hokkaido we stayed at eight different guesthouses, hostels, and hotels. Though they varied in size, they were consistent in their incredible hospitality. Friendly hosts who make you feel less like a traveler and more like an old friend who's come home. Sleeping in their beds I simply felt safe, surrounded by this comforting, familial feeling. It took me back to the times as a kid I'd visited extended family— the way a grandmother or aunt would have prepared a humble but cozy room just for you and then sit you down at the dining table to lavish you with a home-cooked meal. It was a pleasant reminder that when you strip away the interior design and get back to basics, what truly makes a &quot;great place to stay&quot; is the host, and the way people take care of one another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Thank you, Hokkaido, for the meals and the memories. For the way you welcomed us home each night and saw us off on our journey each morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb5&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;I've included a mini-review of each of the eight places we stayed during our road trip. I hope that should you ever find yourself in Hokkaido, this guide will help you find a safe and special place to lay down your head at night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Hakodate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/jp/pension-jokura.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Pension Jokura&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$90/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/jokura_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/jokura_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/jokura_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/jokura_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/jokura_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Pensions, which are quite popular in Japan, are simply another name for a guesthouse and offer meals in addition to room and board. Pension Jokura was the first place we stayed in Hokkaido and such a wonderful introduction to the warm, cozy style of hospitality we’d find all over the island. The interior is filled with the kind of whimsical details that any Ghibli fan would appreciate. We stayed in a private western style room with two twin beds, and never had any issue with timing or access to the pristine shared bathroom and showers during our one night stay. We opted not to purchase breakfast at the pension the following morning so we could check out the city’s famous morning seafood market instead. The pension is run by a retirement-age couple— it was the husband’s longtime dream, although we never actually met him. We did meet the wife and their adorable mini poodle, who was one of the friendliest hosts we had the pleasure of staying with in Hokkaido.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Guest rooms at Pension Jokura are located on the second floor, accessible only by stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/jp/small-town-hostel-hakodate.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Small Town Hostel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$92/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/smalltown_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/smalltown_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/smalltown_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/smalltown_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/smalltown_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/smalltown_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We stayed at Small Town Hostel on our last night in Hokkaido, in which we returned to Hakodate to return our rental car and catch our return flight back to Tokyo. As soon as we pulled up outside I was smitten by the vintage exterior and even more charmed by the building’s well designed interior— including the tiny kitchen of my dreams. We stayed in a private room with a double bed which was quite small and cozy, but okay for us for a night stay considering the spacious common areas we had access to. We had dinner in the restaurant which shares a building with the hostel, a Brooklyn-themed haunt with an eerily accurate recreation of New York classics like a burger and chicken n’ rice dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Access to Small Town Hostel requires ascending a short flight of steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Sapporo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=1622626&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Unwind Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$172/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/unwind_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/unwind_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/unwind_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/unwind_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/unwind_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/unwind_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/unwind_7.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Unwind Hotel was one of our two splurges of the trip, and the only true hotel we stayed at. However, in a city like Sapporo— Hokkaido’s largest— you take advantage of the variety in lodging and range of options when you can. Unwind markets itself as a lodge-style hotel and thus you’ll find cozy, camping themed amenities laced throughout your experience there. There’s the firepit on the rooftop, the bar with a complimentary wine happy hour, free pajamas for use during your stay, and the highlight— a breakfast-in-bed basket delivered to your room in adorable Stanley thermos jugs. I can only imagine how magical this place feels in the actual winter season. We were also pleasantly surprised to learn that Unwind is owned and operated by Japanese hospitality company, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.global-agents.co.jp/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Global Agents&lt;/a&gt;, the team behind two of the hotels we stayed at in Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Unwind Hotel has step-free access and elevators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Furano&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://furanohostel.sakura.ne.jp/english.htm&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Furano Hostel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$31/Person/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/furano_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/furano_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/furano_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/furano_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/furano_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/furano_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;

Furano in the summer season stands out as the island’s most packed little town. The respite you’ll feel from crowds of tourists across the rest of Hokkaido comes to an end as you make your way to view the world-famous flower fields and taste those sweet Nakafurano melons. Naturally, as a result of the high season lodging in the area is notoriously expensive and books up several months in advance. But if you’re lucky you can score a coveted spot at Furano Hostel. The iconic red building was handmade and operated by an older couple. The space has relaxing outdoor spaces, accessible bathrooms, and the shared hostel rooms only accommodate four people each so you don’t need to worry about being packed in. You also won’t find the stereotypical party hostel crowd here, but a mix of solo-travellers, couples, and multi-generational families who are all respectful of one another’s privacy. In the morning we had an unassuming yet delicious breakfast sandwich before setting off for our next destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Furano Hostel is very accessible with a paved, step-free entrance, wide doorways, ground floor beds, and an accessible bathrooms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Asahikawa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/jp/mimatsuso-ryokan.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Mimatsuso Ryokan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$102/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_7.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimat_8.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Mimatsuso is a curious little guesthouse located in the thick of downtown Asahikawa. The building’s teal exterior is like a homing beacon as you pull up and just one of many examples of the ryokan’s unique aesthetic personality. I’ll admit, I initially wanted to judge a book by its cover and was skeptical of Mimatsuso’s stellar reviews based on its somewhat dated exterior, but like many of the guesthouses we stayed at, Mimatsuso is also run by a kind, older couple that truly embody the spirit of hospitality. They took extra care in helping carry our bags to our room (despite my protests) and making sure we were able to access their free parking spot. We booked the ryokan’s spacious private bedroom with living room that can accommodate up to three people, which made for a nice dual live/work space. In the evenings I took up the host on her offer of trying on a kimono with her assistance, and in the morning we enjoyed a vast and varied breakfast spread— perhaps my favorite breakfast out of those provided at places we stayed in Hokkaido.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The guestrooms at Mimatsuso Ryokan are all on the second floor and require going up a flight of stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Koshimizu (near Bihoro &amp;amp; Abashiri)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/7164771&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Tida House ティダハウス&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$114/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/tida_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/tida_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/tida_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/tida_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/tida_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/tida_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Of all the places we stayed, I probably had the lowest expectations for Tida House. You see, I just really needed to find a place for us to spend the night in one of the most remote areas of Hokkaido we’d be traversing during our road trip, where the pickings were slim to say the least. It seemed like a miracle that I found this highly rated Airbnb, even if it was located in a small town an extra thirty minutes out of the way. The thing about low expectations though is that they can easily be surpassed and well, in the end Tida House was not only my favorite place we stayed in Hokkaido, but perhaps one of my top Airbnb experiences &lt;i&gt;ever&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Tida House, as it’s called, is a straw-bale home that the host, Yuya, built himself with the help of his friends. The mud-walls which are insulated with hay keep the home cool in the summer months and warm during the winter. The place itself is absolutely whimsical— there are so many charming little nooks and details, like a light switch hiding behind a tiny tree-shaped door. There are also peace signs a plenty strewn throughout the property— big ones and small ones alike. Finding them all would be a fun game to play. The cozy home is also sort of an aesthetic amalgamation of the host’s travels throughout Asia. The pan-Asian thing can easily come across tacky or surface level in the wrong hands but here it feels genuine and truly appreciative. In that vein, Yuya also owns a pan-Asian cafe located on the same lot as Tida House, however the cafe was currently closed for the season when we visited as Yuya is working on building a larger guesthouse during the summer months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
As the cherry on top of our unexpected ice-cream sundae, Yuya informed us that on the day we checked out there was going to be a town festival and that his cafe would have a booth there. We were excited to get to try his cooking after all, and also learn more about this little town. Turns out the festival was in celebration of Koshimizu’s prime produce— potatoes. We had some amazing fried potatoes that were golden and sweet, cementing Koshimizu as one of the highlights of our trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There is an unpaved path to the entrance of Tida House, in addition to a few steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Kushiro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/jp/kushiro-guesthouse-cooka-doodle-doo.en.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Guesthouse Cocka-Doodle-Doo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$63/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/cocka_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/cocka_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/cocka_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/cocka_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
After a day spent driving around and exploring Akan National Park, we needed somewhere to spend the night in preparation for a long drive back across to the west side of the island. While I was initially looking to stay near Lake Akan, the options were all limited to relatively price-y lake resorts and onsens. Knowing our next stop was going to be the more famous onsen-town of Noboribetsu anyway, I ended up finding this humble little guesthouse about thirty minutes south of Lake Akan, towards the city of Kushiro. Cock-a-doodle-doo (or Koke Kokko in Japanese) is a relatively new guesthouse that’s been open for about a year and is run by two young women about our age— quite the contrast from the other guesthouses we stayed in. They converted a fifty year old building into the inn, which is quite simple and minimal in its decor but charming nonetheless. We stayed in a private, traditional Japanese style room with tatami mats, though they also have hostel-style shared rooms available for even less. The guesthouse also has an array of interesting crafts and vintage items for sale. I ended up buying a vintage set of Nintendo’s hanafuda playing cards from them for about $6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The guestrooms at Cocka-Doodle-Doo are all on the second floor and require going up a flight of stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f2 mt4 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Noboribetsu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=442365&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Morinoyu Sanseikan Ryokan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;$275/Night (Including Meals)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimo_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimo_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimo_5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimo_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimo_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/hokkaido/mimo_6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Noboribetsu was the perfect place to close out our roadtrip, soaking our tired bodies in a warm bath at this famous onsen town. Morinoyu was the most expensive place we stayed in Hokkaido, in part because of the intense dinner and breakfast spreads we added on to our reservation in addition to the room and board. When I was looking for a place to stay in Noboribetsu it came down to Morinoyu Sanseikan or the larger, more famous onsen-hotel of Dai-ichi Takimotokan. What pushed me over the edge was reading reviews that pointed out that due to Morinoyu’s more intimate size, no organized tours ever stay there (in contrast to Dai-ichi which is practically made to accomodate large groups) and it’s very likely that you can get the bath all to yourself in the summer season— and indeed, I did, otherwise it would’ve been impossible to sneak a photo of the gorgeous outdoor bath. Sitting out there in solace, taking in the contrast of the cold night air on my face and toasty waters everywhere else was simply put, an amazing feeling which put me totally at peace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The dinner and breakfast spreads at Morinoyu were freaking huge— filled with things that were both delicious and things that challenged me. I consider myself a very open-minded and adventurous eater but there’s only so many raw, slippery things I can eat in one sitting. I really appreciate the opportunity to be able to try &lt;i&gt;so many&lt;/i&gt; new things though, and though the meals are pricey they were well worth it to me for their portion size and authenticity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There are a few short steps to the entrance of Morinoyu, however there are ramps inside for access to the upper floors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pt4 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I hope that you found this guide to lodging in Hokkaido helpful. If you appreciate our recommendations, please use our provided links to book your lodging in Hokkaido— or anywhere else in the world! The Innbox may collect a small commission from each booking at no extra cost to you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">By Sabrina Majeed</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: Busaba Ayutthaya in Ayutthaya, Thailand</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/busaba-ayutthaya-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: Busaba Ayutthaya in Ayutthaya, Thailand" /><published>2018-08-05T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-08-05T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/busaba-ayutthaya-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/busaba-ayutthaya-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; June 18 — 19, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $54/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;dib&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sabrinasans/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Sabrina&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; Three Companions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/busaba/00.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hid=4489474&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Busaba Ayutthaya's&lt;/a&gt; minimalist white-washed facade provides a stunning contrast against the eroded red and brown ruins that the region is known for. The crisp, cool whites combined with lush greenery make the hostel feel kind of like an oasis in the middle of this hot, dry city which once served as Thailand's capital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The building is a fifty-year old traditional Thai house which has been recently renovated by its owners. In the spirit of family homes popular in Central Thailand, a central zone or common area is surrounded by individual homes or bedrooms, serving as a space for members of the family to come together. In fact, you'll find many thoughtfully curated gathering spaces across the grounds, which is what makes the Busaba's transition from home into hostel feel so seamless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We arrived in Ayutthaya after an hour's train ride from Bangkok. From the train station in Ayutthaya we negotiated with a tuk tuk driver and hopped in for about a ten minute ride to the hotel. We actually overshot the hotel a little bit at first and had to turn around— we were looking for the iconic white buildings we saw in the hotel photos but the hotel itself as actually tucked away behind their cafe and storefront which sits on the main road that circles Ayutthaya Park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/01.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/02.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Checking-in was fairly smooth and the staff provided us with a well-designed map of the area as well as 20% off coupons for their cafes. Before heading to our room or other parts of the grounds we were asked to leave our shoes in a cubby in a room off the lobby and switch into a pair of provided flip flops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While Busaba’s best value is probably it’s gorgeous shared rooms, I booked the site’s only two private rooms for our group which consisted of two couples. The two private rooms are located on the building’s upper floor, behind a charming little outdoor patio.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/03.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/04.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The rooms are very simple yet elegant. The white vertical paneling on the walls and golden fixtures on the outlets and lamps kind of made me feel like I was staying in a spacious train compartment. My favorite feature was probably the windows on both sides of the room, which you can easily open to get a breeze going— although it was &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; hot when we visited. To that point, the air conditioning in the room was very powerful. The room is also furnished with some adorable objects which are also for sale at Busaba’s associated cafes. I ended up buying one of the mugs that was provided in our room.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/05.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/07.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/08.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/06.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Bathroom&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The bathroom situation was a bit surprising to me. When I had booked the two private rooms I had assumed they also came with private bathrooms. In reality, there is one private bathroom that is shared between the two private rooms. Which wasn’t so bad since my entire party had booked up both of the property’s private rooms, but four people sharing one bathroom is a bit of stretch. I actually ended up just going downstairs and using the property’s shared hostel-style bathrooms most of the time and I didn’t mind at all because they were actually impeccably clean, well-designed, and felt a little more airy and relaxing than our designated private bathroom which had no windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fn center mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Shared bathroom. Showers and toilets are located to the left and right, and separated by gender.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Common Areas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The Busaba has many common areas to hang out as a group— from the patio on the second floor to the covered dining area which overlooks the small creek behind the hostel, as well as the lobby. The lobby looks a bit more refined than the usual hostel common room, with spacious cushioned benches and coffee tables set up for playing board games— &lt;i&gt;or&lt;/i&gt; even better, Nintendo Switch. You can borrow the console and four controllers for free and hook it up to the television in the lobby and play all kinds of party games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/15.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Breakfast is included with your stay at Busaba. During check-in you’ll be given a choice between three entrees, two of which are pork congee and pork rice porridge— the distinction between those was confusing even to us. Turns out the rice porridge is more of a rice soup. Breakfast is served on the dining veranda behind the hotel, with unlimited toast, cereal, coffee and tea provided as well. To be honest it wasn’t the most memorable meal and you will definitely need to add a lot of seasoning to your congee or porridge, but it will suffice to get you started for a day of touring the archaeological sites in the city, or hold you over for a morning train ride back to Bangkok.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/17.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/18.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Left: Iced tea and frappes at Busaba Cafe; Right: Lunch at Somtom Sukunya.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I was more impressed with Busaba’s cafes which have an impressive variety of cold drinks that are a perfect reprieve from the city’s dry heat. We visited both the cafe next to the hotel as well as their sister cafe beside two of the temples in the park. The sister cafe is actually just kitty-corner to one of the most amazing Thai restaurants I’ve eaten at in all of Thailand, a lovely little place called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.co.th/maps/place/Somtum+Sukunya/@14.356765,100.569191,15z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0xba286d9d30bc3012!8m2!3d14.356765!4d100.569191&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;Somtum Sukunya&lt;/a&gt;. I highly recommend you take &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; your meals there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;While our interactions with the staff were limited during our one-night stay, everyone we met was extremely friendly and nice. One of the staff members even kept the lobby open late for us when we stayed up playing video games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Another perk that Busaba provides are bicycles for guests to use, free of charge. If biking isn’t your speed they will also help arrange a motorbike rental and have the vehicles dropped off at the hotel. I highly recommend using either a bicycle or motorbike to efficiently get around the city and view the many different historical sites at your own speed.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
On that note, the Busaba is very conveniently located just outside Ayutthaya Park which houses the majority of the temples and ruins in the city. Once we had our motorbikes it probably took us less than five minutes to get to Wat Maha That where you can buy an entrance pass to all of the temples in the park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/22.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/20.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/21.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/19.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
However, aside from the hotel’s own cafe which is better for breakfast/lunch, there aren’t many restaurants or dinner options directly around the hotel. I’d definitely recommend grabbing food either at the night market or on the east side of the park before heading back to the hotel. Luckily with our 24 hour motorbike rental, it was easy for us to get in and out of the hotel to grab food. There was also a convenience store about a block or two away from the hotel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Unfortunately, access to Busaba’s private rooms require climbing one flight of stairs. However, there are hostel-style rooms on the ground floor and the shared bathrooms on the ground floor are accessible as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/busaba/23.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I highly recommend the Busaba for those on a budget who still want to stay somewhere clean, comfortable, and well designed while visiting Ayutthaya. While you could do the trip in one day by leaving and returning to Bangkok in the early morning and late evening, for a reasonable price you could stay overnight and explore the city at a more leisurely pace by staying at Busaba Ayutthaya. As far as hostels go, Busaba is probably one of the most elegant we’ve ever stayed in. It’s also a great choice for groups since you can split up into the private rooms or book an entire hostel-style bunk room for yourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;
Please use our link below to book at Busaba Ayutthaya (or any other hotel!). The InnBox may collect a small share of sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hid=4489474&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ Busaba Ayutthaya&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our hotel reviews:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/hotel-1-busan-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/hotel1/04.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/hotel-1-busan-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: Hotel 1 in Busan, South Korea&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/my-love-inn-lijiang-review/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/myloveinn/1.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/my-love-inn-lijiang-review/&quot;&gt;Hotel Review: My Love Inn in Lijiang, China&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: June 18 — 19, 2018 Rate: $54/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Three Companions</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How I learned to travel like a Type-B in Corsica, France</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-like-a-type-b-corsica-france/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I learned to travel like a Type-B in Corsica, France" /><published>2018-07-28T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-07-28T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-like-a-type-b-corsica-france</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-like-a-type-b-corsica-france/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;By&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/typeb/15.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;“Where’s Corsica?”&lt;/i&gt; most people asked me. &lt;i&gt;“Is it a country?”&lt;/i&gt; No, but fair question as it’s a bit off the beaten path when you think of traveling in Europe, especially for non-Europeans. Most of you are probably more familiar with the beaches of Southern France à la Nice, Marseille, Cannes and the like. Chic shopping along cobblestoned streets, fancy beach clubs with rows of orange parasols, and everyone decked out in white linen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Corsica is actually quite a large island in the Mediterranean off the coast of France, close to Italy. The official language is French, but Corsica is steeped in its own native culture with about 50% of the population conversational in the local Corsican language in addition to French and Italian. Its claim to fame is being the birthplace of Napoléon Bonaparte! But that is not why you go to Corsica...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fn center mb3 mb4-ns tc&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/01.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The impetus to visit Corsica came mostly from a wedding invitation for a dear Swiss friend. When my friends and I were deciding where to pre-game this wedding, we were torn between the South of France and Corsica itself. We ended up choosing to spend our time in Corsica as we would likely not have a reason to return, but we soon discovered that there are one million reasons to return again, and again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Corsica is truly a pearl of the Mediterranean. You like hiking and awesome rock formations? Got it. Secluded white sand beaches and crystal clear water? More beaches than you can count. French food? Oh &lt;i&gt;girl&lt;/i&gt;, Corsica will hook you up with impeccable cheese and charcuterie, not to mention the local wine! You like wine? Cool, go visit the vineyards along the coast. I’m telling you, Corsica has everything and if you want to plan a summer road trip in Europe, go to Corsica, it will not disappoint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/02.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/03.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Left: Lavezzi Islands, right: Bonifacio.&lt;/i&gt; Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
One of the greatest lessons Corsica taught me is how to enjoy the basics of life. Coming from New York myself, it's so easy to get caught up in the hustle and bustle that is city life. Corsica forces you to take it slow and notice the scenery. Since you’re not constantly trying to hit famous landmarks, you can take your time and follow your whims. There is no FOMO here. This is where I shed the trappings of a Type A lifestyle and learned to travel like I’m Type B. Let me explain...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
About a week before my friends and I set out on a road trip around Corsica, we contemplated our lack of pre-planning:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fn center mb3 mb4-ns tc&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/04.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
For those of you who need an Urban Dictionary rundown:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;def.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Type A&lt;/b&gt;: relating to, characteristic of, or having a personality that is marked by being impatient, outgoing, ambitious, rigidly organized, anxious, proactive, and concerned with time management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;def.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;b&gt;Type B&lt;/b&gt;: a personality type characterized as easygoing and thought to have low susceptibility to stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
And so it went, four Type A’s embarked on a journey where they would try to act against every Type A impulse they had. &lt;i&gt;Restaurant reservations?&lt;/i&gt; Wing it. &lt;i&gt;But, don’t we need to hit every beach mentioned on Google?&lt;/i&gt; Let’s drive around and see how we feel. &lt;i&gt;WHAT DO WE DO FOR LUNCH??!?!?!&lt;/i&gt; Well, this, every day:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fn center mb2 tc&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/05.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
For those of you who are uber planners, I’m not knocking it. Certainly a degree of planning is very helpful or else you might end up homeless and stuck at a bus stop with the inability to communicate with locals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
However, I’m advocating for you to take a step back and think about the type of trip you want to have holistically. Do you want to experience the place in its natural form as a local might experience it? If so, for optimal enjoyment and relaxation I recommend keeping your planning to a minimum and go with your gut in the moment. No decision should be difficult when choosing between all good things.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
All roads lead to &lt;i&gt;bliss&lt;/i&gt;.  
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Here are some of the tactics I picked up that will help you travel like you’re Type B, even if it only lasts as long as your vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Start with an MVP (Minimum Viable &lt;i&gt;Plan&lt;/i&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
To truly embrace the Type B lifestyle, you don’t want to plan an exhaustive itinerary because ultimately this will stress you out and undermine your ability to live in the moment since your primary concern will be checking off items on a list. Lists are for your day job——ditch them on vacation.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Do&lt;/i&gt; reserve where you are going to stay ahead of time. By settling on your accommodations, the only thing you need to be concerned about is arriving there in time to sleep. While there are loads of beautiful properties dotting the island, we chose to stay as central as possible so that we would minimize the driving time to get into town and could just walk out our door ready to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The main towns we stayed in along the way were Bastia, Porto Vecchio, Bonifacio, and Ajaccio. In order to see one of the notable UNESCO sites around the island, Piana, we picked a random town to stay in called Cargèse not because it is known for anything in particular, but because it was convenient. This ended up being one of the most valuable decisions we made. We were able to experience small town life by having breakfast at a local café and making some great connections with the locals who were eager to proffer us with advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/00.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I made two food reservations for the entire trip, but didn’t end up making it to either. Once when we arrived in Bastia, our hotel called to make a reservation at one of the best places in town. Instead we got lost and landed at a quiet spot with young locals, which had a stunning view of the port at night. The other reservation was lunch at a vineyard in Sartène which we skipped because we were enjoying ourselves at the beach and couldn’t pull ourselves away. Don’t fret about missing your reservation, Corsica isn’t that kind of place. If you go in low season, you will not have trouble finding a place to chow down on a Corsican stew or fresh seafood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/06.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Settle on your non-negotiables&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;You should do some basic research to figure out the highlights for your destination. This will at least give you some direction when planning where to stay and your route. My favorite sources for pre-trip research is &lt;a href=&quot;https://wikitravel.org/en/Main_Page&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;WikiTravel&lt;/a&gt;, any articles I can find in reputable food or travel magazines,  recommendations from friends, and of course &lt;a href=&quot;theinnbox.co&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;The InnBox&lt;/a&gt;. Your list doesn’t need to be a mile long, but it helps to know what the popular sites are and to figure out what you want to do once you get there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;If you’re traveling with a group of friends, it’s ok to stray a little back into Type A territory before the trip in order to make sure everyone is okay with the game plan. We created a Google Doc where we threw in ideas from our cursory research and then had a quick phone call to regroup and make sure we’re all on the same page about our must-dos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Another bit of advice for group travel: download a bill splitting app like &lt;a href=&quot;https://secure.splitwise.com/#/dashboard&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Splitwise&lt;/a&gt;. This will take all the stress away from constantly splitting bills and taking out money from expensive ATMs. Just keep your receipts, then upload them to the app when you have some downtime, it will automatically settle bills so you don’t have to do the nasty math. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Make decisions the morning of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Instead of staying up late planning the next day’s itinerary, wake up, grab breakfast on the go and figure out what you feel like doing. By not making precious decisions ahead of time, you have the freedom to change around your schedule. One morning we decided to head to the beach first thing since we anticipated rain later in the day——this was the right call since we ended up getting stuck in a Corsican delicacy shop during a thunderstorm as opposed to an open coastline. We ended up befriending the shop owners who gave us some free white wine cookies, delicious!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/07.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Corsican jam at a shop in Porto Vecchio.&lt;/i&gt; Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Roll with the unexpected&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;As with most trips, something WILL go wrong. A true Type B won’t let it stress them out because, well, they will figure out a Plan B on the spot! One of our musketeers was delayed an entire day meeting us in Corsica, so two of us all of a sudden had a free day to explore. This ended up being one of my favorite days of the trip. We asked the front desk at our hotel what towns would be worth exploring and she told us about this medieval town called Nonza about halfway up the Cap Corse peninsula. The ride was absolutely stunning, winding roads through canopies of green trees and cows grazing in fields. Finally we stumbled upon this beautiful town, overlooking a black sand beach—very dramatic. We had some Aperol Spritzes with a view, and hiked down to the beach, then headed back to Bastia to pick up our friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/08.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Nonza.&lt;/i&gt; Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Had we planned our trip to a T, we would have missed out on this gem, which brings me to my next point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Lean on the locals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Remember that random town we stayed in, Cargèse? We did not have anything planned for dinner upon our 10pm arrival, so we asked the old man who ran the hotel where we should go. He recommended a local spot by the harbor, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurant_Review-g663644-d2213362-Reviews-Le_Cabanon_de_Charlotte-Cargese_Corse_du_Sud_Corsica.html&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Le Cabanon de Charlotte.&lt;/a&gt; Located at the bottom of a long winding pitch black road with a sky full of stars, we finally arrived at this beautiful restaurant and were greeted by the kindest soul, Charlotte herself. Her parents owned her namesake restaurant and passed it down to her. She loves Corsica and shared her love for it with us. After ordering two phenomenal bottles of Corsican red wine and a whole fish for each person, she briefed us on what to do the next day after we visited Piana. Whenever someone gives me a written note full of recommendations I cherish it more than any souvenir. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Le Cabanon de Charlotte.&lt;/i&gt; Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Of course, befriending the locals also means you get some perks. With Charlotte it meant 13 scoops of ice cream and one slice of each cake off the menu. Keep your eyes peeled for Chestnut cakes, a local favorite on the island.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Rent your own transportation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Whatever the primary mode of transportation is at your destination, take it. Be it a car, Vespa, or motorbike, being able to get around on your own terms at your own pace will allow you to be as flexible as you can be. Stop along the road for that photo-op, hunny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/12.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Road side photo-op.&lt;/i&gt; Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There are two primary benefits of having your own ride. You don’t have to stick to schedules for public transportation, which can rudely interrupt your Type B non-itinerary. You will also never be hangry as you can always pull over and pick up some snacks. Our eyes were constantly peeled for fresh fruit stands and grocery stores to stock up on Rosé which we leisurely sipped every night on our hotel balcony while getting ready for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/typeb/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Fresh fruit and vegetable stand in Corsica.&lt;/i&gt; Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Arielle Benedek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Word to the wise, make sure you budget for a rental car on a European island as there are limited numbers of automatic vehicles available. They are also...expensive, approximately 5x more expensive, so learn to drive manual if you get the chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
There are all sorts of vacations you could take; cities like Paris, beaches like Tulum, safaris in Tanzania, and you can travel like you’re Type B in each of them. All you need is just the minimum amount of planning, a willingness to go with the flow, and maybe some friends on the same page. A Corsican road trip is an ideal first trip to get your feet wet with this lifestyle. For a run down of the places we hit on our road trip and some that we didn’t (because we’re Type B) check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/d/u/1/viewer?mid=1Bb6xH2XcF5DAe47Z8Fu5u9KePYI_MjgJ&amp;amp;ll=42.06801644910503%2C9.006174650000048&amp;amp;z=8&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;this Google map.&lt;/a&gt; As a little bonus, here’s the ultimate &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/user/zloubert/playlist/2DhH9IJK5E48VxagSL2Mnv?si=ZIjGNO4tRr2ElsHE4Vrsfg&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Corsican Roadtrip Playlist&lt;/a&gt; we swore by every day. Make the trip your own, there’s so much to discover.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/user/zloubert/playlist/2DhH9IJK5E48VxagSL2Mnv&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;380&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; allow=&quot;encrypted-media&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt2 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;About Arielle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Arielle works in Product by day and spends her free time exploring her own city, New York, and planning trips to off the beaten path locales before they become the hot new thing. She’s a sucker for French pastries and ethnic eats. Her next trips include Copenhagen for some summertime hygge and Bolivian salt flats for some 4x4 adventuring. You can follow her travels &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/therelzoe/&quot;&gt;on Instagram.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our travel posts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/how-to-see-it-all-while-traveling/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/seeitall/00.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/how-to-see-it-all-while-traveling/&quot;&gt;How I make time to 'see it all' when I travel&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/200-dollars-airbnb-new-york-city/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('http://theinnbox.co/images/nycair/Splash.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/200-dollars-airbnb-new-york-city/&quot;&gt;Here's what $200 on Airbnb can get you in New York City&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Arielle Benedek</name></author><summary type="html">By Arielle Benedek</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Your travel guide to The Algarve, Portugal: where to stay and what to do.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/the-algarve-portugal-travel-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your travel guide to The Algarve, Portugal: where to stay and what to do." /><published>2018-07-19T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-07-19T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-algarve-portugal-travel-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/the-algarve-portugal-travel-guide/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;By&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/algarve/00.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Algarve is a region in the southernmost part of Portugal and home to some seriously beautiful beaches, of which the town of Lagos is particularly famous for. The waters are cool and clear,  and the coast is dotted with massive, majestic rock formations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you’re the type to be highly active while traveling then... Lagos &lt;i&gt;isn’t&lt;/i&gt; the place to do that. It is best appreciated by taking things slow and enjoying life, whether you’re staying two nights or an entire week.  The best time to go is mid-May, when the tourism hasn’t kicked in yet and the weather is optimal: cool at night but warm enough during the day to lay on the beach and get a sweet tan. It’s quiet around this time which will give you many more opportunities to explore uninterrupted, with no lines to wait on.  You will find that everything in the Algarve and Portugal in general is extremely affordable, which is one of the reasons why it’s such a popular destination for solo travelers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/pt/vivenda-solmar.en-gb.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Vivenda Solmar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $74/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/01.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/02.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Left photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/pt/vivenda-solmar.en-gb.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Booking.com&lt;/a&gt;; right photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Vivenda Solmar is a rarity and the photos do not do it justice. It’s located in a residential area - so it feels like your own home - with close proximity to a beach, while being ultra affordable. I was greeted by a kind host who offered some delicious port wine to sip on while she checked us in.  The room was massive with a balcony that made for some sick views of the ocean.  The cool, dry breeze allowed us to leave the windows open and enjoy the fresh air.  It’s located walking distance to Praia Porto de Mos, which is less crowded and just as beautiful as the other beaches in Lagos.  It’s also away from the city center so it feels remote and peaceful.  The ocean view is simply breathtaking and you will be overcome with emotion when watching the sunset and rise. I highly recommend buying your own groceries and making breakfast in the mornings to enjoy with the view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Vivenda Solmar is a three story building with rooms on the first floor. The entrance is paved, however there are no elevators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/pt/vila-gale-lagos.en-gb.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Vila Gale Lagos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/04.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/03.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/pt/vila-gale-lagos.en-gb.html?aid=1452227&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Booking.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If I had wanted to really splurge and treat myself in Lagos, Vila Gale Lagos would have been my top choice.  It’s large, modern, and right by the beach with an epic outdoor pool.  If you’re into resorts, convenience, amenities, and 5 star service, this is the place to stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Vila Gale Lagos does have facilities for guests with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Things to do in The Algarve&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/d/u/0/viewer?mid=1KXcSxqKeFfZ2UCEWLvs2V6crE5_iOS3N&amp;amp;ll=37.08938703537126%2C-8.67025000000001&amp;amp;z=15&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Go beach hopping&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/20.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/05.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/21.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/19.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Lagos has a handful of beaches and the best way to explore them is to go on a coastal walking tour.  You can even skip the coast and walk along the sand, through grottos and caves.   There’s a lot of nooks and crannies to explore and the view of it all is simply breathtaking.  If you’re looking for something more secluded I highly recommend Praia do Pinhão.  Getting there requires descending steep stairs that have no handrail and kind of end abruptly.  You’ll end up having to rock climb down a little bit but it’s not too bad and totally worth it.  Whichever praia you go to, there is always a more secluded and secret area that requires a small trek to discover, but is ultimately rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Pro-tip:&lt;/i&gt; if you see nude sunbathers, it means you hit the secret garden of beaches!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurant_Review-g189117-d1791275-Reviews-Cervejaria_Ferradura_Lagos-Lagos_Faro_District_Algarve.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Eat at Cervejaria Ferradura&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/06.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/07.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This is where we ended up when my friend and I were trying to find a place to eat on our first night.  It was May and not yet tourist season so a lot of places were closed, and boy, was that a blessing in disguise.  Otherwise, we wouldn’t have found this gem: &lt;i&gt;Cervejaria Ferradura&lt;/i&gt;.  It’s a small brewery with bar seating only (12 ~ 14 people max) and no menu.  There’s a glass display in the front full of prepared and fresh food and you just kinda point at what you want to eat. This worked out great because we didn’t speak enough Portugese to communicate with the owners and instead had to literally communicate through food. The food was incredible - simple but with so much flavor; fresh, and made only better by the house white wine on tap.  Who knew bread and cheese could be &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; good?  I can definitely say, this was one of the most memorable meals of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Take a boat ride around Ponta de Piedade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/08.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/09.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I tend to avoid tourist traps or stereotypical touristy activities — like paying exorbitant fees for gondola rides or riding the tram in Lisbon.  The same &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; be said for boat rides at Ponta de Piedade but this is one tourist attraction that’s worth every penny.  It wasn’t THAT expensive but it was expensive compared to everything else I did in Lagos (20 euro per person).  And you know what?  I had a blast.  The boat ride was about 20 minutes and included some exhilarating moments like trying to squeeze into caves so small, we had to duck down in our boats to pass through.  The payoff to that was exploring the cave interiors intimately, and seeing water in a color I didn’t even think was possible.  Our guide spoke a small amount of English, but it was more than enough to effectively share his knowledge of the rock formations.  By boat (kayak or motor) is the only way you can view these natural wonders up close. Afterwards we climbed back up the cliffs and enjoyed an ice cold refreshing Sagres Radler, a lemon-y beer type drink.  So simple but such a great way to end our trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Eat your weight in seafood (and potatoes)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
It’s fresh, it’s plentiful, it’s cheap, and it’s what Lagos does best.  I can honestly say, no matter where you go, it’s gonna be good. A couple I met recommended &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/Restaurante+O+Camilo/@37.086889,-8.6697266,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0xcc3afe433395edac?sa=X&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwia5J7GwJrcAhWOON8KHeTPBwUQ_BIwDnoECAoQCw&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;O Camilo&lt;/a&gt; which is located by the stairway leading down to Praia do Camilo. It was a bit bougie, but had breathtaking views.  I ordered the mackerel and clams which was un-surprisingly delicious, fresh, and cheap.  The potatoes that came with it were just as delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;O Camilo&lt;/i&gt; - Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
For dinner, we checked out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/Os+Lambertos/@37.1003456,-8.6788408,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x5590e4237bb81ab3?sa=X&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwif4IKawZrcAhWJdd8KHX17AuQQ_BIwCnoECAoQCw&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Os Lambertos&lt;/a&gt; - a favorite among locals and taxi drivers, known for their down home cooking and traditional Portuguese dishes.  Surprisingly, the non-seafood dish - Portuguese steak with potatoes - was the star.  And the potatoes were damn good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Os Lambertos&lt;/i&gt; - Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/Campimar+Restaurante+Bar/@37.0857124,-8.6874175,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x3c0211806d7437d5?sa=X&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwiXrrjKwZrcAhVPPN8KHQUxCmoQ_BIwC3oECAoQCw&quot;&gt;Campimar Restaurant Bar&lt;/a&gt; is located right on Porto de Mós and was my first (and very delicious) meal in Lagos.  I would recommend getting some sort of fresh fish - the flavors are so clean, it’s tender, and never overcooked.  I ordered the sea bream but let me tell you, those potatoes were flavorful AF here too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Campimar Restaurant Bar&lt;/i&gt; - Photo via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Take a surf lesson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/15.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you’re not too ‘busy’ taking holiday in Lagos, I highly recommend taking surf lessons.  Portugal in general is known to be a surfer’s haven, with some of the best waves in the world.  And there’s nothing like spending the whole day riding then having an ice cold beer afterwards. I decided to holiday like a European this trip, so skipped out on lessons.  But if you’re interested, &lt;a href=&quot;http://thesurfexperience.eu/&quot;&gt;The Surf Experience&lt;/a&gt; is a great place to start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Talk to the locals&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
As beautiful as Lagos is, the most beautiful thing about this town were the locals.  They are kind and generous with their knowledge of the area.  To get the most out of your trip here, talk to them, ask questions, and listen. You can learn so much even just from speaking with cab drivers. And I wouldn’t have discovered Os Lambertos had I not asked the locals specifically where they like to eat (as opposed to where I should eat).  It will help you view Lagos through the eyes of its inhabitants and ultimately give you a truly immersive experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Take a day trip to Faro&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/17.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/algarve/18.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Photos via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Joanne Yae&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I’ll be honest.  I had no expectations for Faro.  From my research it seemed there was really nothing to do - it was just a town.  Thankfully my assumptions were off.  Faro is a town, but it’s meant to be explored and appreciated from an architectural and design standpoint.  The lines, colors, and buildings of Faro are a work of art.  Life is simple and you take things slow. Above are some things I came across on my walk around Faro.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3 pb4-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Train is the best way to get here from Lagos, and it is an 1hr 40 min ride.  Once you’ve arrived, you’ll be in the heart of the town and can start exploring right away.  Faro also has an airport, which is the only one in the Algarve, so you can fly in from anywhere else in Portugal easily.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;About Joanne&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Joanne is a developer and surfer girl wannabe based in NYC with a serious skill for getting the perfect tan.  She enjoys seafood, travel photography, and flights paid with points.  Her upcoming travel plans include Hawaii in August and New Zealand in November, with lots of Miami in between. You can follow her travels on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, her &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/jyae7777/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Travel Photo Blog&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;yae.joanne@gmail.com&quot;&gt;contact her directly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our travel guides:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/bariloche/bariloche_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Your travel guide to Bariloche, Argentina: where to stay and what to do.&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/granada-nicaragua-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/granada/NICA_HEADER.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/granada-nicaragua-travel-guide/&quot;&gt;Your travel guide to Granada, Nicaragua: where to stay and what to do.&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Joanne Yae</name></author><summary type="html">By Joanne Yae</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vacation like the protagonist in a romantic film with 8 affordable movie set alternatives.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-like-a-romantic-film-protagonist/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vacation like the protagonist in a romantic film with 8 affordable movie set alternatives." /><published>2018-07-08T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-07-08T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-like-a-romantic-film-protagonist</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-like-a-romantic-film-protagonist/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;../images/moviespots/romanticmovieheader.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;If you've been on Netflix lately, you've probably noticed that the romantic comedy is having a comeback (I'm talking about &lt;i&gt;Set It Up&lt;/i&gt;, which is so so good). It's a good thing too because I, for one, am starving for the tastefully decorated apartments and wanderlust-inducing locales that the genre (along with it's parent category, romance) often sweeps us away to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Recently, CN Traveller &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cntraveler.com/story/you-can-rent-the-villa-from-under-the-tuscan-sun?sp=&amp;amp;weekend_photo=2&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;wrote about the gorgeous villa from &lt;i&gt;Under The Tuscan Sun&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Turns out you can stay there for real— as long as you've got around twenty friends or family members who are willing to split the $2,391/night fee. For those of us who mostly travel with our partners, our friends, or god forbid— &lt;i&gt;alone&lt;/i&gt;, it's all a bit out of reach. Which is ironic considering that the movie is literally about Diane Lane traveling to Italy &lt;i&gt;by herself&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;So, I thought it would be fun to try to find more affordable approximations of popular romance homes and hotels. Depending on how realistic the original film was, some of these are upgrades. Others are admittedly not as fabulous, but it's not too bad for under $300/night to travel or live like a romantic lead...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;1. &lt;i&gt;Under The Tuscan Sun&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/9676103?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=329621833&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;La Villa Scoula&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $118/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/tuscan_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/tuscan_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/tuscan_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/tuscan_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
In &lt;i&gt;Under the Tuscan Sun&lt;/i&gt; Diane Lane plays a divorcée who spontaneously buys and renovates an Italian villa, and forms all kinds of meaningful relationships in the process. The real life &quot;Villa Bramasole&quot; is actually the expansive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.luxuryretreats.com/vacation-rentals/italy/tuscany/cortona/villa-laura-112033&quot;&gt;Villa Laura&lt;/a&gt;, which as I mentioned before, costs a pretty penny. The good news is that yellow tuscan villas are all over Airbnb, and a lot less expensive. My favorite of the options is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/9676103?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=329621833&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot;&gt;Villa La Scuola&lt;/a&gt; at $118 a night. Not only does it have the characteristic yellow and green exterior, the theme is brought inside with bright lemony kitchens and sage accents, plus curved archways separating the rooms. There's even a gorgeous plant covered garden and patio that would be perfect for hosting a small wedding... just sayin'.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Villa La Scuola has step-free access, a brightly lit and flat path to the front door, along with a wide doorway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;2. &lt;i&gt;Mamma Mia!&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/2863822&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Mirabilia Skopelos&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $42/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/mammamia_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/mammamia_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/mammamia_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/mammamia_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The movie musical that launched a thousand trips to Greece. In the movie, Meryl Streep's character Donna runs the dreamy Hotel Bella Donna, perched at the top of a cliff on the Greek island of Skopelos. Unfortunately there is no &quot;real&quot; Hotel Bella Donna as it was just a set, though there is the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.holidayislands.com/skopelos/houses/pyrgos/&quot;&gt;&quot;Hotel Pyros&quot;&lt;/a&gt; located nearby, where Meryl Streep would rest between filming. But while stunning in its own way, Pyros' stony interiors doesn't quite invoke the bright, airy and optimistic charm of the Bella Donna. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/2863822?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=329621833&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot;&gt;This Airbnb&lt;/a&gt; on Skopelos at $42/night however hits all the right notes: bright white walls with pops of blue, perfectly lived in furniture that looks like it came out of an &lt;i&gt;Anthropologie&lt;/i&gt; catalog, and shuttered windows you can dramatically throw open and sing your heart out of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb has a well-lit path to its entrance but relies on stairs to access bedrooms on the upper floors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;3. &lt;i&gt;Leap Year&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/16828159&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Geoghegans Old Stone Cottage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $67/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/leapyear_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/leapyear_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/leapyear_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/leapyear_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
In &lt;i&gt;Leap Year&lt;/i&gt;, Amy Adams hires a surly Irishman played by Matthew Goode to drive her across the country so she can propose to her boyfriend in Dublin. Naturally, hijinks and sexual tension ensue. In one of the more memorable scenes, Adams and Goode have to share a tiny bed in a cozy countryside cottage, as they must convince the conservative innkeepers that they're married. You know, classic rom-com problems. While the film's bed and breakfast was a set, you can find many similar homes in Tipperary, Ireland— like &lt;a href=&quot;Geoghegans Old Stone Cottage&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;this Airbnb&lt;/a&gt; for $67/night. It's got a fire place, cozy leather couches and red accents, plus the bed is honestly an upgrade from the one in the film. Even better, you'd have the place all to yourself— no nosy innkeepers in sight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This entire Airbnb unit is a single story, however its entrance is unpaved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;4. &lt;i&gt;The Notebook&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14995365&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Historical Southern Home in Paradise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/notebook_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/notebook_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/notebook_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/notebook_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
In &lt;i&gt;The Notebook&lt;/i&gt;, Ryan Gosling builds Rachel McAdams a house even though they haven't been together in years. Sorry, it's not &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; a house— it's her dream home, a symbol of his love, and an entire generation's unrealistic expectations. The actual house that was used in the film is Martin's Point Plantation and is a private residence on Wadmalaw Island in South Carolina. The owners have apparently had to deal with many fans wandering onto their property, much to their annoyance. Instead of trespassing you can find a little southern hospitality at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14995365&quot;&gt;this Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;, also located on Wadmalaw Island. Similar to the original it has white clapboard siding, shuttered windows, a gorgeous porch perfect for painting on, and lots of wooden furniture and accents. You can fit up to ten guests here for $200/night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;In order to access this home you must climb stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;5. &lt;i&gt;In The Mood For Love&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=3494&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Luxe Manor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $125/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/moodforlove_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/moodforlove_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/moodforlove_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/moodforlove_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;i&gt;In The Mood For Love&lt;/i&gt; follows two neighbors in 1960's Hong Kong who both suspect their spouses are having an affair— with each other. So much of the film is dominated by punchy colors and patterns; deep reds, oranges, and splashes of purple. Much of it also takes place in homes and hotel rooms. The film was actually mostly shot in Bangkok, and of the few scenes shot in Hong Kong, many of the locations have changed dramatically since  the movie was released in 2000. That's what makes finding an approximate Airbnb somewhat difficult. The set design for &lt;i&gt;In The Mood For Love&lt;/i&gt; is very representative of its time and today, bold graphic wallpaper has been replaced with minimalism and large glass windows. However, you can find the best of both worlds— that's the film's signature color and patterns with today's modern luxury— at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.agoda.com/partners/partnersearch.aspx?pcs=1&amp;amp;cid=1801609&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;hid=3494&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Luxe Manor&lt;/a&gt; hotel in the Kowloon area of Hong Kong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Luxe Manor has in-room accessibility and roll-in showers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;6. &lt;i&gt;Notting Hill&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/10088507&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Beautifully Designed 2 Bedroom Near Notting Hill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $215/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/nottinghill_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/nottinghill_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/nottinghill_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/nottinghill_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
In &lt;i&gt;Notting Hill&lt;/i&gt; Hugh Grant plays Will, the owner of a travel bookstore (be still my heart) who meets and forms a relationship with a famous actress played by Julia Roberts. Several pivotal scenes take place in Will's Notting Hill flat— which looks like a charming yet realistically lived-in bachelor pad. The apartment's exterior is known for its iconic blue door, which in real life belonged to the film's screenwriter. Finding an apartment that looks like Will's today is a bit challenging, as it such a product of its time and that time was the late 90's. It's an aesthetic that most of Notting Hill's tasteful Airbnb hosts seem to want to avoid today. However, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/10088507&quot;&gt;this unit&lt;/a&gt; for $215/night comes close. It has a very similar layout to Will's apartment with a thin kitchen and large glass windows at the end of the room for tons of light. It's even got a blue door like the original, and blue walls on the interior to suit the theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;There are a few small steps from the apartment's entryway into the kitchen, but we recommended reaching out directly to the Airbnb host for more accessibility information..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;7. &lt;i&gt;The Lake House&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.candlewoodcabins.com/meadowhouse&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Meadow House&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $195/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/lakehouse_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/lakehouse_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/lakehouse_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/lakehouse_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The eponymous lake house is probably one of my favorite movie homes of all time. They custom-built the steel and glass home from scratch for the film after weeks of location scouting around Chicago and failing to find an existing building that met their needs. The architects claim that the house was inspired by 1960's glass houses, the Regency period, as well as greenhouses. They were able to film the movie at Maple Lake near Chicago under the agreement that the lake be returned to its prior condition after filming wrapped— which meant demolishing the lake house, much to everyone's disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;For my affordable alternative I may have cheated a little. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.candlewoodcabins.com/meadowhouse&quot;&gt;Candlewood Cabins' Meadow House&lt;/a&gt; is a gorgeous square glass building, raised slightly above the ground with rustic yet minimal wooden interiors, just like the one from the movie. No, it's not on a lake, but it is right by a river and a pond. But to be fair, even an actual film crew and professional location scouts couldn't find something like this on an actual lake. Candlewood Cabins is about 3.5 hours out of Chicago, across the Wisconsin border. The Meadow House's rates are currently $195/night but will go up to $245 in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Access to Meadow House requires ascending a flight of stairs from an unpaved road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;8. &lt;i&gt;Nights in Rodanthe&lt;/i&gt; — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/13980800&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Octopus' Garden Cottage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $115/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/rodanthe_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb2&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/rodanthe_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/rodanthe_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/moviespots/rodanthe_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Turns out, Diane Lane characters have really great— and really expensive— taste in where to stay. In &lt;i&gt;Nights in Rodanthe&lt;/i&gt; Lane's character is operating her friend's bed and breakfast, an iconic and towering building right on the seashore in North Carolina's outer banks, with shingled siding and beachy blue interiors. The original building was built in the 1980s and was condemned and deemed unsafe by local officials shortly after filming. A year after the film was released a couple that claim to be huge fans of the movie purchased the inn and actually had the entire building physically relocated to a safer beachfront location. The inn is now known as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sunrealtync.com/outer-banks/rodanthe-nc-rentals/oceanfront/r-51
&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Inn at Rodanthe&lt;/a&gt; and you can stay there for $1995/week, with a one week minimum stay. Or, you can make your way a little further up the banks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/13980800&quot;&gt;this Airbnb in Kill Devil Hills&lt;/a&gt; for $115/night. While you're staying there you can just imagine that they remade the film today except with Diane Lane as a millennial tending to her friend's two-bedroom Airbnb and it'll all make sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Access to this Airbnb requires ascending a flight of stairs off of an unpaved path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;BRB going to rewatch all of these movies now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>