<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-14T18:44:06+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">The InnBox</title><subtitle>The InnBox is a weekly newsletter featuring unique, affordable places and spaces for busy folks who need a break.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Your travel guide to Tromsø, Norway: where to stay and what to do.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tromso-travel-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your travel guide to Tromsø, Norway: where to stay and what to do." /><published>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tromso-travel-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tromso-travel-guide/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/baschtelt/10782896243/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/tromso/tromso_header.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I’ve heard that Tromsø is beautiful in the summer, it mainly draws visitors in the colder months because it is one of the best places in the world to view the Aurora Borealis, or northern lights. That’s certainly what brought me to this arctic destination— so I didn’t expect to fall in love with the city for a whole bunch of other reasons. Of all the cities I visited in Norway, Tromsø was my favorite. The locals were so incredibly friendly, the food was amazing, and it had such a laid-back, cozy atmosphere. If I could describe it in a few words I might call it a metropolitan fishing village.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We certainly have lots to say about chasing the northern lights, but first let’s talk about where to stay when you head up north.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver i mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for February 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tromsø’s hospitality scene seems nascent compared to larger Norwegian cities like Oslo and Bergen. The Airbnb inventory left something to be desired and there are few if any independently run hotels— especially if you want to be located near the city center. In fact, this is one of the few times our top recommendations include hotels that are a part of a larger chain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travelers &amp;amp; the budget conscious — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/no/comfort-xpress-tromso.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Comfort Hotel Xpress Tromsø&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $136/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/comforthotel_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/comforthotel_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comfort Hotel Xpress is part of Scandinavian chain Nordic Choice Hotels, which is a franchise of American-owned Choice Hotels, which operates Comfort Inn &amp;amp; Suites in the US. But this isn’t your momma’s Comfort  hotel. After spending days of research trying to find a place to stay I ultimately decided to stay at Comfort Hotel because of its location, positive reviews, and the price— since Tromso was the last leg of my trip and Norway is expensive, I really wanted to cut costs here. Honestly, I went into this with low expectations but found myself pleasantly surprised by this Comfort Hotel outpost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, they offer room rates specifically for single travelers. Which is great because as a solo-traveller I hate paying more for space I won’t use. The hotel is centrally located in the town center and walking distance to every single attraction. Besides my trip from the airport I didn’t take a single taxi here which also helped with my budget. Lastly, as a little cherry on top the hotel lobby has a well-stocked deli stand with grab-and-go items and drinks like coffee and wine available for purchase, which was super convenient when I didn’t feel like going outside in the cold. Check-in and check-out is also done via a tablet in the lobby for minimal human interaction, if that’s a thing you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d be lying if I said I didn’t pay attention the interior design of the places I stay at. I do, and sometimes I find that the aesthetics of these modern boutique hotel chains &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; be a bit tacky— a little IKEA but with all the leftover green and orange furniture no one wanted. Comfort Hotel Express was actually a step-up from that, although certainly youthful in appearance. It’s like how I imagine Hollywood would interpret what a college dormitory should look like, if that makes sense. The only downside to my stay here was the sad little view from my room of a back alley (look to the more expensive waterfront hotels for a better view) and because it was so youthful there were a couple of loud groups of students staying on my floor. Which wasn’t a huge deal for me because I’m a deep sleeper, but something to keep in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Comfort Hotel Xpress has an elevator for wheelchair access to rooms on the upper floors, as well as ground floor units.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For bibliophiles &amp;amp; friends traveling together — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bedandbooks.no/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Tromsø Bed &amp;amp; Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $95/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/bedbooks_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/bedbooks_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So admittedly this was my first choice for where to stay in Tromsø, but the small guest house sells out fast so it’s better to book this place way in advance. It’s one of the few individually owned lodging options in the city and while single rooms start at $95, the best deal is the triple room that if fully occupied comes out to a little over $50/night. Bed &amp;amp; Books is run similar to a hostel with shared bathrooms and common areas, including, you guessed it, a generous library for your perusal. My only initial hesitation to staying here was that as a solo-traveler it seemed a little farther out from the city center and I was worried about walking back at night, but having now been to Tromsø and I think the distance is actually not that far at all, and I felt fairly safe walking around at night. I would definitely try to stay here the next time I’m in town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Bed &amp;amp; Books doesn't specifically state that they are wheelchair accessible. Considering what we know of the architecture and the presence of stairs, we wouldn't recommend this spot for wheelchair users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples &amp;amp; business travelers — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/no/the-edge.en-gb.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Clarion Hotel The Edge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $216/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/clarion_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/clarion_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clarion is another brand operated by Choice Hotels, the same parent company responsible for Comfort Hotel Express. While our other suggestions are perfectly reasonable for couples, if what you’re after is romance than The Edge is a much better choice because of its location on the harbor and majestic views of the water, Arctic cathedral, and surrounding mountains. It’s the most centrally located of the options presented here and also a great choice if someone else is footing your hotel bill. The hotel’s restaurant, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kitchenandtable.se/story/&quot;&gt;Kitchen &amp;amp; Table&lt;/a&gt;, is run by Marcus Samuelsson and features dishes that combine his Scandinavian background with New York influences. Breakfast at the hotel is also included in most rates, and The Edge also offers lower rates for single travelers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The Edge has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;On Airbnbs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While there are certainly plenty of Airbnbs available, I felt like it was hard to find one that met all of my criteria without trade-offs. For one, I prefer to rent out an entire apartment for privacy and safety. Second, I only want to stay in an Airbnb where the value is better than staying in a hotel. That means I want something that is clean, well-decorated, in a good location, for &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; than I would pay for a hotel. Third, reviews matter a lot to me, again for safety reasons. So I personally found it difficult to reconcile all of these things in Tromsø. The options with more affordable rates were often private rooms and not as centrally located. Renting an entire apartment was often more expensive than the hotel rates and the few well-priced options had less than ten reviews. I think it’ll be really interesting to watch the hospitality scene in Tromsø ramp up over the next year or so— the influx of new properties on Airbnb is certainly a sign that it’s coming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; id=&quot;whattodo&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;What To Do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://enjoythearctic.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Chase the Northern Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/lights_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/lights_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what you come to Tromsø for. There's a whole industry around northern light tours and it's fascinating to me because despite being independent competitors all the tour guides essentially work together and constantly communicate with each other throughout the night so that if one person finds the lights, everyone else does too. You'll notice that the tours are often describe as northern light &quot;chases&quot; and that's because there's no guarantee you'll actually see one. But if you pay for a tour these guys will do everything possible to make sure you do. It was raining the night I went on my tour and our guide drove us three hours across the border into Finland to find us a clear patch of sky. The place we ended up, Kilpisjärvi, was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afar.com/magazine/get-intimate-with-the-aurora-borealis-in-the-finnish-wilderness?inspiration=outdoor-adventure&amp;amp;sub_inspiration=winter-sports&amp;amp;email=sabrinaymajeed%40gmail.com&amp;amp;utm_source=Sailthru&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_campaign=northern%20lights&amp;amp;utm_term=Daily%20Wander%20Newsletter&quot;&gt;recently featured in a recent article by Away&lt;/a&gt; as the best place to view the lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tours can be a little pricey (around $150 per person) and many of my friends have opted instead to rent a car and find the lights on their own. However, since I was traveling alone I felt more comfortable going on a tour and looking back on it I think the price was justified for the total experience. Most of the tours limit themselves to about 12 people, the amount that can fit into a small van. It's a really intimate experience and actually great for meeting other travelers because, at least in my case, it was a nine hour long experience. Three hours driving to find the lights, three hours camping out for them, and three hours driving back to Tromsø. The vans are equipped with high speed wifi for the long drive and the guides were incredibly knowledgable and prepared— ours brought snow suites for everyone as well as hot tea and coffee, and set up a campfire and cooked everyone reindeer hotdogs. Most of the guides are also professional photographers who can help you adjust your camera to the proper settings to capture the lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking the gas, food provided, and expertise of the guide and the cost of living in Norway, I felt like the cost of the tour was worth it in the end for me. The specific tour I went on was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g190475-d6583184-Reviews-Enjoy_the_Arctic-Tromso_Troms_Northern_Norway.html&quot;&gt;Enjoy the Artic&lt;/a&gt; with Andrei, who was amazing, but from what I understand the experience is consistent across the main tours you can find on TripAdvisor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/reindeer.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bardus.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Reindeer Ragout @ Bardus Bistro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite places I ate in all of Norway. Bardus is a cozy little gastropub with the friendliest staff (the waitress gave me tons of suggestions on things to do in Tromsø). But more importantly I had this creamy reindeer ragout with lingonberries and it was so, so good (sorry, Rudolph). They also serve beer from a local brewery in town, in small glasses which was the perfect portion size for me and also a really great way to avoid getting hammered over lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/cathedral.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ishavskatedralen.no/en/the-arctic-cathedral/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Arctic Cathedral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tromsdalen Church, a.k.a Ishavskatedralen a.k.a the Arctic Cathedral is the northernmost cathedral in the world. It's a wonderful example of Scandinavian architecture and was designed by architect Jan Inge Hovig in the 60's, with glass mosaics by Norwegian artist Victor Sparre added to the building in the 70's. The unique structure provides for excellent acoustics so many concerts are held at the cathedral. The cathedral is located across a winding bridge from Tromsø's city center. It's about a twenty minute walk across the bridge from start to finish.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.polaria.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Polaria&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/polaria.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Polaria is the world's northernmost aquarium and a great option for families with young children (although this adult still had fun by herself). The museum itself is rather small (I probably spent a little less than an hour there) but provides an interactive and educational overview of the area's marine ecology. The main attraction is an open pool with bearded seals, with a live feeding show twice a day. The architecture is also a part of the appeal and is an abstract representation of ice floes pushing up against land. Entrance fees are around $15 for adults and $8 for kids, although they do occasionally have discounted prices (the day I went entrance was 50% off).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/mathallen.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mathallentromso.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mathallen Tromsø&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mathallen may be more familiar to those who've visited the famous food hall in Oslo. This outpost is much smaller and includes a fine dining restaurant and a speciality deli that also makes for a great place to pick up gifts to take home like reindeer jerky. As for the restaurant, they offer a 4-course tasting menu for approx. $86 per person. Ingredients sold in the deli and used in the restaurant are all locally sourced across Norway.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/svalbard.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Visit Svalbard&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TBH I'm kind of kicking myself for not spending more time in Tromso, because if I could re-do my trip I would spend less time in Olso and Bergen in order to fit in a trip to Svalbard, an archipelago located a little under two hours north from Tromso by plane. Svalbard is home to the northernmost settlement with a  permanent population (meaning, not researchers). In fact, people often say there are more polar bears in Svalbard than people. In addition to polar bears there are arctic foxes, reindeer, blue whales, narwhals, and a host of other marine species. Fun fact: after Norwegians, Thais are the most populous immigrant group in Svalbard.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/cmichel67/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Christopher Michel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/bedstuy/bedstuy_header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Where to stay in Bedford-Stuyvesant for under $100 per night</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-bed-stuy-brooklyn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where to stay in Bedford-Stuyvesant for under $100 per night" /><published>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-bed-stuy-brooklyn</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-bed-stuy-brooklyn/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/baschtelt/10782896243/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bedstuy/bedstuy_header.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the thing about Bed-Stuy is, there really aren’t many hotels in the neighborhood. Which makes sense because it’s largely a residential neighborhood and not a huge business or tourist center. The dearth of hotels presents a huge opportunity to live like a local in one of the many brownstone apartments available on Airbnb. When compared to the cost of hotels in Brooklyn, this option also tends to be a lot more affordable. In fact, we originally set out to make a list of “the best” places to stay in Bed-Stuy and fortuitously all the places we chose just happened to fall under $100/night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who feel more comfortable staying in a hotel or are concerned about wheelchair accessibility, we recommend &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thebrooklynny.com/?WT.srch=1&amp;amp;WT.mc_id=PPC2P&amp;amp;DCSext.ppc_kw=the+brooklyn+hotel&amp;amp;ppc_ac=Brand&amp;amp;ppc_ag=Brand+Exact&amp;amp;ppc_mt=Exact&amp;amp;platform=c&quot;&gt;The Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt; on Atlantic, with rates starting at $110/night in February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Solo-Travellers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/15883070?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=247693292&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Homey Room&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $39/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/homey1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/homey2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests can stay in one of two available bedrooms in this light-filled apartment, which is shared with the host, Carolina, and her partner. Many reviewers remarked on how clean the apartment was, and positively commented on the amount of privacy afforded for a shared space. If you’re a solo traveller that prefers other humans around, or one who just doesn’t want to pay extra for space you won’t use, Carolina’s apartment is perfect for you and just three blocks from the nearest G train station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/1148279?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=KpNNNYLn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Family Owned &amp;amp; Operated Brownstone&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $60/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/family1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/family2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For solo-travellers who prefer having the privacy of an entire unit to themselves, look no further than Yoki’s renovated 1800’s brownstone. The apartment is full of historic touches like carved wood and stained glass. The unit is quite cozy, so while it can fit up to 3 guests, for the price we think it’s reasonable to go solo on this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Couples &amp;amp; Close Friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/6500246?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=247693292&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Brownstone Building&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $60/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/brownstone1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/brownstone2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This historic brownstone straddles the border between Bed-Stuy and its neighboring neighborhood (heh) Clinton Hill. Donovan’s apartment is not only filled with antiques and unique treasures, it’s a treasure in itself because of the shared backyard space you have access to. Any New Yorker will tell you, that’s quite the rarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/9155021?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=KpNNNYLn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Spacious &amp;amp; Luminous Room + Bath&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $89/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/spacious1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/spacious2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For couples looking for a more modern space than the traditional brownstone, there’s Linda and Dorian’s townhouse. The guest unit is located on the basement floor but couldn’t look more inviting. And they weren’t kidding about the ‘spacious’ part. The unit has high ceilings and enough room for a bed, working area, and lounging area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Families&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17339881?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=8oL8nuCP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Brownstone Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $99/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/studio1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/studio2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly this is my favorite Airbnb on the list. Michelle’s cozy brownstone studio gets gorgeous light and looks so inviting. It’s actually just fine for a couple or a solo traveller but because of the price (most expensive on this list) we think it’s the best value for a family traveling with young children. Though the studio can sleep 4, other reviewers have noted it can be a little tight for four adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14359772?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=KpNNNYLn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Comfy Home Away from Home&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $89/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/comfy1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/comfy2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A family of four or group of friends would feel totally comfortable in Pamela’s space. There are two other rooms in the apartment available for rent, making it a true guest-house. The kitchen is spacious for New York standards and many reviewers noted how clean and modern the bathroom facilities are. The other thing they noted? That Pamela is a natural born host.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/bedstuy/bedstuy_header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">10 places to feed your stomache and your soul in Bed-Stuy, Brooklyn</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 places to feed your stomache and your soul in Bed-Stuy, Brooklyn" /><published>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn/">&lt;p class=&quot;mt3&quot;&gt;This is the InnBox’s first list that’s exclusively about food and boy, is it personal. I hesitate to even say these are “the best” places to eat at in Bed-Stuy, it’s more like these are the places which I often frequented during my time living in the neighborhood (so don’t be surprised if you notice a disproportionate amount of Asian restaurants featured here). Bed-Stuy is also a very big neighborhood and many of these eateries are located on the west side, closer to where I’m based and near the Bedford-Nostrand G stop as well as the Franklin Avenue C stop.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I’m also not going to talk too much about already very popular Bed-Stuy establishments like Speedy Romeo’s, Peaches Hothouse, and Dough. These spots are all wonderful and have been featured extensively on several lists about the neighborhood’s dining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/750-myrtle-diner/554ac24b498e13945411029d&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;750 Myrtle Diner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Japanese&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/myrtle1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/myrtle2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually found this place because I was looking at nearby cafes with free wifi and their name popped up on the list. I assumed 750 Myrtle Diner was a diner in the traditional American sense but it turned out to be a lovely Japanese diner that’s only open for dinners. Their menu changes daily although fan favorites like the Pon-Kara (their take on karaage) seem to be frequently available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.molokobarnyc.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Moloko&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/moloko.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moloko is run by the team behind Dynaco, a more popular bar further south in Bed-Stuy. But unlike Dynaco, Moloko offers both drinks and food. It’s a true neighborhood bar and a great place to go for a low-key dinner with friends. They have great happy hour specials and a simple, mostly stable menu, the highlights of which are their burger and the seared tuna sandwich. It is, however, cash only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.evajeans.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eva Jean's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;New American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/evajeans1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/evajeans2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This place is literally on my block and according to Foursquare I’ve been there twelve times… which is, probably the most times I’ve ever been to any restaurant in New York. Eva Jean’s is basically my go-to for any occasion: date night, special occassions, catching up with friends, brunch, happy hour (which they dub ‘magic hour’), coffee… It’s the kind of like the room of requirement. The cuisine is New American which kind of means anything goes, and my some of my favorite dishes have been their pastrami eggs benedict and white bean soup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.swelldive.nyc/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Swell Dive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Filipino &amp;amp; Tex-Mex&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/swelldive1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/swelldive2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swell Dive serves filipino tacos and tiki-style drinks. It’s the newest venture from the owners of another Bed-Stuy establishment, Brooklyn Kolache Co. If you’re from Texas you may be putting two and two together right about now… tacos… and kolaches? Yep, they’re from Austin. And every weekend Swell Dive serves breakfast tacos until 3 p.m. They offer both classic Tex-Mex style breakfast tacos as well as Filipino breakfast tacos— I usually order one of each. When visiting in warmer weather, don’t forget to also check out their backyard patio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldakitchen.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Golda&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Mediterranean &amp;amp; American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/golda1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/golda2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually just went here last week on my neighborhood bucket-list tour and fell in love. Not only were the staff exceptionally kind and attentive, it’s hard to decide what to order from the experimental and mediterranean-inspired menu because everything looks so good. I settled on the eggplant menemen— a delicious mix of tomato sauce, eggs, saffron yogurt, and vegetables served with toast— and was not disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pilarny.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pilar Cuban Eatery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cuban&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/pilar.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pilar was actually the first restaurant I ever ate at in Bed-Stuy, long before I lived here. It’s got one of the most beautiful bars in the neighborhood, generous portions (the cuban sandwich is huge), and the best dessert— guava cheesecake. Almost all the entrees are under $20 with the exception of a seafood paella.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.captdansgoodtimetavern.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Captain Dan's Good Time Tavern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Southern &amp;amp; American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/dan.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/dan2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Affordable, southern-inspired brunch. Need I say more? I mean, technically it’s a bar so you can drink here too but honestly I’ve mostly come here when I’m nursing a hangover and desperately need fried, carb-loaded food in my stomach stat. Pretty much everything on their brunch menu is good but the best value is the chicken biscuit sandwich for around $7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/The-Civil-Service-Cafe-190890911113655/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Civil Service Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/civil1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/civil2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Civil Service is sort of my go-to weekday cafe to work from. It’s usually not too crowded (emphasis on “weekday” because the weekends are a different story), they make a great chai latte, and a mean breakfast sandwich with avocado and hot sauce. The team behind Civil Service also recently opened &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/TheTradeUnionCafe/&quot;&gt;Trade Union cafe&lt;/a&gt; on Malcolm X Blvd further east in Bed-Stuy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nostrandcafe.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nostrand Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Korean &amp;amp; American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/nostrand.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nostrand Cafe is an unpretentious and spacious coffeeshop that also serves really good, and simple Korean food. They also offer standard American breakfast and brunch fare with the option to add Bulgogi for an extra fee. Disclaimer: I’m not Korean but I think their bibimbap is pretty solid and the portions are generous. They also serve Korean-fusion items like bulgogi tacos and burritos, and the staff are always super friendly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.samuraipapabk.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samurai Papa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Japanese&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/samurai1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/samurai2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samurai Papa isn’t my favorite ramen place in New York City by any means, but it is the closest ramen spot to my apartment and it’s more than decent. They have great lunch specials, really affordable appetizers (we’re talking in the $6 and under range), and a simple ramen menu. I’ve tried both their curry ramen— yum— and their bukkake vegan tomato ramen which was less good, but I’m glad there’s an option for the vegans in the neighborhood. Samurai Papa used to be a lot emptier when it was standing-room only, but now that they’ve added seating you can expect it to be a little more crowded at dinner time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">This is the InnBox’s first list that’s exclusively about food and boy, is it personal. I hesitate to even say these are “the best” places to eat at in Bed-Stuy, it’s more like these are the places which I often frequented during my time living in the neighborhood (so don’t be surprised if you notice a disproportionate amount of Asian restaurants featured here). Bed-Stuy is also a very big neighborhood and many of these eateries are located on the west side, closer to where I’m based and near the Bedford-Nostrand G stop as well as the Franklin Avenue C stop. I’m also not going to talk too much about already very popular Bed-Stuy establishments like Speedy Romeo’s, Peaches Hothouse, and Dough. These spots are all wonderful and have been featured extensively on several lists about the neighborhood’s dining.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/austin/Austin_Header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The 7 best boutique hotels in Paris under $300</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-boutique-hotels-paris/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 7 best boutique hotels in Paris under $300" /><published>2017-11-12T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-12T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best-boutique-hotels-paris</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-boutique-hotels-paris/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/paris_header.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week we covered how Austin is the king city of Airbnbs in terms of quantity and quality. Well, you could say the same for Paris with its endless supply of top notch boutique hotels. There are an almost overwhelming amount of options, all with their own character and many at a surprisingly affordable price for a city with such an expensive reputation. We’ve narrowed down our top picks to help you find the perfect Parisian place for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver i mt4 mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for January 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For living like a local — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lespiaules.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Les Piaules&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $30/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lespiales1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lespiales2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the recent proliferation of out-of-the-box hostel chains in Europe, it’s always refreshing to come across independently owned hostels that are done well. Les Pialues is located in the up and coming neighborhood of Belleville, a bit farther from many of Paris’ main tourist attractions. The hostel features a custom designed bunk bed intended to improve and reinvent the standard hostel experience. There’s also a poppin’ bar downstairs for guests and locals alike. Shared rooms start as low as $30 and private rooms at $102.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Les Piaules is wheelchair accessible and has roll-in showers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For families — &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.astotel.com/hotel/monterosa-en/overview&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hôtel Monterosa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $133/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/monterosa1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/monterosa2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monterosa is the first hotel we’ve featured on The InnBox that’s belongs to a chain, but to be fair the chain in question, Astotel, only operates in Paris. They run 16 hotels all of which are somewhat similar in their design, highly reviewed, and kind on the budget. I personally stayed at the Monterosa and thought it had a great location, being walking distance to both Pigalle and Saint Georges metro stations. The decor is modern and clean, continental breakfast is provided, and we spent countless nights just hanging out drinking tea in the little lobby cafe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel Monterosa has an elevator but does not have facilities specifically for handicapped guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For New Yorkers at heart — &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotelpanache.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel Panache&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $143/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/panache1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/panache2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The building that houses Hotel Panache has no right angles— it’s triangular shape gives it something in common with the iconic Flatiron building in New York City, and thus that’s where Panache’s industrial designer drew her inspiration. The Flatiron was finished in 1902, so at Panache you’ll find many examples of art nouveau, the major art movement on the time. While each room is uniquely decorated (including one with this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cole-and-son.com/en/collection-fornasetti/wallpaper-77/7024/&quot;&gt;malachite wallpaper&lt;/a&gt; I’d sell my unborn child for), they all feature a custom headboard inspired by Thonet bentwood chairs. New Yorkers who’ve spent a lot of time in the Flatiron neighborhood will feel right at home here. We’ve also heard a rumor that if you are traveling with small children they will bring a miniature teepee to your room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Second and third floors are accessible by elevator and there are facilities for wheelchair users. Hotel Panache rates are typically above $300 but you can often find discounted rates for under $250.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For design nerds — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coqhotelparis.com/en/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;COQ Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $158/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/coq1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/coq2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COQ is a reference to both the bird and an acronym for “community of quality”. That quality comes through in the curated furnishings like wooden flooring from Limogues and vintage Kilim rugs from Turkey and Moldova. The hotel, which was designed to invoke the sense of being in a family home, also has a dark and muted, almost masculine vibe— a welcome departure from the more clinical white rooms that have become on-trend as of late. The hotel also has a greenhouse and a small courtyard with a chicken coop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel COQ has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For minimalists — &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotel-lapin-blanc.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Le Lapin Blanc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $166/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lapinblanc1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lapinblanc2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meaning “the white rabbit”, Le Lapin Blanc is an ode to Alice in Wonderland without coming across too twee. The decor is all muted millennial pastels against snowy whites, with interesting details like carpet cut-outs that transition into bathroom tile and geometric tubs. Le Lapin Blanc is located in the Latin Quarter, a stone’s throw away from the Sorbonne as well as the famous bookstore Shakespeare and Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Le Lapin Blanc has an elevator but does not have facilities specifically for handicapped guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For trendsetters — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotelfabric.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel Fabric&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $175/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/fabric1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/fabric2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hotel that’s a little more Hermès than Chanel. Housed in a former textile factory, Hotel Fabric pays tribute to its history through its playful and colorful combinations of patterns and textures, such as the fanciful tile work in the bathrooms. While it’s located in a less touristy area it’s still within walking distance to many of Paris’ major attractions but the real value is in its proximity to the fashionable nightlife and restaurant scene in Oberkampf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel Fabric has an elevator and wheelchair accessible facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For the honeymoond period — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hoteldejobo.paris/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel de JOBO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $272/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/jobo1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/jobo2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hotel is a homage to the former social and empress of France, Josephine Bonaparte (get it? Jo..Bo?). The decor references Josephine’s tastes, like her fondness for roses or her credit for being the first to sport a leopard print rug. The building, a former convent. features 24 rooms, most of which feature revitalized Directoire-era wallpaper and empire style beds. There’s an undeniable air of romance here, making it perfect for new couples who can’t get enough of each other or time-tested romances looking to rekindle the flame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel de JOBO has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/paris/paris_header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The 13 Best Airbnbs in Asheville, North Carolina</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 13 Best Airbnbs in Asheville, North Carolina" /><published>2017-11-05T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-05T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/asheville_header.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm just going to come out and say it— Asheville is a hipster haven. There are microbreweries, art galleries, and new american gastropubs a plenty— but perhaps it's the fact that they've been doing this for ages (most residents would identify as hippies, not hipsters) combined with Asheville's lush, woodsy backdrop and the Blue Ridge Mountains that keeps the vibe down to earth rather than insufferably cool. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the hotels in Asheville offer a great value by American standards, many of them seem determined to aesthetically replicate one of Asheville's biggest tourist attractions, The Biltmore estate. While there's nothing wrong with Biltmore, to me the Airbnb inventory offers a much more authentic representation of what makes Asheville unique, such as woodsy cottages and mystical domes created by the artists who live there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those concerned about accessibility we recommend staying in a ground floor room at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thebeaucatcher.com/&quot;&gt;The Beaucatcher&lt;/a&gt;, or the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bohemianhotelasheville.com/&quot;&gt;Grand Bohemian Hotel&lt;/a&gt; in Asheville.

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples &amp;amp; close friends&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/18151750?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Gashes Fluff Haus&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $85/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/gashes1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/gashes2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This historic 116-year old cottage is so picturesque, and makes us feel like we're in Central Europe instead of the U.S. The home itself is located a bit farther out from Asheville in a rural area, but it is close to major roads leading downtown and into the mountains. Many reviewers also mentioned waking up to the sight of bunnies and puppies outside their window so... if you're not sold on that, do you even have a heart?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible and has low ceilings at 6'2&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/10900676?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Arch Suite&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $90/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/dome1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/dome2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The centerpiece of this minimalist home are the half moon windows overlooking the forest outside. Inside, the bedroom and bathroom were recently remodeled this past year and the home also has a lovely circular deck for lounging and enjoying the fresh air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14690762?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Motherwood Sanctuary&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $55/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/motherwood1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/motherwood2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one's for the adventure seekers. The geodesic dome is located farther out in the woods— so it's not the best spot if you're wanting to dine out often. But it does offer gorgeous views of the surrounding nature. For the price and size this would be a totally great option for solo-travelers too, but I think it would be so romantic to experience this place with company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/881707?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;West A'Ville Sanctuary in the Trees&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $90/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/sanctuary1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/sanctuary2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wooden interiors and surrounding trees will make you forget this home is actually in the middle of a residential neighborhood in West Asheville. Located underneath the host's modern home this seems like the perfect place for two to unwind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travellers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17787933?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Urban Oasis in Asheville&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $62/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/urban1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/urban2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This charming little home is one of the best values in Asheville if you're going to be traveling alone— and while it can fit up to 4 people, we think it'd be most comfortable for one. It's also a short drive to downtown (yes, you'll need a car in Asheville) while still being pleasantly private.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14857013?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;West Asheville Urban Abode&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $78/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/abode1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/abode2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A colorful garden unit that's located on Asheville's west side and walking distance to the farmer's market and several restaurants— which means not having to deal with parking. We also hear the host sometimes leaves complimentary drinks for guests! ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/13716891?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Zen Cabin&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $80/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/zen1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/zen2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This cabin looks like a witch's home from a storybook, and also like the perfect place to get away from your everyday life and reflect or work on a creative project. The private space also has large windows to give you a great view of the enchanting forest all around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/6054250&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Rad Pad&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $110/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/radpad1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/radpad2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in the same area as the &quot;West Asheville Urban Abode&quot; listed above and walking distance to restaurants on Haywood street, but for a bit more a night you can get a lot more room to stretch out and also enjoy all the natural light in this bright and sunny loft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For groups and gatherings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/18256162?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Rustic Pine, Peaceful Mountain Home&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $135/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/rusticpine1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/rusticpine2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This gorgeous mountain home blends in perfectly with the surrounding forest. In fact, the home boasts of the variety of trees that can be found on their grounds. What's even more impressive is the natural light bursting into the living room which would be perfect for socializing as a family or big group. Accomodates up to 4 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/9944111?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Serenity Yurt&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $140/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/yurt1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/yurt2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like 90% of the yurts I see on Airbnbs are overpriced for what they offer. Sorry, it's true. Serenity Yurt however makes the cut because it has almost as many amenities as a hotel or typical airbnb— including a functional bathroom, kitchen area with fridge, and a huge wraparound porch with a hot tub. The interior kind of reminds me of the tents in Harry Potter when they go to the Quidditch world cup. 🤓   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/16774726?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Bungalow on Norwood&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $175/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/british1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/british2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what I love about Asheville: that in the American southeast you can somehow find what looks to be Sherlock Holmes' modern day bachelor pad. This home is actually gorgeous, though. It's got two cozy living rooms, a spacious and modern kitchen, even a little home gym with a sunroof. It's the perfect place for a fall or winter group gathering. Accomodates up to 5 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/12363894?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Best View in Asheville&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $199/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/bestview1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/bestview2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, so this house kind of looks like something out of Black Mirror (you know the episode), but it's also pretty much perfect for its location. They weren't kidding about the 'best view' part as every room in the single story home has huge windows. It's spacious, it's luxurious, surrounded by nature, and it even has underfloor heating. I mean, come on. Accomodates up to 4 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb *IS* wheelchair accessible. Wahoo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/mexicocity/MexicoCity_Header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The top 9 things to do for first-timers in Austin, Texas</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/what-to-do-austin-texas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The top 9 things to do for first-timers in Austin, Texas" /><published>2017-11-05T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-05T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/what-to-do-austin-texas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/what-to-do-austin-texas/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Austin_Header.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mt3&quot;&gt;There are some cities that are worth seeing because of the sights, and others worth visiting because of the food. But the best cities have both and Austin is one of those special places. Everytime I visit Austin I see another side to the city I didn't realize existed, and I'm sure I will continue to learn on subsequent trips. But in the meantime, here's a list of the things I *wish* I knew about the first time I visited:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://parks.traviscountytx.gov/find-a-park/hamilton-pool&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Hamilton Pool Preserve&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/HamiltonPool.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Around a thirty minute drive outside of Austin you’ll find Hamilton Pool: the beautiful result of erosion and a collapsed grotto. The pool is open to the public and swimming is allowed (and encouraged!) exempting any bad weather. I’d recommend going on a weekday because it can get crowded (you may even have to wait in line) on weekends. Keep in mind that while it is a pool, there are no lifeguards on duty so swim at your own risk. The entrance fee is $15 per vehicle with discounts for senior citizens and disabled vets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://austintexas.gov/department/barton-springs-pool&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Barton Springs Pool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Barton2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have a car or don’t want to make the trek to Hamilton Pool, Austin also has another natural spring pool right within city limits: Barton Springs. With an average temperature of 68-70 degrees, Barton Springs is ideal for swimming year round. The pool is open daily with lifeguard supervision during popular hours. Admission is $8 for most non-residents but discounted for children and seniors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;The best of Texas barbecue&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Barbecue.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may be familiar with the fact that each southern state has its own twist on barbecue, or a style that makes it unique. For Texas, it’s the fact that we prefer beef or pork: brisket, to be exact. While &lt;a href=&quot;https://franklinbbq.com/&quot;&gt;Franklin’s&lt;/a&gt; is undeniably the most famous game in town, you could be waiting in line up to three hours to get some of the low and slow goodness. We recommend checking out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.labarbecue.com/&quot;&gt;La Barbecue&lt;/a&gt; instead: the joint was started by the daughter of a Texas barbecue legacy. If you get there before opening hours you’ll likely only (only!) have to wait one hour instead of three.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/barbarella/4b52a8e5f964a5204c8527e3&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Barbarella&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Barbarella.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Night clubs aren’t really my scene anymore but Barbarella’s is different, ok? Maybe that’s just the New Yorker in me talking because I’m not used to bars or spaces that are so… big. Drinking and dancing at Barbarella’s is more like going to a house party that’s actually fun than being at a pretentious club, and with many different rooms at your disposal it’s easy not to get bored. Plus they seem to know my biggest weakness: nostalgic pop music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/barbarellaaustin&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;@barbarellaaustin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://hopecampaign.org/hopeprojects/hope-outdoor-gallery/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HOPE Outdoor Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Hope.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A failed condo-development reborn as a public art gallery thanks to Shepard Fairey. There are so many details to uncover and explore throughout the ground’s skeleton walls and levels. Climbing to the top will also give you a wonderful view of the downtown. Check out some free art and get a colorful new profile picture while you’re at it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Rainey Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Rainey.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re the collegiate crowd that takes over East 6th street at night isn’t your scene but you still want a chill place to have a drink, check out Rainey Street. It’s an adorable little street of old homes that were converted into bars, live music venues, and also a popular parking spot for many food trucks. The crowd tends to be young professionals. Some of our favorite spots on the street are Javelina, BlackHeart, The Container Bar, and Bungalow. Also be sure to check out the whimsical Indian restaurant: G’raj Mahal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/javelinabar/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;@javelinabar&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/grajmahalaustin/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;@grajmahalaustin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Breakfast Tacos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Tacos.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s a trip to Austin without eating at least one breakfast taco, aka the best breakfast ever. If you’re not familiar, it’s exactly what you think it is: a taco filled with egg, cheese, and bacon for meat-eaters or potatoes and avocado for vegetarians. Our favorite places in Austin to eat breakfast tacos are &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tacodeli.com/&quot;&gt;TacoDeli&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://juaninamillion.com/&quot;&gt;Juan in Million&lt;/a&gt;, but you can’t go wrong with any of the unnamed taco trucks parked around town either. If you’re willing to drive 30 minutes out of town, there’s a special little truck called “Grandpa’s Tacos” run by an adorable older couple on the side of the highway near Lake Travis that’s worth a stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.batsinaustin.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;South Congress Bat Bridge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Bats.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From March through October, every night just before sundown, over 1.5 million Mexican free-tailed bats fly out from under the South Congress bridge in a giant swarm that’s unlike anything I’ve ever seen before. Yes, you’re going to look like a clichéd tourist standing on the South Congress bridge waiting for nearly an hour but suck it up because nature is cool and it’s worth seeing at least once in your life. Plus it’s free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/bmendez68/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;bmendez68&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Restaurants&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Restaurants.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could probably make a separate list just dedicated to places to eat in Austin, there are so many. Some of the more memorable places we’ve eaten that I’d highly recommend checking out: &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/elizabeth-st-caf%C3%A9/4ef4c212b8f77e0f983c04e4&quot;&gt;Elizabeth St. Cafe&lt;/a&gt; for Vietnamese food, &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/ramen-tatsuya/501831f5e4b06251be422605&quot;&gt;Ramen Tatsu-ya&lt;/a&gt; for Japanese, &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/chilantro/54b495ab498ebacc93b337bf&quot;&gt;Chi’lantro&lt;/a&gt; for Korean/Tex-Mex fusion, &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/hopdoddy-burger-bar/4cb5e045e262b60c46cb6ae0&quot;&gt;Hopdoddy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/tamale-house-east/4f5cd4e6e4b008b15792ebac&quot;&gt;Tamale House East&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/salt--time/50d3997ae4b0200540c19f7c&quot;&gt;Salt &amp;amp; Time&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/odd-duck/5256c1f611d2949f1623a789&quot;&gt;Odd Duck&lt;/a&gt; for a fancy meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mt4 mb0&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Additional Notes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We highly recommend renting a car in order to fully experience everything has to offer. If you plan on staying inside the city limits you could very well get by with ride-sharing apps, but if you’re interested in checking out some of the incredible nature outside of the city, rent a car! &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-austin-texas/&quot;&gt;Read more about our recommendations on where to stay in Austin here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">There are some cities that are worth seeing because of the sights, and others worth visiting because of the food. But the best cities have both and Austin is one of those special places. Everytime I visit Austin I see another side to the city I didn't realize existed, and I'm sure I will continue to learn on subsequent trips. But in the meantime, here's a list of the things I *wish* I knew about the first time I visited:</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/austin/Austin_Header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Where to Stay in Austin, Texas— Including the 9 Best Airbnbs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-austin-texas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where to Stay in Austin, Texas— Including the 9 Best Airbnbs" /><published>2017-11-05T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-05T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-austin-texas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-austin-texas/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/stay_header.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin is one of my favorite cities in America, and a place I hope to live one day. I’m lucky to have family there’s that shown me all the wonderful places (and the food! THE FOOD) beyond “Dirty Sixth”, a.k.a the strip of downtown bars that I’d often be relegated to when visiting during South by Southwest. Austin is definitely worth visiting outside of the festival season mayhem, especially so that you can have the time to truly explore and take advantage of the incredible hill country nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I’ll be heading back there next February, I thought now was as good of a time as any to start thinking about where to stay on my next trip…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb2&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;The 9 Best Airbnbs in Austin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s any city in America where you can’t go wrong on Airbnb— it’s Austin. Ironically, I still managed to somehow ‘go wrong’ here— but more on that later. The quality and inventory of Airbnb homes in Austin is unlike any other place I’ve travelled to, so much so that this list is going to be longer than usual and I decided to dedicate a section exclusively to my top Austin Airbnb picks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there are many modern new developments on Airbnb that provide for a perfectly comfortable and clean place to stay in Austin, I tend to gravitate towards the places that show off more of the city’s weird personality and history. This often means homemade “tiny” homes (bigger than my NYC apartment), vintage airstream trailers, and mid-century modern architecture. The trade off is that some of these options may not be as wheelchair friendly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples &amp;amp; close friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/5337141?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=87001568&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;East Side Beehive&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Beehive1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Beehive2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably one of the most unique Airbnbs I’ve seen on the entire site. The unusual space is the result of designing around city codes and regulatory constraints and many of the materials used were salvage, like the exterior shingles which came from an old home that was remodeled years ago. Despite being a part of the “tiny house movement” this home feels spacious and bright, and is perfectly located in Austin’s East Side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/16157135?location=Austin%2C%20TX%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=HUyE1DZH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Zen Private Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $99/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Zen1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Zen2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another home that manages to nail the trade-off between natural light and privacy. I love the layout of the home, which is almost like a small, modern warehouse. It’s located near the popular South Congress ave and close to Austin’s amazing outdoors areas like Barton Springs, Zilker Park, and Lady Bird Lake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/5083004?location=Austin%2C%20TX%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=HUyE1DZH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Modern Spartan Mansion&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $95/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Spartan1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Spartan2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most airstream trailers I’ve seen on Airbnb tend to lean fully into a 60s or 70s aesthetic but this one is refreshingly modern without sacrificing personality. The original interior was actually burned out in a fire in the 60s so as a homage the owners refinished many of the walls with burnt cedar, using a Japanese preservation technique known as Sho Sugi Ban.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Caveat:&lt;/b&gt; Remember how I said “it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; possible to go wrong with an Airbnb in Austin”? The Last time I was in Austin I stayed in an airstream trailer (not the one listed above). It was beautiful, had friendly hosts, great reviews, but… while there we had a few days of heavy rain and what tends to happen with those is that bugs (like roaches) want to come indoors, and it’s easier to get inside an airstream trailer compared to a house. I mean, it’s just the way mother nature works and you can’t really get mad at anyone (the hosts or the bugs) for it. But it is something to keep in mind. Check the weather before booking, and if you’re not squeamish around bugs this may not be a big deal at all! Personally, I think I can check off staying in an airstream trailer off my list for awhile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travellers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/15706510?location=Austin%2C%20TX%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=HUyE1DZH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Cozy Studio in Private Garden&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $97/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Studio1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Studio2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look y’all, I’m a sucker for a well-tiled bathroom and this is one of those. This little studio home is located in the back of a garden/farm in North Loop, and walking distance to several restaurants and bars. While it would be a cozy fit for two, I think it’d be even more perfect for a single adventurous soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/5171509?location=Austin%2C%20TX%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=HUyE1DZH&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Fresh Modern + Bright Tiny House&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $85/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Tinyhouse1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Tinyhouse2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This quintessential tiny home comes with its own porch and a full kitchen, which is perfect if you want to save money on eating out. It’s located in the trendy but quieter residential neighborhood of Windsor Park. I also love how the design of the building lets in light while still feeling private.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/6704541?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=87001568&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;East Side Hideaway Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $75/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Hideaway1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Hideaway2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the price, I don’t think you can do better on location than this Airbnb, especially for first time visitors. You’re walking distance to all the bars and restaurants on Cesar Chavez (including La Barbecue, if you want to get in line early) and close to the popular nightlife areas: Rainey Street and East 6th Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For groups and gatherings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14690262?location=Austin%2C%20TX%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;adults=5&amp;amp;guests=5&amp;amp;s=_Dvgl6oe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Luxury Family Retreat&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $255/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Family1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Family2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exterior of this home is so unique and the spacious (by New York standards) kitchen is perfect for people who love to cook. It’s also one of the few homes for big groups I’ve seen that actually has 2.5 baths, meaning less holding your pee and fighting over the shower. They even have an Ofuro soaking tub on the (private) balcony if you’re into that. Accommodates up to 6 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/4351493?location=Austin%2C%20TX%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;adults=5&amp;amp;guests=5&amp;amp;s=_Dvgl6oe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Greenhouse&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $205/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Greenhouse1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Greenhouse2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This home was originally built in 1954 and exemplifies mid-century modern. I love the green and orange themed vintage furniture and the custom tile (made in Nicaragua) in the kitchen. The Airbnb is located on Austin’s east side, walking distance to many great restaurants and nightlife. Accommodates up to 6 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/4545175?location=Austin%2C%20TX%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;adults=5&amp;amp;guests=5&amp;amp;s=_Dvgl6oe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Barcelona Modern&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $275/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Barcelona1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Barcelona2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admittedly, this home looks more like what I would expect to find in L.A., like the set of a crazy party in a Bret Easton Ellis novel. But that’s what makes its presence in Austin weird and therefore… appropriately Austin? Enjoy browsing the home’s art collection and discovering cool oddities like the giant “bird bath” tub or jungle-themed bathroom. Accommodates up to 7 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Hotels in Austin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver i mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for February 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For grown-ups on a budget — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/native-hostels-austin.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Native Hostel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $59/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Native1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Native2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may be called a “hostel” but you won’t find raucous partying or youths here. The group behind Native Hostels set out to design a hostel for adults and it shows in the decidedly grown-up decor. It’s also got a great location, straddling the border between the younger, dirty 6th-area and the quieter but still happening East Cesar Chavez Street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Native Hostel has facilities for disabled guests and a hypo-allergenic room available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For minimalists — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/kimber-modern.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Kimber Modern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $249/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Kimber1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Kimber2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Staying at the Kimber Modern is what I imagine a sleepover in a modern art museum would be like. The hotel was conceived of by a local couple who wanted to channel their traveling experiences into designing the perfect place to stay (truly, ladies after my own heart). The hotel only has five rooms and one of the owner’s main goals was to make each room as quiet as possible: hence investments in a $44,000 Mitsubushi heating system that is virtually noiseless, and “Quiet Rock”, a sound-insulating drywall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Rooms at the Kimber Modern are only accessible by stairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples &amp;amp; creatives — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.heywoodhotel.com/index.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Heywood Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $237/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Heywood1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Heywood2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally a bungalow built in 1925, the Heywood refurbished itself as a 7-room hotel on Cesar Chavez Street in East Austin (my favorite location, if you couldn’t tell by my other recommendations). All the beds in the hotel sit on walnut wood platforms handmade by one of the owners, along with other artisans crafts and furniture throughout which guests are able to purchase. Your stay also comes with free bicycles for use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Heywood Hotel has wheelchair accessible rooms on the ground floor and a wheelchair accessible lobby. All rooms are non-smoking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For BFFs — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/us/austin-motel.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Austin Motel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $120/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Motel1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/austin/Motel2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Austin Motel has been around since 1938, when it earned itself the nickname of “The Phallus Palace” (the shape of the sign should give that one away). The historic motel has recently come under the management of the group behind Austin’s well known Hotel San Jose and Hotel Saint Cecilia. It recently reopened with updated furnishings, including custom wallpaper by https://voutsa.com/ that references the original, retro designs. The attached restaurant is still under renovation but for now you can relax at the poolside bar, explore South Congress, hang out in the courtyard, or even walk a few blocks to its new sister hotels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Austin Motel is wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mt4 mb0&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Additional Notes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you decide to stay in an Airbnb or at a hotel, we highly recommend renting a car in order to fully experience everything has to offer. If you plan on staying inside the city limits you could very well get by with ride-sharing apps, but if you’re interested in checking out some of the incredible nature outside of the city, rent a car! &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/what-to-do-austin-texas&quot;&gt;Read more about what to do in Austin here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/mexicocity/MexicoCity_Header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Why right now is actually a good and most helpful time to visit Mexico City</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/why-right-now-is-actually-a-good-and-helpful-time-to-visit-mexico-city/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why right now is actually a good and most helpful time to visit Mexico City" /><published>2017-10-16T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-10-16T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/why%20right%20now%20is%20actually%20a%20good%20and%20helpful%20time%20to%20visit%20mexico%20city</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/why-right-now-is-actually-a-good-and-helpful-time-to-visit-mexico-city/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/MexicoCity_Header.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it wasn’t my original intention to write about Mexico City for the first issue of The InnBox. I was just there last week and I usually like a little more time to process and reflect before writing about a place I’ve visited. However, the aftermath of the earthquake on September 19th has presented a sense of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friends and I had booked our tickets and accommodations before the earthquake hit, but up until a few days before our trip we were still debating if we should go. Our main concerns were a combination of personal safety (in case of aftershocks) and not wanting to be a nuisance or distraction to the citizens during this time. After reading accounts from people on the ground in Mexico City, it seemed like there had been significant progress in the recovery efforts and businesses were opening up again, and so it seemed okay to go forward with the trip. That, and our hotel had a very strict cancellation policy, so our decision was mostly made for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, I’m really glad we went because…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Mexico City's citizens really want you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tourism is a huge part of Mexico City’s economy. Roma-Condesa, one of the most popular neighborhoods for tourists was also one of the hardest by the earthquake and resulted in business losses ranging from 50% to 80% of sales (if not total loss due to damage) and an estimated loss of $34.5 million pesos ($1.8 million USD) in the first five days alone &lt;a href=&quot;http://expansion.mx/nacional/2017/10/02/el-duelo-por-sismo-pasma-la-vida-economica-en-la-roma-condesa?internal_source=MEGAMENU_TRENDING&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;according to reporting by Expansión&lt;/a&gt;. Almost everyone we encountered who is tangentially touched by the tourism industry— from tour guides to taxi drivers to wait staff has thanked us specifically for coming in spite of the earthquake. A few have even explicitly asked us to share our experiences with friends in hopes of gaining new customers. They’re eager for business to return to normal, so bringing your tourism dollars to Mexico City is actually one of the easiest ways you can help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;As a tourist, the earthquake will not really impact your experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost all of the restaurants and businesses have since reopened for business in Roma-Condesa, and if you venture out to other popular neighborhoods like Polanco, Reforma, and Centro Historico, you will be hard pressed to find any visual evidence of the earthquake. For every one bar or restaurant that might be closed there are 4 more other great ones open. In Roma-Condesa you will see a few damaged buildings but they are all cordoned off with caution tape. If you do come across a damaged building or rescue scene, do not stare and do not take photos out of respect for those affected. The disposition of many of the people we interacted with was also very positive and welcoming, in a way that reminded me of New Yorkers and our tendency to move forward and find a sense of normalcy after tough times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;No crowds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re still not convinced, then consider the fact that many of the otherwise overcrowded tourist destinations will be more accessible in the next few months. There weren’t any lines to get into the Torre Latinoamericana, and no waits at many of the popular restaurants (our reservations made in advance were largely unnecessary). Most of us even had a whole row to ourselves on our flights into Mexico City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver i mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for January 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For families or groups of friends — &lt;a href=&quot;http://izta54.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Izta 54&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $60/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Itza1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Itza3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the hotel we chose to stay at, and I absolutely adored it. The place is low-key, kind of like staying in an Airbnb with 24 hour security and a daily cleaning service. They have hostel-style rooms with bunk beds starting as low as $60 per night, or if you’re a family or group of friends you can opt for one of their lofts rooms at $189. Keep in mind that the bedrooms in the lofts do not have doors, so privacy is limited. The building itself is beautiful and perfectly located in Hipódromo, putting it right in between the popular Roma and Condesa neighborhoods, next to tons of great restaurants and bars, and also right across from Parque Mexico, and if you’re a dog lover this is definitely the place you want to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;There are no stairs and no ground floor units so this is not a wheelchair accessible place. In addition, the cheapest hostel-style rooms are on the 5th and top floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For design nerds — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotelcarlota.com.mx/en&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel Carlota&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $108/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Carlota1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Carlota2.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re a fan of modern architecture and geometry then you’ll love the aesthetic of Hotel Carlota. Carlota is a revitalized hotel that was once a hot spot in the 70’s. Each room was designed by a different group of emerging artists and interior designers in Mexico, and the common spaces feature furniture by Mexican design collective &lt;a href=&quot;http://lametropolitana.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;La Metropolitana&lt;/a&gt;. It’s also got a ridiculously sick looking pool, a restaurant and gift shop on-site (Taxonomía) that features unique items by Mexican designers ranging from furniture to homeware to fashion. Hotel Carlota is also located in the Cuauhtémoc district, across the street from a large mall with more mid-range stores and restaurants. Hotel Carlota is also one of the more centrally located places you can stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel Carlota does have an elevator for guests to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples and campers — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lavalise.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;La Valise Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $320/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/LaValise1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/LaValise2.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located in the trendy and hip Roma Norte, La Valise is a small boutique hotel with only three suites. One of which, the Terraza suite, features a bed that can slide out onto the balcony. YEAH. If I weren’t traveling with a group I would’ve been all over this, but La Valisa only features rooms for two. So if you’re like me and love the idea of sleeping in the outdoors while also having all the amenities of a hotel, this is the perfect place for you. The other two suites also each feature their own unique elements like a patio and hammock or a giant circular slab that is also a room divider (I don’t know why… just go with it).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;La Valise does not have an elevators due to it being an old building, and children under 12 are not permitted to stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Airbnb lovers — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/wishlists/131706663&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Mr. W Rentals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $93/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/MrW1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/MrW2.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hat tip to my friend Gopal, who told me about his experience staying in an Airbnb by Superhost Chris. Chris lists his Mexico City apartments under the moniker “Mr. W” and they are all beautifully furnished and available at quite a wide price range from $93 per night to $1545. My favorite is this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17847049?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=131706663&amp;amp;role=wishlist_public&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;$165 apartment in Roma Norte&lt;/a&gt; with big glass windows and natural light. For an additional fee, Chris and his staff will also cook you a traditional dinner in your Airbnb!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The $165 apartment in Roma Norte has an elevator, but you'll want to check the other individual listings to confirm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;What To Do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Barragan.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.casaluisbarragan.org/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Luis Barragán House Tour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you love minimal yet cozy and natural looking architecture, you will enjoy this tour of architect Luis Barragan’s home, for which he won the coveted Pritzker Prize. You’ll witness the ways in which Barragan masters light, color, human psychology, and also learn a bit about how his idiosyncrasies influenced the design. You need to make a reservation in advance and tours cost $21, but you’ll need to pay a little more to take photos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/simonsok/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;@simonsok&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/StreetFoodTour.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Street Food Tour&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We found Ben, a Mexican City native and author of the blog, &lt;a href=&quot;https://whatscookingmexico.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;What’s Cooking Mexico&lt;/a&gt; via Airbnb Experiences. But if you want to cut out the middle man, you can book a tour with him directly &lt;a href=&quot;https://whatscookingmexico.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover red&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; Ben introduced us to the best taco I had during the entire trip, a Carnitas Campechano taco at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yelp.com/biz/taqueria-el-abanico-m%C3%A9xico-2&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover red&quot;&gt;Tacqueria El Albanico&lt;/a&gt; which uses the whole pig, including pig uterus. He also showed us around the Mercado Jamaica which is known for its flowers and where we got to eat squash blossom quesadillas amongst other delicious dishes. $42 per person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Pujol.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pujol.com.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover red&quot;&gt;Pujol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the exact opposite experience of the street food tour, eat at the #20 restaurant on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theworlds50best.com/list/1-50-winners#t11-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover red&quot;&gt;World’s Top 50 Restaurants&lt;/a&gt; list. You’ll get to see what “New Mexican” cuisine is like and taste their signature dish, a mole that has been cooking for 4 years, with new ingredients added as necessary. The chef’s menu will run you about $93 per person not including wine. Bonus: watch the Chef’s Table episode about founder Enrique Olvera on Netflix before going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/tarngerine/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;@tarngerine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/luchalibre.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Lucha Libre&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve never really understood the appeal of WWE until I went to a live Lucha Libre match. If you’re unfamiliar with Lucha Libre I’d highly recommend going with Rick’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/experiences/58415?location=mexico%20city&amp;amp;source=p2&amp;amp;currentTab=experience_tab&amp;amp;searchId=44850de4-c35d-447e-a800-96701730a0f0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover red&quot;&gt;Airbnb Experience&lt;/a&gt;. Not only is it one of the highest rated experiences on the site, but Rick and his friend Gus give you an informative introduction to the world of Lucha Libre so by the time you get to the match you know who to root for and what’s at stake. They also start you off with a fun lucha ‘mask masking’ activity. The match itself was crazy and seeing everyone else get so excited instantly makes you excited to! The Airbnb experience is $58 per person.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Anthropologia.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mna.inah.gob.mx/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Museo Nacional de Antropología&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kind of a “must” when visiting Mexico City. The Anthropology museum details the history of Mexico starting from evolution (with lots of shade thrown towards creation theory!) to the Mayans, Toltecs, Aztecs, and Spanish colonization. You’ll see lots of historic works of architecture, art, tools, and pottery. One of their temporary exhibits even features braille exhibit signage and braille versions of the cave paintings that are on display. Be prepared to spend at least two to three hours here. Admission is an affordable $3.70.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
 &lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
 &lt;img src=&quot;../images/mexicocity/Biblioteca.png&quot; /&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Biblioteca Vasconcelos&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another cool find from Simon. If you love architecture or libraries, you must go here. It’s free to enter and the architecture is modern, airy, and bright. The stacks look like they’re floating in space and challenge our perception for what a library could look like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mt4 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Additional Notes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mexico City is pretty temperate year round, and the weather reminds me a lot of San Francisco. In the morning it’s kind of dewy and a little foggy, mid-day there might be a lot of sunshine and warmth, and in the afternoon you might get a little rain shower. So, you know, carry a light (rain) jacket just in case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uber is the main ride-sharing service available in Mexico City, which many people recommend if you don’t feel comfortable haggling with taxi drivers. They’re also really affordable by American standards. A week’s worth of Uber rides cost us about $80 total.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you aren’t able or interested in traveling to Mexico City, consider making a donation to &lt;a href=&quot;https://hispanicfederation.org/donate/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hispanic Federation&lt;/a&gt;, which is currently supporting both Mexico City and Puerto Rico. 100% of your donation goes towards aid.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/mexicocity/MexicoCity_Header.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Poop!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-test/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Poop!" /><published>2017-08-21T05:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-08-21T05:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-test</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-test/">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jfdsflkdjsflksdjflksdj&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry></feed>