<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-02-11T16:05:25+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">The InnBox</title><subtitle>The InnBox is a weekly newsletter featuring unique, affordable places and spaces for busy folks who need a break.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: The Birdhouse El Nido in Palawan, Philippines</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/birdhouse-el-nido-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: The Birdhouse El Nido in Palawan, Philippines" /><published>2018-02-11T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-02-11T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/birdhouse-el-nido-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/birdhouse-el-nido-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; January 30th — February 1st, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $125/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/birdhouse/1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thebirdhouseelnido.com&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;The Birdhouse&lt;/a&gt; is a unique &quot;glamping&quot; experience nestled into the foresty hills of El Nido, with treehouse-inspired nests that overlook the breathless Bacuit Bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I actually discovered The Birdhouse through the fortuitous magic of SEO. I was in the early stages of planning our trip to El Nido, not yet looking into lodging but doing research on how long our trip should be. I stumbled onto &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thebirdhouseelnido.com/how-many-days-should-i-stay-in-el-nido/&quot; target=&quot;new&quot;&gt;a blog entry with sample itineraries&lt;/a&gt; and out of curiosity clicked on the domain, only to find the exact type of unique, well-designed lodging that The InnBox is all about!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Fast-forward to our trip. We spent first half of our time in El Nido at The Amakan (review forthcoming). I would've preferred to spend the entire time at The Birdhouse but this place fills up &lt;i&gt;fast&lt;/i&gt; and I literally planned our entire Philippines trip around the two nights of availability they had in January. The Birdhouse staff were incredibly communicative in coordinating our arrival— because, yes, it involves some logistics. Let's get into that!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Checking In&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The most important thing you need to know about The Birdhouse, logistically, is that it's not located off a major road. There is no door-to-door drop off service. Unless you plan to stay on their grounds for the entirety of your stay (and miss out on all the beautiful El Nido islands) there will be some walking involved to get in and out of The Birdhouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We were dropped off at the entrance to Marimegmeg beach, the closest a vehicle can get. Because we coordinated with The Birdhouse, they had two staff members there to greet us and help us out with our bags. We followed them down a set of stairs and across almost the entire length of the crescent shaped beach. We took a left turn behind one of the many beach bars and walked through a cleared path in the forest, across a few small bridges until we hit the foot of the stairs leading up to the Birdhouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The first time I took these stairs, I was panting and out of breath. As you ascend you'll come across a few signs with motivational messages like &lt;i&gt;&quot;one step at a time!&quot;&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;&quot;the best is yet to come!&quot;&lt;/i&gt;. When we reached the lobby a staffer was waiting with fresh glasses of ice water, which I immediately seized while wheezing out a &quot;thank you&quot; and then chugging for my life. The funny thing is, the climb seemed so much worse the first time we did it (and we weren't even carrying our own bags) but the subsequent two times it really wasn't that bad. It also helped that our tent was located the closest to ground level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Nest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
You might think that being &quot;closest to the ground&quot; meant that we had the worst view, but it was actually the exact opposite. We were already pretty high up off the ground and our &quot;nest&quot;, Number 3, was actually perfectly positioned so that our view of the bay wasn't as obstructed by the trees that shade the rest of the compound. I mean... look at this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This was my first &quot;glamping&quot; experience so I wasn't sure what to expect but the tent was so much bigger and roomier than I expected. For one, I didn't realize there'd be two additional twin beds inside in addition to the queen bed, meaning each tent can accommodate up to 4. Our room came supplied with some basic amenities: towels and bottled water, and a flashlight in case the generator went out (it didn't during our stay).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Birdhouse is also big on conservation so they only turn on their electricity from 6PM—6AM at night, which is honestly the only time you really need it with most guests off on excursions during the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/7.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/8.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/9.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I thought the bed was super comfy and each side is flanked by a huge fan. With the fan on at a low setting I felt the temperature was perfectly comfortable for me at nights (and I usually find myself getting either &quot;too hot&quot; or &quot;too cold&quot;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
There's also a significant amount of space outside the tent on your own private wooden platform, including a drying line behind the tent for hanging up any wet clothes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt; Bathrooms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;I love the idea of &quot;glamping&quot;, camping, or generally sleeping in the outdoors. I get excited about that... what I get anxious about is the bathroom sitch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We had been warned by the staff not to be freaked out if there were geckos around the bathroom. It's expected, it's normal. I braced myself for it. And yet, I didn't see a single gecko in or around our bathroom during our entire stay! In fact, I saw less crawling critters in our outhouse bathroom at The Birdhouse than I did in our indoor bathrooms at all the other hotels we stayed at in The Philippines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Honestly, it was fine. The bathroom was cozy, it was cute, and the appliances all seemed up to date and new. The shower water doesn't get very warm but you don't really need it to the kind of weather we had. You'll also be confronted in the bathroom with a lot of signage about conservation and water-use; seriously, the commitment is strong. The owner even mentioned to us that he's looking into switching to solar power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;We got a hint from a fellow guest that the Birdhouse lets you break off a piece of aloe from their plant to treat your burns. When we enquired about it one of the managers came out to help us, cutting off a piece of the plant and showing us how to skin the plant and get the most use out of the aloe. They even let us take it with us on the road, although we had to throw it away before we got to the airport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The owner of the Birdhouse, Mark, is also a friendly face that often pops up during your stay and is happy to chat with guests. He actually greeted us from his spot chilling on the beach during our initial trek to the lodge and not knowing who he was, I thought &quot;wow people in El Nido sure are friendly!&quot; before one of the staffers carrying our luggage explained his presence. His wife, Camille, is responsible for all the stunning interior design at the Birdhouse, and we even befriended the current yoga teacher on-site at one of the local bars— although we never did ended up making it to the free yoga class...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Complimentary breakfast is included at The Birdhouse and they serve a different dish everyday accompanied by fresh fruit, like yellow watermelons, which I'd never had before. The first day we had chorizo, eggs, and garlic rice and the second day we had apple butter toast, which was my favorite of the two breakfasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/15.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/14.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We also ate at the restaurant for dinner on our first night there (after climbing those stairs we weren't in a hurry to go back down). The food is kind of expensive but it's a bit understandable when you take into consideration the labor and effort to get the necessary ingredients and supplies up there— and the food was good, so that helps! I had the pumpkin vegetable curry which had very generous portions. If you're lucky and it's not too crowded you can grab the one table on the restaurant's balcony for a shady yet unobstructed view of the bay, or chill in the cute lounge area on the balcony for evening drinks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/16.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/17.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/18.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The Birdhouse is located in Corong-Corong, a more sparsely populated area compared to the denser El Nido town. There are tons of beaches, including Marimegmeg beach which is big and gorgeous, and quite a few bars and cafes around the shore. During our stay we even got to go down to a little Full Moon party at one of the beach bars, where tourists and a few locals were all mingling.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Since most of the tours in El Nido leave from the beach at El Nido town, it will take a twenty minute drive (included in the cost of most tours) to get there. If you want to experience more diverse dining options its recommended to eat and hang around El Nido town after your day tour before heading back to Marimegmeg beach and The Birdhouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This one kind of goes without saying but... given the trek across the beach and several steep stairs to access The Birdhouse, we really can't recommend it for wheelchair users or anyone who has difficulty walking.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/birdhouse/5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If you enjoy active vacations and want to experience El Nido to the fullest, I highly recommend staying at The Birdhouse El Nido. It's probably one of the most memorable places I've stayed at, which pushed me a little bit out of my comfort zone while still being a relaxing and inspiring place to put my feet up.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;If you found this review helpful, please let The Birdhouse know when you book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;http://www.thebirdhouseelnido.com/
&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ The Birdhouse El Nido&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: January 30th — February 1st, 2018 Rate: $125/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Boyfriend</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The 13 Best Airbnbs in San Francisco</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-san-francisco/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 13 Best Airbnbs in San Francisco" /><published>2018-02-04T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-02-04T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-san-francisco</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-san-francisco/">&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;mt3-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/sf/sf_bnb_header.png&quot; /&gt;
San Francisco is our most requested city to cover, so we're starting out with a deep dive into the city's Airbnb scene. Before moving to New York I spent my first two years out of college living in San Francisco and I'm still nostalgic for the beautifully painted Victorians and breathless bay windows. Not to mention the space! Sure, New York and San Francisco are equally crippling expensive but at least you can rely on San Francisco's California address for a few extra square feet and pleasant weather to distract you from the burning hole in your paycheck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The other good news is that Airbnbs in San Francisco are actually quite reasonably priced. Perhaps the sizable supply, thanks to Airbnb being based there, keeps the rates competitive. It's also generally a better choice to stay in an Airbnb if you want to truly experience the city. Most of San Francisco's hotels are located downtown or near the financial distract and sadly not in its best neighborhoods (we will feature our favorites soon nonetheless). Since there is such  huge inventory of Bay Area bnbs we've limited this list to options within San Francisco city limits, and will touch on Oakland and North / South bay options at a later date!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo-travelers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/11924237&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Pavilion&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $120/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/solo_pavilion_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/solo_pavilion_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This so called tiny house has everything you could ever need or want: big windows, an industrial-inspired kitchen, and minimalist bedroom. The fact that it's surrounded by trees only adds to the charm. This architectural gem is available in limited capacity throughout the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14804950&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Private Bernal Heights Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $90/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/solo_bernal_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/solo_bernal_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; id=&quot;anchor&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Have you ever wandered around the IKEA showroom and wished that your apartment could look like their thoughtfully designed fake apartments? Well, this one actually does. This little studio has a calming vibe, a custom shower with some gorgeous tile work, and is located near two of my favorite small parks: Precita and Bernal Heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Access to this studio requires going up a short flight of 3 steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/16824774&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Sunny Misson/Noe/Bernal Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $110/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/solo_mnb_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/solo_mnb_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This studio has a brilliant layout and big windows for soaking up all that California sunshine. There'a also an adorable little breakfast nook in the apartment, which is located at the cross-section of three of my favorite SF neighborhoods: Mission, Noe Valley, and Bernal Heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples &amp;amp; BFFs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14917006&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Noe Apartment with Luscious Garden&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $135/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_plant_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_plant_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We love the dark, moody vibes of this abode, which will please any plant lover. The dark wood paneling gives it a cozy, homey feeling, working in favor of the unit's basement level location instead of against it. The unit is located in a renovated 1906 Victorian cottage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/8192881&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Modern Cole Valley Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $150/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_cole_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_cole_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
If dark and cozy basements aren't your thing, then this light-filled top unit may be more up your alley. We love the minimalist, subtly nautical color scheme and the private deck is an added bonus. It's also located in quaint Cole Valley, a neighborhood I always dreamed about living in during my time in San Francisco!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14996188&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Private Golden Gate Park Suite&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $130/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_gg_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_gg_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
A gorgeous, light-filled apartment close to Golden Gate Park and the vibrant Inner Sunset neighborhood. We love the white and wooden kitchenette and how the apartment is optimized for storage, making a small space seem even bigger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/18359884&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Executive Garden Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $250/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-50 w-25-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_exec_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-50 w-25-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_exec_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-50 w-25-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_exec_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-50 w-25-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/pair_exec_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This apartment is serving executive realness with its sumptuous velvet and leather accents and splashes of navy blue. The outdoor rooftop dining area looks the most romantic place to enjoy a glass of wine and take in the sweeping views after a long day exploring the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Please enquire directly with the host regarding accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For groups and gatherings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/20077167&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Quiet &amp;amp; Comfy Mission&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $130/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/group_mission_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/group_mission_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This spacious Mission apartment is an incredible value, especially when fully occupied. The Airbnb is operated by a French industrial designer, whose taste comes through in the marble countertops and clawfoot bathtubs adorning this gorgeous place. Hosts up to 4 people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/7845599&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Ugliest Dump In The World&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $150/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/group_ugly_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/group_ugly_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The San Francisco design aesthetic these days is sunny and minimal— and I love that, but for something a little different, check out the self-proclaimed &quot;ugliest place in the world&quot;, operated by a funny fellow named Merkley. This Airbnb's aesthetic harkens more to the San Francisco of decades past, a little vintage, a little seedy and a little sinful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/2612741&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Cozy Garden Cottage&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $200/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/group_garden_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/group_garden_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This Castro apartment is full of personality and splashes of vibrant color, including the exterior of the building itself which is a buttery lemon. The outdoor patio looks enchanting, the kitchen cozy, and bathroom just plain fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb unit is located on the ground floor. It is also pet friendly upon approval.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For big groups&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14826774&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Luxury Loft in SOMA&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $459/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/bg_soma_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/bg_soma_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This industrial-style loft is a classic example of SOMA residences, and a fantastic option for a team off-site or business trip due to its proximity to many other tech companies in the area. Accommodates up to 6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is accessible via elevator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/6107359&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Mission Foodie Paradise&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $284/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/bg_mission_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/bg_mission_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
This apartment is located in the same area of the Mission I used to live and in and fills me with nostalgia. It's spacious, has a gorgeous and recently updated kitchen, bright-tiled bathroom, and plenty of light. It's also close to so many wonderful places to eat in the East Mission. Accommodates up to 6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is located on the ground floor but with two short steps separating the door from street level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'; max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/20126616&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Location You Want&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $420/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/bg_mission_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb3-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/sf/bg_mission_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Another East Mission abode, although this one is filled with quirky and artful little details and vintage vibes befitting of the neighborhood. The apartment itself also has a huge kitchen island for a group to gather around, and a backyard patio table for dining al fresco. A few scenes from the movie &quot;Blue Jasmine&quot; were even filmed in the backyard. Accommodates up to 8.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 pb3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Check out more of our top Airbnb picks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr2-ns mb3 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-austin-texas/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/austin/stay_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-austin-texas/&quot;&gt;Where to Stay in Austin, Texas— Including the 9 Best Airbnbs&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl2-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;relative&quot; style=&quot;height: 450px; background-color:#ECEAE7;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;bg-center cover&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url('../images/asheville/asheville_header.png'); padding-bottom:100%; width:100%;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;absolute bottom-2 bg-white pv3 ph4 mh4&quot;&gt;
      &lt;h2 style=&quot;font-family: 'Inconsolata', monospace;&quot; class=&quot;mb1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;a class=&quot;f5 lh-title post-link&quot; href=&quot;http://theinnbox.co/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/&quot;&gt;The 13 Best Airbnbs in Asheville, North Carolina&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">San Francisco is our most requested city to cover, so we're starting out with a deep dive into the city's Airbnb scene. Before moving to New York I spent my first two years out of college living in San Francisco and I'm still nostalgic for the beautifully painted Victorians and breathless bay windows. Not to mention the space! Sure, New York and San Francisco are equally crippling expensive but at least you can rely on San Francisco's California address for a few extra square feet and pleasant weather to distract you from the burning hole in your paycheck.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hotel Review: My Love Inn in Lijiang, China</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/my-love-inn-lijiang-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hotel Review: My Love Inn in Lijiang, China" /><published>2018-01-21T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-01-21T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/my-love-inn-lijiang-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/my-love-inn-lijiang-review/">&lt;div style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dates:&lt;/b&gt; October 24th — 26th, 2017&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di mr4&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rate:&lt;/b&gt; $70/Night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 di&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Who Stayed:&lt;/b&gt; Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Mom&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;mt4-ns mt3 mb4-ns mb3&quot; src=&quot;/images/myloveinn/1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4 f4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Tucked into an unassuming alley in Lijiang's quieter and less popular ancient town, Shuhe, is a tranquil, homey, and harmonious little guest house with the most adorable name: &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/cn/my-love-inn.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot;&gt;My Love Inn.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Blink and you might miss the entrance as I did. The wooden entryway frames a large potted plant against a white backdrop, almost like a piece of art. In addition to starting our stay with a little bit of ambiance, the obscured entrance also provides a sense of privacy. Stepping across the threshold, we found ourselves in an open air courtyard surrounded by wooden slats, ceramic pots, and a shallow pool of water that's home to a handful of tranquil koi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Upon check in we were treated to a tea ceremony inside the lobby— which is less like a traditional hotel lobby and more like a minimalist dining room fit with a long wooden table for entertaining. The tea break was a much appreciated opportunity to catch our breath after pulling our luggage through Shuhe's cobblestone streets (where cars are not permitted). We learned that My Love Inn is, like most guest houses in Lijiang, a family run affair. The dream and vision of a matriarch whose son is now responsible for daily operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Rooms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
We were offered a free upgrade to the &quot;superior twin room&quot;. The main difference between that and our originally booked twin room is that it's slightly bigger and has an divider between the seating area and the beds. The divider between the two areas was actually very useful because the entrance to our room opened up into the courtyard. If we wanted to enjoy the daylight and a fresh breeze we could keep the door to our room open while still maintaing privacy behind the divider.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The beds were super comfortable and came with electric blankets, which was sooo nice since Shuhe is near a mountainous area and tends to get cold at night. The rooms also come with fluffy robes and free cozy slippers with &quot;My Love&quot; embroidered on them in Chinese (which I took with me and still use at home). I'm pretty sure even without an upgrade we would have enjoyed our original room (the cheapest option at the inn), although if I were ever back in Lijiang I would go ahead and splurge for the Deluxe Family Room on the second floor which looks like the best suite in the joint with its huge glass windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/5.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/6.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/7.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt; Bathrooms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;The bathrooms were quite modern in contrast to all the wooden furniture and interiors. The fixtures and appliances were all by Moen or Kohler so, ya know, they got those quality American bathroom products. The bathrooms also have heated tile floors and our room had an enclosed standing shower (some rooms have tubs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
The only room for improvement here is that the bathroom is separated from the bedroom by a sliding wooden door (like all the doors at the inn). Our door didn't really slide to a snug close which gave me a little bit of anxiety, and it wasn't really soundproof. I would probably for-go the aesthetically consistent choice for a normal hinged door that locks. That said, the sliding door was still an improvement over the other hotel we stayed at in Lijiang where the bathroom was separated by a hanging piece of fabric!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Service&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;I can't speak highly enough about the service at My Love Inn. The staff go above and beyond to make you feel at home. During our stay my mom got a headache and asked the staff if they had any pain relievers she could buy. They didn't, but a member of the staff personally escorted us to the nearest pharmacy so that she could help my mom translate and pick out the right medication, as well as pay for it. Likewise they were also very hands on in helping us coordinate excursions we had booked outside of the hotel. For context, I speak ~zero~ Chinese and my mom's is very limited from her early childhood growing up in China. The staff were so helpful in coordinating w/ local tour agencies on our behalf and also escorting us to the right pick up areas since vehicles are not allowed in the immediate area around the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/8.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/9.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Upon check out they gave us each a parting gift— a box of black sugar, a local specialty which we had seen in various shops around Lijiang. I'm a sucker for foodie gifts— I mean these are the type of things it's hard to justify buying for yourself but make such good presents. I can't say if this is a normal occurrence though or if they just really liked my mom who managed to endear herself to everyone on staff. Either way, it was a great way to end our stay at both the inn and in Lijiang.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Food&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4-ns pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;Free breakfast is included daily at My Love Inn and it does not disappoint. The atmosphere and offerings are less continental-breakfast-buffet and more like eating breakfast at a cute cafe, which is actually a cozy sun-dappled room in the inn's entryway. The first night we had heart-shaped fried eggs (adorable!) and congee. The second day they offered us breakfast noodles in a fresh, tomato-y broth that was surprisingly light and clean to the taste. Breakfast also comes with warm soy milk or tea/coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/10.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;The Neighborhood&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb3&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
Shuhe is like the Brooklyn to Lijiang's Manhattan. While both are distinguished as &quot;ancient towns&quot;, Shuhe is a little smaller and slower in pace— with wider streets that are far less packed than Lijiang Ancient Town. Instead of chain boutique pastry stores you'll find independent owned fruit carts lining the streets. On the flip side, the dining options are so much more varied in Lijiang Ancient Town. For dinner the majority of restaurants in Shuhe do Hot Pot (which is great! Just maybe not for every meal). Muzi restaurant, located on the edge of town, was a welcome way to change it up with a more diverse menu focused around vegetables. The fare is literal farm-to-table as the restaurant is located across the street from their farm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
For this trip I spent half my time in Lijiang Ancient Town and half in Shuhe Ancient Town, though it's more common to stay in one of the ancient towns and do a day trip to the other. Based on the quality of My Love Inn compared to the hotels in Lijiang Ancient Town and Shuhe's relative chill factor, I'd recommend staying there and then day-tripping to Lijiang Ancient Town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;Accessibility&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
While most of the rooms are located on the ground floor, access to My Love Inn requires walking and carrying luggage across a few unpaved streets, with many wooden thresholds, which may be inconvenient for wheelchair users or anyone with difficulty walking.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-third-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/11.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-third-ns pl1-ns pr1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/12.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-third-ns pl1-ns mb3 mb4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/myloveinn/13.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pb2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto; font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold';&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;pb4&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
I highly recommend staying at the My Love Inn if you ever find yourself in Lijiang. It's been one of the best hotel experiences I've had, at such a humble little place for such a reasonable price.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tc tl-ns&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 650px; margin: auto;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lh-copy&quot;&gt;If you found this review helpful, please use our link to book:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;f5 link ba bw1 ph3 pv2 mb2 dib orange&quot; href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/cn/my-love-inn.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot;&gt;Book your stay @ My Love Inn&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">Dates: October 24th — 26th, 2017 Rate: $70/Night Who Stayed: Sabrina &amp;amp; Her Mom</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">12 Low-Key, Last-Minute Valentine’s Day Getaways for Everyone</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/last-minute-valentines-day-escapes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="12 Low-Key, Last-Minute Valentine's Day Getaways for Everyone" /><published>2018-01-14T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2018-01-14T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/last-minute-valentines-day-escapes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/last-minute-valentines-day-escapes/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/valentines/valentines_header.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I know— Valentine’s Day is a manufactured event intended to sell Hallmark cards and chocolate with no real bearing on the health of our relationships. But the fact it falls pretty squarely in the midst of our winter hibernation always makes me excited for an excuse to do &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt;, literally &lt;em&gt;anything&lt;/em&gt; out of the ordinary, whether that’s dressing up for a fancy dinner or packing my bags for a weekend escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also find it interesting the ways in which traveling can strengthen our relationships, or at least put them to the test. Whether that’s through spending a longer stretch of time than usual with our significant others and friends, working together to navigate an unfamiliar place, or learning more about yourself and what you’re capable of on a solo-trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’ve put together some low-key ideas on how to celebrate, regardless of your relationship status. Fun fact: I’ve probably spent more of the past five Valentine’s Days with my best friend than my boyfriend— there’s really no wrong way to spend it and to be honest nothing sounds more romantic to me than exploring a new city where nobody knows your name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 light-silver i mb0&quot;&gt;As of writing all of the hotels recommended still have availability for the night of February 14th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; id=&quot;west&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Western Getaways&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travelers — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/12956782?location=Salt%20Lake%20City%2C%20UT%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;check_in=2018-02-14&amp;amp;check_out=2018-02-15&amp;amp;s=FEmOwSn4&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;City Den&quot; in Salt Lake City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $81/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/slc_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/slc_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This minimal yet warm Airbnb in Salt Lake City is perfectly located and walking distance to downtown and many of the city’s major attractions. Stroll around Temple Square, load up on cheap and delicious diner food at Ruth’s, and of course visit the namesake lake. The weather during Valentine’s week is projected to be in the high 40s/low 50s and JetBlue offers flights from Long Beach to SLC starting at $53 each way and $78 from SFO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor1&quot; class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For pal-entines — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/20364076?s=41&amp;amp;ref_device_id=8b5c099e0fb540002ca1c671dff56f913c1e005b&amp;amp;user_id=11653969&amp;amp;_branch_match_id=480386357325893675&amp;amp;check_in=2018-02-14&amp;amp;guests=1&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;check_out=2018-02-16&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Hideout Cabin&quot; in Leavenworth, Washington&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $185/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/leavenworth_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/leavenworth_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This adorable little Bavarian town in eastern Washington looks straight out of a storybook. It’s a two hour drive from Seattle and this modern, custom-built Airbnb was only just completed last year. The Airbnb is perfect for a cabin weekend with a group of friends, close to the town for shopping and dining but also with access to nearby ski resorts and hiking trails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/malibu-riviera-motel-malibu.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Native Hotel in Malibu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $230/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/malibu_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/malibu_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a 45 minute drive up from Pacific Coast Highway from L.A. lies the newly re-opened Native Hotel, a series of bungalows formally known as the Malibu Riviera Motel where old Hollywood types like James Dean and Marilyn Monroe wood often escape to. Get in your prerequisite long walks on the beach, brunch at Malibu Farm Cafe, and get your fill of some of the region’s best wines before closing out the night in your coastal abode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The Native Hotel does not specifically state whether or not they have accessible facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; id=&quot;south&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Southern Getaways&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travelers — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/sobro-guest-house.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;SoBro Guesthouse in Nashville&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $160/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/nashville_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/nashville_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located around the corner from the Country Music Fall of Hame, SoBro Guest House is an all-suite hotel in which each of the 24 rooms come complete with a modern kitchen and living area. Take in a show at the Grand Ol’ Opry and if you’re feeling up for it, take a 20 minute Uber ride outside of town to try the homemade biscuits at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lovelesscafe.com/&quot;&gt;Loveless Cafe&lt;/a&gt;. Round-trip flights to Nashville from Dallas are as low as $91 if you’re flexible enough to fly back on Valentine’s Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;SoBro Guesthouse has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For pal-entines — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.catahoulahotel.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Catahoula Hotel in New Orleans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $174/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/neworleans_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/neworleans_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Catahoula hotel occupies a historic townhouse originally built in 1845 and sits just outside of the French Quarter— close enough to the revelry without being in the thick of the madness.  Start your morning with beignets and coffee, and end the night with an amazing Peruvian dinner and drinks at the hotel’s restaurant and Pisco bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The Catahoula Hotel has in-room accessibility and roll-in showers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/havana.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Hotel Havana in San Antonio, Texas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $143/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/sanantonio_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/sanantonio_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I was a little girl growing up in Texas, the San Antonio riverwalk seemed like the most romantic place in the world. Take a night-time cruise amidst rainbow colored lights and then spend your nights at the historic Hotel Havana, originally opened in 1918 by a local groper and recently reopened under the management of the Austin based hotel group Bunkhouse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The Hotel Havana offers facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; id=&quot;midwest&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Midwestern Getaways&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travelers — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/hotel-arapahoe-ave-boulder.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Basecamp Boulder in Boulder, Colorado&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $167/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/boulder_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/boulder_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Basecamp Boulder is the perfect HQ for a weekend trip to the   rocky little town 45 minutes outside of Denver. Hike around Chautauqua Park, go shopping on Pearl Street, kick back with a beer at many of the area’s local breweries, or literally hang out on the hotel’s climbing wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Basecamp Boulder has in-room accessibility and accessible bathrooms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For pal-entines — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/the-richards-house.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Richards House in Galena, Illinois&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $43/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/galena_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/galena_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A three hour drive/one hour flight east of Chicago is a little town called Galena, with a big Irish influence and the former home of Ulysses S. Grant. The main street is filled with adorable little shops, restaurants, and distilleries. We recommend staying a 20 minute drive across stay lines in Dubuque, Iowa, at The Richards House, a budget friendly bed &amp;amp; breakfast that has all the magic of a Hogwarts common room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The Richards House does not specifically state whether or not they have accessible facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/alma.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel Alma in Minneapolis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $186/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/minneapolis_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/minneapolis_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re going to go Minneapolis in the winter, you probably want to go with someone you can cuddle with. Luckily the Alma Hotel is situated right above its namesake Restaurant and Cafe so with the wonders of room service you don’t even have to leave your love nest if you don’t want to. Round trip flights from Chicago are as low as $74 on Spirit airlines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Basecamp Boulder has in-room accessibility and accessible bathrooms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; id=&quot;east&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Eastern Getaways&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travelers — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/5539197?location=Philadelphia%2C%20PA%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;check_in=2018-02-14&amp;amp;check_out=2018-02-15&amp;amp;s=4ZJxRSUx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Rittenhouse Apartment in Philadelphia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $86/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/philly_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/philly_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The city of brotherly love is easy to get to from anywhere else on the Northeast corridor and the perfect place to explore on your own. Brush up on your American history at historical sites like Ben Franklin’s house and the Liberty Bell and then treat yourself to all American eats like burgers at High Street on Market or fried chicken and donuts from Federal Donuts. All before falling into bed at this adorable row-house in Rittenhouse Square.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For pal-entines — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/roundhouse-beacon2.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Roundhouse in Beacon, New York&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $189/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/beacon_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/beacon_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beacon is a charming little city that’s an hour and a half drive north of New York City, and it’s perfect for art lovers. Spend your days viewing modern art the Dia:Beacon museum or cross the river to take in outdoor installations at Storm King Art Center. Roundhouse, a cluster of restored historic buildings including a hotel is an additional work of art to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Roundhouse has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.booking.com/hotel/us/the-dewberry-charleston.html?aid=1452227&amp;amp;checkin_monthday=14&amp;amp;checkin_month=2&amp;amp;checkin_year=2018&amp;amp;checkout_monthday=15&amp;amp;checkout_month=2&amp;amp;checkout_year=2018&amp;amp;no_rooms=1&amp;amp;group_adults=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;The Dewberry in Charleston, South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $243/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/charleston_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/valentines/charleston_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re based up north then what better way to simultaneously escape the cold and celebrate love than booking a ticket straight into the heart and soul of southern hospitality? You can find round trip flights for $117 on Valentine’s Day from New York City to Charleston via JetBlue. The Dewberry with its decadent marriage of gold and wood is the perfect place to come back to after getting your fill of other perfect pairs like shrimp and grits &amp;amp; chicken and waffles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The Dewberry has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Your travel guide to Bariloche, Argentina: where to stay and what to do.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your travel guide to Bariloche, Argentina: where to stay and what to do." /><published>2017-12-17T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-12-17T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/bariloche-argentina-travel-guide/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bariloche/bariloche_header.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bariloche is full of dualities— considered the gateway to Argentinian Patagonia, this magical land of lakes is equally enchanting in either summer or winter weather. It’s famous vistas include both the high altitudes of the surrounding Andes and the low lakes in-between them. Much like Buenos Aires, Bariloche also has a distinctly European influence— except instead of Parisian architecture you’ll find Swiss style chalets alongside many fondue and chocolate shops. In fact, Bariloche is considered the chocolate capital of the country. If your idea of the perfect vacation involves both breathtaking views and eating copious amounts of high quality food, then Bariloche is the perfect place for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver i mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for February 2018. Remember: Bariloche is south of the equator and experiences opposite seasons to the U.S.!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cursory search into where to stay in Bariloche will introduce you to Llao Llao, the big game in town and surprisingly the only one that’s really talked about. I won’t begrudge anyone their preference for luxury but personally I’ve never been a big resort person— for both the price point and how isolated they can feel from the very place you’ve come to experience. So you won’t find many recommendations for resorts here, and I bring it up in regards to Bariloche because I think it’s a shame. There are so many interesting places to stay that capture the spirit of the region. Let’s give them some recognition, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travelers &amp;amp; the budget conscious — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hostel41below.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;41 Below Hostel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $26/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/41below_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/41below_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;41 Below is an unpretentious and charming hostel run by some friendly Kiwis. It’s also probably the best value you’re going to find in Bariloche because of its proximity to downtown, the jumping off point for many excursions in the region. It’s also convenient for solo-travelers because it’s very easy to meet fellow travelers in the hostel lounge and pair up to split excursion costs. I’ll admit just like I’m not a huge resort person, I’m also not a huge hostel person. I’m always a bit concerned there might be too much of a party vibe which is not what I’m looking for these days, but 41 Below was extremely chill, at least when I stayed there in the winter season. It’s not so youthful that you’ll feel out of place if you’re not a student, but I would say that someone in their late 40s might be less likely to find company of a similar age. And look, while 41 Below is probably not going to win any design awards anytime soon, for a hostel at this price range the decor is charmingly simple and sufficiently tasteful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;We would not recommend 41 Below for guests with wheelchairs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor1&quot; class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For digital nomads — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/12279136?location=Bariloche%2C%20San%20Carlos%20de%20Bariloche%2C%20R%C3%ADo%20Negro%2C%20Argentina&amp;amp;s=BMB5OMrp&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Patagonian Style Cabin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $42/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/cabin_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/cabin_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This sunny cabin is located just a little ways off from downtown, which is accessible via a 15 minute bus ride from the nearby stop. In a refreshing twist the bed is actually located on the main floor instead of the loft, which has been instead converted into an office-like space. The modern bathroom also looks newer and nicer than what you’ll find at many hotels in the area. The cabin sits on private property that the host’s parents live on, who are also available as a helpful point of contact for guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;We don't recommend this airbnb for wheelchair users. In addition it's been noted that the bed may be small for any exceptionally tall guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For families — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.ca/rooms/65145&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;CABIN - PYRAMID&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $49/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/Pyramid_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/Pyramid_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The layout of this cabin is perfect for families traveling with small children, and also for anyone who prefers being a little farther removed from the more tourist-centric downtown areas. It’s like being in a tent but with indoor plumbing and sturdy walls. Wake up to scenic views of the surrounding mountain and lakes, one of which is only a twenty minute walk away for a summer swim. Because of its more rural location, you’ll definitely want to rent a car when staying here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;We don't recommend this airbnb for wheelchair users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;A little something for everyone — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/users/1518997/listings&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Nuno's Listings&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $65/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/nuno_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb1 mb2-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/nuno_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/nuno_4.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/nuno_3.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Portuguese architect who goes by Nuno is literally slaying the Bariloche Airbnb game. He manages 23 listings across the region varying from $65 to $412 a night, and all of which are impeccably designed and decorated. Our favorite of the bunch is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/11521531?s=-250liCw&quot;&gt;this 6 bedroom, centrally located home&lt;/a&gt; which embodies all of our modern farmhouse dreams for an extremely reasonable $115/night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Two of Nuno's listings claim to be wheelchair accessible: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/7849214&quot;&gt;this 3-bedroom cottage&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/974290&quot;&gt;this contemporary mountain home&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For winter vacations — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/ar/design-suites-bariloche&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Design Suites Bariloche&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $131/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/design_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/design_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ignore the on-the-nose name. The main selling point of this lodge are the circular jacuzzi tubs overlooking the lake— but hey, even the rooms with the boring ol’ rectangular tubs look just as amazing. We’re recommending this one for winter travel. If it’s too cold to do anything outside then get you some champagne and bubble bath and treat-yo-self. This one’s also got a great location just far enough outside the hustle and bustle of touristy downtown but still close enough for it to be accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Design Suites does have an elevator on the premises but we recommend directly confirming with the hotel that they have facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/ar/peninsula-petit&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Peninsula Petit Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $140/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/petit_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/petit_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peninsula Petit boasts world class service for a reasonable price. It’s one of the more remotely located places we’re recommending, a ways off from downtown but the hotel makes up for it by providing everything you need right at home. For starters, people &lt;i&gt;rave&lt;/i&gt; about the on-site &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.es/Restaurant_Review-g312848-d7376546-Reviews-Desde_El_Sur-San_Carlos_de_Bariloche_Province_of_Rio_Negro_Patagonia.html&quot;&gt;restaurant&lt;/a&gt; and its breakfast in particular. The premises also include a private, pup-friendly beach for guests, and we hear the hands-on owner also lends out his kayak to guests for free. Peninsula Petit is often fully booked so this is definitely a place you want to book far in advance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Peninsula Petit offers facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For resort quality without resort prices — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/ar/lirolay-suites&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Lirolay Suites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $190/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/lirolay_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/lirolay_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every room at Lirolay is comes with a jacuzzi and a suite designation— there’s no cheap seats here, okay? Still, their most affordable offering is a triple room that when fully occupied comes to a reasonable $60 a person. This lodge looks straight out of a fairytale and I’m sure a record number of proposals have gone down here. Breakfast is included and keep in mind that the intimate little hotel’s twelve rooms go fast, so book in advance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Lirolay has fascilities for disabled guests including roll-in showers, accessible bathrooms, and in-room accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; id=&quot;whattodo&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;What To Do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cerrocampanario.com.ar/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Cerro Campanario&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/cerrocompanario.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you only have a day in Bariloche, this is probably the first thing I’d recommend doing. A steep hour’s hike to the top of Cerro Campanario gives you a breathtaking panoramic view of the entire surrounding region. I still think back on this trip and this specific hike as one of the most stunning glimpses of nature I’ve witnessed. At the top you can also ride the chairlift back down to the base of the mountain. Technically you can ride it up too, but where’s the fun in that? Getting to Cerro Companario is also easy and very affordable by bus and the hike itself is straightforward— so skip the $$$ on a private tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;anchor2&quot; class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4 mt3&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/lamarmite.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://lamarmite.com.ar/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;La Marmite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behind this cute little red storefront is a cheese lover's paradise. La Marmite specializes in swiss-style fondue and each order is enough for 2-3 people and comes with meats, vegetables, and bread accompaniements to dip. They also offer chocolate fondue for dessert. Locals seem torn on the price: depending on who you ask this is either one of the cheaper places to get fondue in Bariloche, or one of the more expensive!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;http://lamarmite.com.ar/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;lamarmite.com.ar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/nahuel_huapi.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Explore the lakes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lake Nahuel Huapi is the big lake which Bariloche sits on the south coast. The lake has seven branches, most of which were carved out by glaciers back in the day. Boat tours are available daily— we easily booked one through the hostel we were staying at, but there is also a tourist center downtown from which you can book tours as well. The best part of the boat tour was seeing just how gargantuan the Andes are when viewed at sea level, compared to being viewed from afar at Cerro Campanario.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/rapanui.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Buy some chocolate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
As mentioned earlier, Bariloche is the chocolate capital of Argentina. The two big players in town are &lt;a href=&quot;http://chocolatesrapanui.com.ar/&quot;&gt;Rapa Nui&lt;/a&gt;, which looks like an offshoot of Willy Wonka's chocolate factory and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mamuschka.com/&quot;&gt;Mamushka&lt;/a&gt;, which looks like the inside of a set of Russian nesting dolls. Both also function as an ice cream shop and are a great place to pick up gifts to take home, although I slightly preferred Rapa Nui because they had a larger variety of food products for sale.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/cerrocatedral.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Go skiing @ &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.catedralaltapatagonia.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Cerro Catedral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my biggest regrets from my trip is NOT going skiing in Bariloche. I didn't know how to back then and I got intimidated about the idea of learning in a foreign country. But if skiing is your &lt;i&gt;thang&lt;/i&gt;, Cerro Catedral is apparently where everyone goes to catch some air. Lift tickets cost around $25 and in addition to skiing Catedral also offers snow tubing (called &quot;donuts&quot; there), sleding, snow shoes, along with &quot;Snow BMX&quot; and &quot;Snow Scoot&quot;, both of which are not helping my FOMO.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.catedralaltapatagonia.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;catedralaltapatagonia.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/antares.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Taste beer @ &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Restaurant_Review-g312848-d2660620-Reviews-Antares-San_Carlos_de_Bariloche_Province_of_Rio_Negro_Patagonia.html&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Antares&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Antares is the most popular of many local breweries in Bariloche. You can get a tasting flight of four different beers for around $7, the most popular of which is their honey beer. It's a welcome break from all the Quilmes you'll be drinking the rest of your time in Argentina. And while Antares is also a gastropub, we recommend sticking to the drinks here— there are better places to eat in Bariloche!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/antaresbariloche/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;@antaresbariloche&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bariloche/portblest.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Puerto Blest&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Puerto Blest is a tiny but scenic port near the border to Chile, and a popular stop on many of the boat tours in the area. If you don't have a Chilean visa, tbh the little port is going to seem very small and boring. If you do, it's going to open up a whole new world. You can explore parts of the area across the border, or like many people, actually leave Argentina and enter Chilean patagonia through this point.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The 13 Best Airbnbs in Asheville, North Carolina</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 13 Best Airbnbs in Asheville, North Carolina" /><published>2017-12-10T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-12-10T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-airbnbs-asheville-north-carolina/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/asheville_header.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm just going to come out and say it— Asheville is a hipster haven. There are microbreweries, art galleries, and new american gastropubs a plenty— but perhaps it's the fact that they've been doing this for ages (most residents would identify as hippies, not hipsters) combined with Asheville's lush, woodsy backdrop and the Blue Ridge Mountains that keeps the vibe down to earth rather than insufferably cool. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the hotels in Asheville offer a great value by American standards, many of them seem determined to aesthetically replicate one of Asheville's biggest tourist attractions, The Biltmore estate. While there's nothing wrong with Biltmore, to me the Airbnb inventory offers a much more authentic representation of what makes Asheville unique, such as woodsy cottages and mystical domes created by the artists who live there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those concerned about accessibility we recommend staying in a ground floor room at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thebeaucatcher.com/&quot;&gt;The Beaucatcher&lt;/a&gt;, or the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bohemianhotelasheville.com/&quot;&gt;Grand Bohemian Hotel&lt;/a&gt; in Asheville.

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples &amp;amp; close friends&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/18151750?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Gashes Fluff Haus&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $85/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/gashes1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/gashes2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This historic 116-year old cottage is so picturesque, and makes us feel like we're in Central Europe instead of the U.S. The home itself is located a bit farther out from Asheville in a rural area, but it is close to major roads leading downtown and into the mountains. Many reviewers also mentioned waking up to the sight of bunnies and puppies outside their window so... if you're not sold on that, do you even have a heart?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible and has low ceilings at 6'2&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/10900676?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Arch Suite&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $90/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/dome1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/dome2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The centerpiece of this minimalist home are the half moon windows overlooking the forest outside. Inside, the bedroom and bathroom were recently remodeled this past year and the home also has a lovely circular deck for lounging and enjoying the fresh air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;anchor&quot; class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14690762?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Motherwood Sanctuary&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $55/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/motherwood1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/motherwood2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one's for the adventure seekers. The geodesic dome is located farther out in the woods— so it's not the best spot if you're wanting to dine out often. But it does offer gorgeous views of the surrounding nature. For the price and size this would be a totally great option for solo-travelers too, but I think it would be so romantic to experience this place with company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/881707?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;West A'Ville Sanctuary in the Trees&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $90/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/sanctuary1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/sanctuary2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wooden interiors and surrounding trees will make you forget this home is actually in the middle of a residential neighborhood in West Asheville. Located underneath the host's modern home this seems like the perfect place for two to unwind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travellers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17787933?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Urban Oasis in Asheville&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $62/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/urban1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/urban2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This charming little home is one of the best values in Asheville if you're going to be traveling alone— and while it can fit up to 4 people, we think it'd be most comfortable for one. It's also a short drive to downtown (yes, you'll need a car in Asheville) while still being pleasantly private.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14857013?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;West Asheville Urban Abode&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $78/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/abode1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/abode2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A colorful garden unit that's located on Asheville's west side and walking distance to the farmer's market and several restaurants— which means not having to deal with parking. We also hear the host sometimes leaves complimentary drinks for guests! ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/13716891?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Zen Cabin&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $80/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/zen1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/zen2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This cabin looks like a witch's home from a storybook, and also like the perfect place to get away from your everyday life and reflect or work on a creative project. The private space also has large windows to give you a great view of the enchanting forest all around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/6054250&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Rad Pad&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $110/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/radpad1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/radpad2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Located in the same area as the &quot;West Asheville Urban Abode&quot; listed above and walking distance to restaurants on Haywood street, but for a bit more a night you can get a lot more room to stretch out and also enjoy all the natural light in this bright and sunny loft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt4 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For groups and gatherings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/18256162?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Rustic Pine, Peaceful Mountain Home&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $135/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/rusticpine1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/rusticpine2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This gorgeous mountain home blends in perfectly with the surrounding forest. In fact, the home boasts of the variety of trees that can be found on their grounds. What's even more impressive is the natural light bursting into the living room which would be perfect for socializing as a family or big group. Accomodates up to 4 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/9944111?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Serenity Yurt&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $140/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/yurt1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/yurt2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like 90% of the yurts I see on Airbnbs are overpriced for what they offer. Sorry, it's true. Serenity Yurt however makes the cut because it has almost as many amenities as a hotel or typical airbnb— including a functional bathroom, kitchen area with fridge, and a huge wraparound porch with a hot tub. The interior kind of reminds me of the tents in Harry Potter when they go to the Quidditch world cup. 🤓   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/16774726?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Bungalow on Norwood&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $175/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/british1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/british2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what I love about Asheville: that in the American southeast you can somehow find what looks to be Sherlock Holmes' modern day bachelor pad. This home is actually gorgeous, though. It's got two cozy living rooms, a spacious and modern kitchen, even a little home gym with a sunroof. It's the perfect place for a fall or winter group gathering. Accomodates up to 5 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/12363894?location=Asheville%2C%20NC%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;s=ff_3BGyk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;The Best View in Asheville&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $199/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/bestview1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/asheville/bestview2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, so this house kind of looks like something out of Black Mirror (you know the episode), but it's also pretty much perfect for its location. They weren't kidding about the 'best view' part as every room in the single story home has huge windows. It's spacious, it's luxurious, surrounded by nature, and it even has underfloor heating. I mean, come on. Accomodates up to 4 people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb *IS* wheelchair accessible. Wahoo!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Your travel guide to Tromsø, Norway: where to stay and what to do.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tromso-travel-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your travel guide to Tromsø, Norway: where to stay and what to do." /><published>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tromso-travel-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tromso-travel-guide/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/tromso/tromso_header.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I’ve heard that Tromsø is beautiful in the summer, it mainly draws visitors in the colder months because it is one of the best places in the world to view the Aurora Borealis, or northern lights. That’s certainly what brought me to this arctic destination— so I didn’t expect to fall in love with the city for a whole bunch of other reasons. Of all the cities I visited in Norway, Tromsø was my favorite. The locals were so incredibly friendly, the food was amazing, and it had such a laid-back, cozy atmosphere. If I could describe it in a few words I might call it a metropolitan fishing village.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We certainly have lots to say about chasing the northern lights, but first let’s talk about where to stay when you head up north.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb0&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Where to Stay&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver i mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for February 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tromsø’s hospitality scene seems nascent compared to larger Norwegian cities like Oslo and Bergen. The Airbnb inventory left something to be desired and there are few if any independently run hotels— especially if you want to be located near the city center. In fact, this is one of the few times our top recommendations include hotels that are a part of a larger chain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For solo travelers &amp;amp; the budget conscious — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/no/comfort-xpress-tromso.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Comfort Hotel Xpress Tromsø&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $136/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/comforthotel_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/comforthotel_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comfort Hotel Xpress is part of Scandinavian chain Nordic Choice Hotels, which is a franchise of American-owned Choice Hotels, which operates Comfort Inn &amp;amp; Suites in the US. But this isn’t your momma’s Comfort  hotel. After spending days of research trying to find a place to stay I ultimately decided to stay at Comfort Hotel because of its location, positive reviews, and the price— since Tromso was the last leg of my trip and Norway is expensive, I really wanted to cut costs here. Honestly, I went into this with low expectations but found myself pleasantly surprised by this Comfort Hotel outpost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, they offer room rates specifically for single travelers. Which is great because as a solo-traveller I hate paying more for space I won’t use. The hotel is centrally located in the town center and walking distance to every single attraction. Besides my trip from the airport I didn’t take a single taxi here which also helped with my budget. Lastly, as a little cherry on top the hotel lobby has a well-stocked deli stand with grab-and-go items and drinks like coffee and wine available for purchase, which was super convenient when I didn’t feel like going outside in the cold. Check-in and check-out is also done via a tablet in the lobby for minimal human interaction, if that’s a thing you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d be lying if I said I didn’t pay attention the interior design of the places I stay at. I do, and sometimes I find that the aesthetics of these modern boutique hotel chains &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; be a bit tacky— a little IKEA but with all the leftover green and orange furniture no one wanted. Comfort Hotel Express was actually a step-up from that, although certainly youthful in appearance. It’s like how I imagine Hollywood would interpret what a college dormitory should look like, if that makes sense. The only downside to my stay here was the sad little view from my room of a back alley (look to the more expensive waterfront hotels for a better view) and because it was so youthful there were a couple of loud groups of students staying on my floor. Which wasn’t a huge deal for me because I’m a deep sleeper, but something to keep in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Comfort Hotel Xpress has an elevator for wheelchair access to rooms on the upper floors, as well as ground floor units.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For bibliophiles &amp;amp; friends traveling together — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bedandbooks.no/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Tromsø Bed &amp;amp; Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $95/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/bedbooks_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/bedbooks_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So admittedly this was my first choice for where to stay in Tromsø, but the small guest house sells out fast so it’s better to book this place way in advance. It’s one of the few individually owned lodging options in the city and while single rooms start at $95, the best deal is the triple room that if fully occupied comes out to a little over $50/night. Bed &amp;amp; Books is run similar to a hostel with shared bathrooms and common areas, including, you guessed it, a generous library for your perusal. My only initial hesitation to staying here was that as a solo-traveler it seemed a little farther out from the city center and I was worried about walking back at night, but having now been to Tromsø and I think the distance is actually not that far at all, and I felt fairly safe walking around at night. I would definitely try to stay here the next time I’m in town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Bed &amp;amp; Books doesn't specifically state that they are wheelchair accessible. Considering what we know of the architecture and the presence of stairs, we wouldn't recommend this spot for wheelchair users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For couples &amp;amp; business travelers — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.booking.com/hotel/no/the-edge.en-gb.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Clarion Hotel The Edge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $216/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/clarion_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/clarion_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clarion is another brand operated by Choice Hotels, the same parent company responsible for Comfort Hotel Express. While our other suggestions are perfectly reasonable for couples, if what you’re after is romance than The Edge is a much better choice because of its location on the harbor and majestic views of the water, Arctic cathedral, and surrounding mountains. It’s the most centrally located of the options presented here and also a great choice if someone else is footing your hotel bill. The hotel’s restaurant, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kitchenandtable.se/story/&quot;&gt;Kitchen &amp;amp; Table&lt;/a&gt;, is run by Marcus Samuelsson and features dishes that combine his Scandinavian background with New York influences. Breakfast at the hotel is also included in most rates, and The Edge also offers lower rates for single travelers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;The Edge has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;On Airbnbs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While there are certainly plenty of Airbnbs available, I felt like it was hard to find one that met all of my criteria without trade-offs. For one, I prefer to rent out an entire apartment for privacy and safety. Second, I only want to stay in an Airbnb where the value is better than staying in a hotel. That means I want something that is clean, well-decorated, in a good location, for &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; than I would pay for a hotel. Third, reviews matter a lot to me, again for safety reasons. So I personally found it difficult to reconcile all of these things in Tromsø. The options with more affordable rates were often private rooms and not as centrally located. Renting an entire apartment was often more expensive than the hotel rates and the few well-priced options had less than ten reviews. I think it’ll be really interesting to watch the hospitality scene in Tromsø ramp up over the next year or so— the influx of new properties on Airbnb is certainly a sign that it’s coming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f2 mt5 mb4&quot; id=&quot;whattodo&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;What To Do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://enjoythearctic.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Chase the Northern Lights&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/lights_1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/lights_2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is what you come to Tromsø for. There's a whole industry around northern light tours and it's fascinating to me because despite being independent competitors all the tour guides essentially work together and constantly communicate with each other throughout the night so that if one person finds the lights, everyone else does too. You'll notice that the tours are often describe as northern light &quot;chases&quot; and that's because there's no guarantee you'll actually see one. But if you pay for a tour these guys will do everything possible to make sure you do. It was raining the night I went on my tour and our guide drove us three hours across the border into Finland to find us a clear patch of sky. The place we ended up, Kilpisjärvi, was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.afar.com/magazine/get-intimate-with-the-aurora-borealis-in-the-finnish-wilderness?inspiration=outdoor-adventure&amp;amp;sub_inspiration=winter-sports&amp;amp;email=sabrinaymajeed%40gmail.com&amp;amp;utm_source=Sailthru&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_campaign=northern%20lights&amp;amp;utm_term=Daily%20Wander%20Newsletter&quot;&gt;recently featured in a recent article by Away&lt;/a&gt; as the best place to view the lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tours can be a little pricey (around $150 per person) and many of my friends have opted instead to rent a car and find the lights on their own. However, since I was traveling alone I felt more comfortable going on a tour and looking back on it I think the price was justified for the total experience. Most of the tours limit themselves to about 12 people, the amount that can fit into a small van. It's a really intimate experience and actually great for meeting other travelers because, at least in my case, it was a nine hour long experience. Three hours driving to find the lights, three hours camping out for them, and three hours driving back to Tromsø. The vans are equipped with high speed wifi for the long drive and the guides were incredibly knowledgable and prepared— ours brought snow suites for everyone as well as hot tea and coffee, and set up a campfire and cooked everyone reindeer hotdogs. Most of the guides are also professional photographers who can help you adjust your camera to the proper settings to capture the lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking the gas, food provided, and expertise of the guide and the cost of living in Norway, I felt like the cost of the tour was worth it in the end for me. The specific tour I went on was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g190475-d6583184-Reviews-Enjoy_the_Arctic-Tromso_Troms_Northern_Norway.html&quot;&gt;Enjoy the Artic&lt;/a&gt; with Andrei, who was amazing, but from what I understand the experience is consistent across the main tours you can find on TripAdvisor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/reindeer.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bardus.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Reindeer Ragout @ Bardus Bistro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite places I ate in all of Norway. Bardus is a cozy little gastropub with the friendliest staff (the waitress gave me tons of suggestions on things to do in Tromsø). But more importantly I had this creamy reindeer ragout with lingonberries and it was so, so good (sorry, Rudolph). They also serve beer from a local brewery in town, in small glasses which was the perfect portion size for me and also a really great way to avoid getting hammered over lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/cathedral.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ishavskatedralen.no/en/the-arctic-cathedral/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Arctic Cathedral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tromsdalen Church, a.k.a Ishavskatedralen a.k.a the Arctic Cathedral is the northernmost cathedral in the world. It's a wonderful example of Scandinavian architecture and was designed by architect Jan Inge Hovig in the 60's, with glass mosaics by Norwegian artist Victor Sparre added to the building in the 70's. The unique structure provides for excellent acoustics so many concerts are held at the cathedral. The cathedral is located across a winding bridge from Tromsø's city center. It's about a twenty minute walk across the bridge from start to finish.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.polaria.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Polaria&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/polaria.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Polaria is the world's northernmost aquarium and a great option for families with young children (although this adult still had fun by herself). The museum itself is rather small (I probably spent a little less than an hour there) but provides an interactive and educational overview of the area's marine ecology. The main attraction is an open pool with bearded seals, with a live feeding show twice a day. The architecture is also a part of the appeal and is an abstract representation of ice floes pushing up against land. Entrance fees are around $15 for adults and $8 for kids, although they do occasionally have discounted prices (the day I went entrance was 50% off).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/mathallen.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mathallentromso.no/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mathallen Tromsø&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mathallen may be more familiar to those who've visited the famous food hall in Oslo. This outpost is much smaller and includes a fine dining restaurant and a speciality deli that also makes for a great place to pick up gifts to take home like reindeer jerky. As for the restaurant, they offer a 4-course tasting menu for approx. $86 per person. Ingredients sold in the deli and used in the restaurant are all locally sourced across Norway.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 mb4&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/tromso/svalbard.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl4-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 mb1 lh-title mt0-ns mt3&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;Visit Svalbard&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TBH I'm kind of kicking myself for not spending more time in Tromso, because if I could re-do my trip I would spend less time in Olso and Bergen in order to fit in a trip to Svalbard, an archipelago located a little under two hours north from Tromso by plane. Svalbard is home to the northernmost settlement with a  permanent population (meaning, not researchers). In fact, people often say there are more polar bears in Svalbard than people. In addition to polar bears there are arctic foxes, reindeer, blue whales, narwhals, and a host of other marine species. Fun fact: after Norwegians, Thais are the most populous immigrant group in Svalbard.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f7 light-silver&quot;&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/cmichel67/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Christopher Michel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where to stay in Bedford-Stuyvesant for under $100 per night</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-bed-stuy-brooklyn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where to stay in Bedford-Stuyvesant for under $100 per night" /><published>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-bed-stuy-brooklyn</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/where-to-stay-bed-stuy-brooklyn/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/baschtelt/10782896243/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/bedstuy/bedstuy_header.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the thing about Bed-Stuy is, there really aren’t many hotels in the neighborhood. Which makes sense because it’s largely a residential neighborhood and not a huge business or tourist center. The dearth of hotels presents a huge opportunity to live like a local in one of the many brownstone apartments available on Airbnb. When compared to the cost of hotels in Brooklyn, this option also tends to be a lot more affordable. In fact, we originally set out to make a list of “the best” places to stay in Bed-Stuy and fortuitously all the places we chose just happened to fall under $100/night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who feel more comfortable staying in a hotel or are concerned about wheelchair accessibility, we recommend &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thebrooklynny.com/?WT.srch=1&amp;amp;WT.mc_id=PPC2P&amp;amp;DCSext.ppc_kw=the+brooklyn+hotel&amp;amp;ppc_ac=Brand&amp;amp;ppc_ag=Brand+Exact&amp;amp;ppc_mt=Exact&amp;amp;platform=c&quot;&gt;The Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt; on Atlantic, with rates starting at $110/night in February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt5 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Solo-Travellers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/15883070?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=247693292&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Homey Room&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $39/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/homey1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/homey2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guests can stay in one of two available bedrooms in this light-filled apartment, which is shared with the host, Carolina, and her partner. Many reviewers remarked on how clean the apartment was, and positively commented on the amount of privacy afforded for a shared space. If you’re a solo traveller that prefers other humans around, or one who just doesn’t want to pay extra for space you won’t use, Carolina’s apartment is perfect for you and just three blocks from the nearest G train station.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/1148279?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=KpNNNYLn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Family Owned &amp;amp; Operated Brownstone&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $60/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/family1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/family2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For solo-travellers who prefer having the privacy of an entire unit to themselves, look no further than Yoki’s renovated 1800’s brownstone. The apartment is full of historic touches like carved wood and stained glass. The unit is quite cozy, so while it can fit up to 3 guests, for the price we think it’s reasonable to go solo on this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Couples &amp;amp; Close Friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/6500246?wl_source=list&amp;amp;wl_id=247693292&amp;amp;role=wishlist_owner&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Brownstone Building&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $60/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/brownstone1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/brownstone2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This historic brownstone straddles the border between Bed-Stuy and its neighboring neighborhood (heh) Clinton Hill. Donovan’s apartment is not only filled with antiques and unique treasures, it’s a treasure in itself because of the shared backyard space you have access to. Any New Yorker will tell you, that’s quite the rarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/9155021?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=KpNNNYLn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Spacious &amp;amp; Luminous Room + Bath&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $89/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/spacious1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/spacious2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For couples looking for a more modern space than the traditional brownstone, there’s Linda and Dorian’s townhouse. The guest unit is located on the basement floor but couldn’t look more inviting. And they weren’t kidding about the ‘spacious’ part. The unit has high ceilings and enough room for a bed, working area, and lounging area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For Families&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17339881?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=8oL8nuCP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Brownstone Studio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $99/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/studio1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/studio2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly this is my favorite Airbnb on the list. Michelle’s cozy brownstone studio gets gorgeous light and looks so inviting. It’s actually just fine for a couple or a solo traveller but because of the price (most expensive on this list) we think it’s the best value for a family traveling with young children. Though the studio can sleep 4, other reviewers have noted it can be a little tight for four adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f4 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/14359772?location=Bedford%20Stuyvesant%2C%20Brooklyn%2C%20NY%2C%20United%20States&amp;amp;adults=1&amp;amp;children=0&amp;amp;infants=0&amp;amp;tier_override=0&amp;amp;s=KpNNNYLn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;&quot;Comfy Home Away from Home&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $89/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/comfy1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/comfy2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A family of four or group of friends would feel totally comfortable in Pamela’s space. There are two other rooms in the apartment available for rent, making it a true guest-house. The kitchen is spacious for New York standards and many reviewers noted how clean and modern the bathroom facilities are. The other thing they noted? That Pamela is a natural born host.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;This airbnb is not wheelchair accessible.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">10 places to feed your stomache and your soul in Bed-Stuy, Brooklyn</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 places to feed your stomache and your soul in Bed-Stuy, Brooklyn" /><published>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-20T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/where-to-eat-bed-stuy-brooklyn/">&lt;p class=&quot;mt3&quot;&gt;This is the InnBox’s first list that’s exclusively about food and boy, is it personal. I hesitate to even say these are “the best” places to eat at in Bed-Stuy, it’s more like these are the places which I often frequented during my time living in the neighborhood (so don’t be surprised if you notice a disproportionate amount of Asian restaurants featured here). Bed-Stuy is also a very big neighborhood and many of these eateries are located on the west side, closer to where I’m based and near the Bedford-Nostrand G stop as well as the Franklin Avenue C stop.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
I’m also not going to talk too much about already very popular Bed-Stuy establishments like Speedy Romeo’s, Peaches Hothouse, and Dough. These spots are all wonderful and have been featured extensively on several lists about the neighborhood’s dining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foursquare.com/v/750-myrtle-diner/554ac24b498e13945411029d&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;750 Myrtle Diner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Japanese&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/myrtle1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/myrtle2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually found this place because I was looking at nearby cafes with free wifi and their name popped up on the list. I assumed 750 Myrtle Diner was a diner in the traditional American sense but it turned out to be a lovely Japanese diner that’s only open for dinners. Their menu changes daily although fan favorites like the Pon-Kara (their take on karaage) seem to be frequently available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.molokobarnyc.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Moloko&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/moloko.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moloko is run by the team behind Dynaco, a more popular bar further south in Bed-Stuy. But unlike Dynaco, Moloko offers both drinks and food. It’s a true neighborhood bar and a great place to go for a low-key dinner with friends. They have great happy hour specials and a simple, mostly stable menu, the highlights of which are their burger and the seared tuna sandwich. It is, however, cash only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.evajeans.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eva Jean's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;New American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/evajeans1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/evajeans2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This place is literally on my block and according to Foursquare I’ve been there twelve times… which is, probably the most times I’ve ever been to any restaurant in New York. Eva Jean’s is basically my go-to for any occasion: date night, special occassions, catching up with friends, brunch, happy hour (which they dub ‘magic hour’), coffee… It’s the kind of like the room of requirement. The cuisine is New American which kind of means anything goes, and my some of my favorite dishes have been their pastrami eggs benedict and white bean soup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.swelldive.nyc/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Swell Dive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Filipino &amp;amp; Tex-Mex&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/swelldive1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/swelldive2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swell Dive serves filipino tacos and tiki-style drinks. It’s the newest venture from the owners of another Bed-Stuy establishment, Brooklyn Kolache Co. If you’re from Texas you may be putting two and two together right about now… tacos… and kolaches? Yep, they’re from Austin. And every weekend Swell Dive serves breakfast tacos until 3 p.m. They offer both classic Tex-Mex style breakfast tacos as well as Filipino breakfast tacos— I usually order one of each. When visiting in warmer weather, don’t forget to also check out their backyard patio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldakitchen.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Golda&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Mediterranean &amp;amp; American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/golda1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/golda2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually just went here last week on my neighborhood bucket-list tour and fell in love. Not only were the staff exceptionally kind and attentive, it’s hard to decide what to order from the experimental and mediterranean-inspired menu because everything looks so good. I settled on the eggplant menemen— a delicious mix of tomato sauce, eggs, saffron yogurt, and vegetables served with toast— and was not disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pilarny.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pilar Cuban Eatery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Cuban&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/pilar.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pilar was actually the first restaurant I ever ate at in Bed-Stuy, long before I lived here. It’s got one of the most beautiful bars in the neighborhood, generous portions (the cuban sandwich is huge), and the best dessert— guava cheesecake. Almost all the entrees are under $20 with the exception of a seafood paella.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.captdansgoodtimetavern.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Captain Dan's Good Time Tavern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Southern &amp;amp; American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/dan.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/dan2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Affordable, southern-inspired brunch. Need I say more? I mean, technically it’s a bar so you can drink here too but honestly I’ve mostly come here when I’m nursing a hangover and desperately need fried, carb-loaded food in my stomach stat. Pretty much everything on their brunch menu is good but the best value is the chicken biscuit sandwich for around $7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/The-Civil-Service-Cafe-190890911113655/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Civil Service Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/civil1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/civil2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Civil Service is sort of my go-to weekday cafe to work from. It’s usually not too crowded (emphasis on “weekday” because the weekends are a different story), they make a great chai latte, and a mean breakfast sandwich with avocado and hot sauce. The team behind Civil Service also recently opened &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/TheTradeUnionCafe/&quot;&gt;Trade Union cafe&lt;/a&gt; on Malcolm X Blvd further east in Bed-Stuy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nostrandcafe.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nostrand Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Korean &amp;amp; American&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 pr1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/nostrand.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nostrand Cafe is an unpretentious and spacious coffeeshop that also serves really good, and simple Korean food. They also offer standard American breakfast and brunch fare with the option to add Bulgogi for an extra fee. Disclaimer: I’m not Korean but I think their bibimbap is pretty solid and the portions are generous. They also serve Korean-fusion items like bulgogi tacos and burritos, and the staff are always super friendly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.samuraipapabk.com/&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samurai Papa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Japanese&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/samurai1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/bedstuy/samurai2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Samurai Papa isn’t my favorite ramen place in New York City by any means, but it is the closest ramen spot to my apartment and it’s more than decent. They have great lunch specials, really affordable appetizers (we’re talking in the $6 and under range), and a simple ramen menu. I’ve tried both their curry ramen— yum— and their bukkake vegan tomato ramen which was less good, but I’m glad there’s an option for the vegans in the neighborhood. Samurai Papa used to be a lot emptier when it was standing-room only, but now that they’ve added seating you can expect it to be a little more crowded at dinner time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html">This is the InnBox’s first list that’s exclusively about food and boy, is it personal. I hesitate to even say these are “the best” places to eat at in Bed-Stuy, it’s more like these are the places which I often frequented during my time living in the neighborhood (so don’t be surprised if you notice a disproportionate amount of Asian restaurants featured here). Bed-Stuy is also a very big neighborhood and many of these eateries are located on the west side, closer to where I’m based and near the Bedford-Nostrand G stop as well as the Franklin Avenue C stop. I’m also not going to talk too much about already very popular Bed-Stuy establishments like Speedy Romeo’s, Peaches Hothouse, and Dough. These spots are all wonderful and have been featured extensively on several lists about the neighborhood’s dining.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The 7 best boutique hotels in Paris under $300</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/best-boutique-hotels-paris/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The 7 best boutique hotels in Paris under $300" /><published>2017-11-12T11:10:36+07:00</published><updated>2017-11-12T11:10:36+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/best-boutique-hotels-paris</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/best-boutique-hotels-paris/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/paris_header.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week we covered how Austin is the king city of Airbnbs in terms of quantity and quality. Well, you could say the same for Paris with its endless supply of top notch boutique hotels. There are an almost overwhelming amount of options, all with their own character and many at a surprisingly affordable price for a city with such an expensive reputation. We’ve narrowed down our top picks to help you find the perfect Parisian place for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;tc f6 light-silver i mt4 mb4&quot;&gt;Rates are based on a one-night search for January 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For living like a local — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lespiaules.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Les Piaules&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $30/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lespiales1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lespiales2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the recent proliferation of out-of-the-box hostel chains in Europe, it’s always refreshing to come across independently owned hostels that are done well. Les Pialues is located in the up and coming neighborhood of Belleville, a bit farther from many of Paris’ main tourist attractions. The hostel features a custom designed bunk bed intended to improve and reinvent the standard hostel experience. There’s also a poppin’ bar downstairs for guests and locals alike. Shared rooms start as low as $30 and private rooms at $102.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Les Piaules is wheelchair accessible and has roll-in showers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For families — &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.astotel.com/hotel/monterosa-en/overview&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hôtel Monterosa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $133/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/monterosa1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/monterosa2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monterosa is the first hotel we’ve featured on The InnBox that’s belongs to a chain, but to be fair the chain in question, Astotel, only operates in Paris. They run 16 hotels all of which are somewhat similar in their design, highly reviewed, and kind on the budget. I personally stayed at the Monterosa and thought it had a great location, being walking distance to both Pigalle and Saint Georges metro stations. The decor is modern and clean, continental breakfast is provided, and we spent countless nights just hanging out drinking tea in the little lobby cafe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel Monterosa has an elevator but does not have facilities specifically for handicapped guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For New Yorkers at heart — &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotelpanache.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel Panache&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $143/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/panache1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/panache2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The building that houses Hotel Panache has no right angles— it’s triangular shape gives it something in common with the iconic Flatiron building in New York City, and thus that’s where Panache’s industrial designer drew her inspiration. The Flatiron was finished in 1902, so at Panache you’ll find many examples of art nouveau, the major art movement on the time. While each room is uniquely decorated (including one with this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cole-and-son.com/en/collection-fornasetti/wallpaper-77/7024/&quot;&gt;malachite wallpaper&lt;/a&gt; I’d sell my unborn child for), they all feature a custom headboard inspired by Thonet bentwood chairs. New Yorkers who’ve spent a lot of time in the Flatiron neighborhood will feel right at home here. We’ve also heard a rumor that if you are traveling with small children they will bring a miniature teepee to your room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Second and third floors are accessible by elevator and there are facilities for wheelchair users. Hotel Panache rates are typically above $300 but you can often find discounted rates for under $250.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For design nerds — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.coqhotelparis.com/en/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;COQ Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $158/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/coq1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/coq2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COQ is a reference to both the bird and an acronym for “community of quality”. That quality comes through in the curated furnishings like wooden flooring from Limogues and vintage Kilim rugs from Turkey and Moldova. The hotel, which was designed to invoke the sense of being in a family home, also has a dark and muted, almost masculine vibe— a welcome departure from the more clinical white rooms that have become on-trend as of late. The hotel also has a greenhouse and a small courtyard with a chicken coop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel COQ has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For minimalists — &lt;a href=&quot;https://hotel-lapin-blanc.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Le Lapin Blanc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $166/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lapinblanc1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/lapinblanc2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meaning “the white rabbit”, Le Lapin Blanc is an ode to Alice in Wonderland without coming across too twee. The decor is all muted millennial pastels against snowy whites, with interesting details like carpet cut-outs that transition into bathroom tile and geometric tubs. Le Lapin Blanc is located in the Latin Quarter, a stone’s throw away from the Sorbonne as well as the famous bookstore Shakespeare and Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Le Lapin Blanc has an elevator but does not have facilities specifically for handicapped guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For trendsetters — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hotelfabric.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel Fabric&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $175/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/fabric1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/fabric2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hotel that’s a little more Hermès than Chanel. Housed in a former textile factory, Hotel Fabric pays tribute to its history through its playful and colorful combinations of patterns and textures, such as the fanciful tile work in the bathrooms. While it’s located in a less touristy area it’s still within walking distance to many of Paris’ major attractions but the real value is in its proximity to the fashionable nightlife and restaurant scene in Oberkampf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel Fabric has an elevator and wheelchair accessible facilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;f3 pt3 lh-title&quot; style=&quot;font-family: 'Gilroy-ExtraBold'&quot;&gt;For the honeymoond period — &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hoteldejobo.paris/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;link underline-hover orange&quot;&gt;Hotel de JOBO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;f5 light-silver&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Starting at $272/Night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pr1-ns mb1 mb0-ns&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/jobo1.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fl w-100 w-50-ns pl1-ns mb3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../images/paris/jobo2.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hotel is a homage to the former social and empress of France, Josephine Bonaparte (get it? Jo..Bo?). The decor references Josephine’s tastes, like her fondness for roses or her credit for being the first to sport a leopard print rug. The building, a former convent. features 24 rooms, most of which feature revitalized Directoire-era wallpaper and empire style beds. There’s an undeniable air of romance here, making it perfect for new couples who can’t get enough of each other or time-tested romances looking to rekindle the flame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;f6 i light-silver&quot;&gt;Hotel de JOBO has facilities for disabled guests.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sabrina Majeed</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>